<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ViralMuffin</title>
	<atom:link href="http://viralmuffin.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://viralmuffin.com/</link>
	<description>Discover the World</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 17:37:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Gardenscapes Hack &#8211; Gardenscapes New Acres Hack</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/gardenscapes-hack/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=105</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/gardenscapes-hack/">Gardenscapes Hack &#8211; Gardenscapes New Acres Hack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first working Gardenscapes Hack. Hack Gardenscapes New Acres for free and receive unlimited coins or stars. Enjoy Gardenscapes to it&#8217;s fullest. You can access the hack <a href="http://viralmuffin.com/hacks">here </a>or click &#8220;Go to Generator&#8221; below.</p>
<h1 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://viralmuffin.com/hacks">Go to Generator</a></h1>
<h3>Gardenscapes Hack:</h3>
<p>The Gardenscapes hack was made by an experienced team of app developers with one simple goal in mind, we want people to enjoy apps to the fullest. We make all of our tools completely free to ensure everyone can use them. You can use the Gardenscapes hack by pressing &#8220;Go to Generator&#8221; above.</p>
<h3>Gardenscapes New Acres:</h3>
<p>Welcome to Gardenscapes! Enter a story full of unexpected twists and give your splendor to a wonderful garden!</p>
<p>Embark on an authentic adventure: Beat levels, restore and decorate different areas of the garden, discover the secrets you hide and have fun with the friendly characters in the game, including Austin, your butler! What are you waiting for? Build the garden of your dreams!</p>
<p>Game Features:<br />
● A unique play style: swap and match, restores and decorates the garden, and follows an amazing storyline. Everything at once!<br />
● Hundreds of unique combination levels.<br />
● Dozens of characters in the game that can be your friends.<br />
● A lovely pet always ready to cheer you up.<br />
● A social gaming network that you can use to get the latest news.<br />
● Different areas in the garden with unique structures: broken fountains, mysterious labyrinths and much more.<br />
● Community comes first: your Facebook friends can be your neighbors!</p>
<p>Gardenscapes is played for free, but some game items can be bought for real money.</p>
<p>Having fun with Gardenscapes? Find out more about the game!<br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Gardenscapes">https://www.facebook.com/Gardenscapes </a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/gardenscapes_mobile/">https://www.instagram.com/gardenscapes_mobile/ </a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/garden_scapes">https://twitter.com/garden_scapes</a></p>
<p>Gardenscapes: New Acres is overall a great game that will keep you hooked. Try it out for free at the <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/gardenscapes-new-acres/id1105855019">App Store</a> or <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.playrix.gardenscapes">Google Play store</a>.</p>
<p><img class="gardenscapes hack aligncenter" title="gardenscapes hack" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hMyYwLOEm4hqw_16GmBhxict2_UYwLelRG2hzrJtxobEJv8gtk1buVBPSDXcvM6AU3U=h900" alt="gardenscapes hack" width="1440" height="900" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Gardenscapes Hack Last Thoughts:</h3>
<p>Well what are you waiting for? Go and use the Gardenscapes hack now!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/gardenscapes-hack/">Gardenscapes Hack &#8211; Gardenscapes New Acres Hack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Graj King of Thieves</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/graj-king-of-thieves/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=98</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/graj-king-of-thieves/">Graj King of Thieves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://movfe.com/srv.html?id=1418014&amp;pub=779619">Zagraj teraz!</a></h1>
<p>Ubierz klejnoty, buduj swoją obronę i wygrywaj wojnę gildii w tej unikalnej kombinacji gry zręcznościowej, platformy i multiplayer PVP!<br />
Konkurować z ponad 50 milionami użytkowników na całym świecie i tworzyć własne klany złodziei. Przenieś się do lochu wroga i ukradnij złoto.<br />
Udowodnij, że jesteś najmądrzejszym i najzdolniejszym złodziejem na świecie!</p>
<p>UWAGA: gra jest bardzo wciągająca i nieuchronnie prowadzi do zwiększenia liczby Twoich znajomych.</p>
<p>KLUCZOWE CECHY:</p>
<p>STANDARDOWE WYDARZENIA. Kradzieży to zabawa! Zbieraj złoto i kamienie innych graczy, aby stać się najbogatszym złodziejem na świecie.<br />
OCHRONA DWA. Zaprojektuj broń obronną, pułapki i platformy, aby uniemożliwić innym kradzież skarbu. Zobacz, jak zostali złapani w pułapki. Nie ma ucieczki, muhaha!<br />
ZAREJESTRUJ SIĘ THRONE. Zanurkuj się w akcji, zwiększ swoje umiejętności i konkurować z innymi graczami na całym świecie, aby przejść na szczyty liderów.<br />
JOIN GUILD. Znajdź wiarygodne dudy i ogłaszaj wojnę innym gildiom. Wygraj epickie walki klanów!<br />
DOSTOSUJ TWÓJ WYDAJNOŚĆ. Wybierz fajny kostium, który idealnie pasuje do twojej osobowości. Bądź eleganckim złodziejem, wyróżnij się z tłumu!<br />
PODRÓŻ I PRZEGLĄD. Sprawdź swoją zwinność dzięki 112 poziomom pojedynczego trybu lub zanurz się w podziemnym świecie treści generowanych przez użytkowników.<br />
_________________________________________________________<br />
SUBSKRYPCJA. Subskrybuj, aby mieć szansę szybszego i szybkiego dostępu do ekskluzywnych kostiumów!</p>
<p>Poprzez subskrypcję Króla Złodziei otrzymuje się:<br />
&#8211; blokady x10 (zwiększenie maksymalnej pojemności)<br />
&#8211; Odblokowanie blokady bloków jest szybsze od x10<br />
&#8211; Kopalnia złota wytwarza codziennie &#8220;łzy&#8221;<br />
&#8211; 3 unikalne stroje<br />
_________________________________________________________</p>
<p>Gotowi sprostać wyzwaniu? Gra na!<br />
Dołącz do społeczności, znajdź przyjaciół i sprawdź wiadomości:<br />
<a href="http://www.facebook.com/kingofthievesgame">www.facebook.com/kingofthievesgame</a><br />
<a href="http://www.twitter.com/kingthieves">www.twitter.com/kingthieves</a><br />
&#8220;Król złodziei to dobrze zaprojektowane wyzwanie dla wielu graczy, które pozwoli Ci wrócić i zdecydowanie ukradnia ofertę bezpłatnej rozrywki&#8221; &#8211; Apple&#8217;N&#8217;Apps</p>
<p>&#8220;Król złodziei to najcudowniejsza gra PvP, która może się pojawić od dłuższego czasu. Dobrze być zły, więc idź dalej i rozkoszuj się &#8220;- Gamezebo</p>
<p>&#8220;King of Thieves jest jednym z największych aplikacjach tam” &#8211; App Mag</p>
<p>&#8220;King of Thieves to z pewnością warto go wypróbować gry teraz” &#8211; ZoGames</p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/BPVU1uxVIK_gZy_JS5Lbsa_TQ0TKeR-18hhrZW5kfL-aBTGgHTZvLyM8zjMWbkispQ=h900-rw" alt=" King of Thieves – zrzut ekranu " /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/graj-king-of-thieves/">Graj King of Thieves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Win een reis naar De Maldiven voor jezelf en je gezin!</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/win-een-reis-naar-de-maldiven-voor-jezelf-en-je-gezin/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=95</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/win-een-reis-naar-de-maldiven-voor-jezelf-en-je-gezin/">Win een reis naar De Maldiven voor jezelf en je gezin!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://movfe.com/srv.html?id=350777&amp;pub=779619">Ga nu binnen!</a></h1>
<h3>Waarom ga naar de Maldiven</h3>
<p>Beeld het: Een prive-villa staat over kristalblauw water; Dagen eindigen met oranje zonsondergangen die je hongerig maken voor lokale citrusvruchten; Gastronomische roomservice en een masseuse zijn op gesprek om onnodige uitstapjes te voorkomen op uw veranda; En het enige dat je wilt verlaten is het adembenemende koraalrif en onderwaterbeesten die een scuba-sessie vragen voor een goede introductie. Dit zijn de Maldiven.</p>
<p>Als u dat cliché Caribisch strandverblijf (de Bahama&#8217;s) of dat trendy Zuid-Pacifische retraite wilt (zie Bora Bora) niet wilt, moet u naar de Maldiven wagen. Het bereiken van en verblijf in dit tropische paradijs vereist geduld (d.w.z. geen directe vluchten vanuit de staten) en overvloedig geld. Gelegen tussen de Arabische en Laccadive zee, ongeveer 500 mijl ten zuidwesten van Sri Lanka, zijn de Maldiven ongeveer zo geïsoleerd als u kunt krijgen (of zou dat toch wel willen). En terwijl de regering en de economie van het land onlangs in vloed is geweest, is de sublieme aard van dit paradijs constant gebleven in de dromen van reizigers.</p>
<h3>Hoe geld te sparen in de Maldiven</h3>
<p>Kies vluchten Wisely Airfare van de Staten is ongelooflijk duur en een van de belangrijkste redenen waarom de Maldiven geen Amerikaanse toeristische hotspot zijn geworden. Als u hier een vakantie kunt koppelen met een in het Midden-Oosten of Europa (waar u directe vluchten kunt krijgen), dan is de kosten minder belachelijk.<br />
Kies Accommodaties Zorgvuldig &#8220;Budget&#8221; accommodaties bestaan ​​niet hier; Zelfs de low-end hotels zijn overvloedig en adverteren stevige prijskaartjes. Zo vermijd de duurste eigenschappen, omdat eten, drinken en excursies er ook een arm en been kosten.<br />
Overweeg all-inclusive pakketten Tarieven die airfare, hotelverblijf en maaltijden omvatten, kunnen uw gemakkelijkste en goedkoopste weddenschap zijn.</p>
<h3>Cultuur &amp; Douane</h3>
<p>De Maldiven is sinds de 12e eeuw een islamitische natie geweest. Met dit rijke erfgoed vind je religieuze tradities in de cultuur gevestigd. Moskeeën dot de hoofdstad van mannetje &#8216;, en je ziet een aantal mannen en vrouwen gekleed in zeer conservatieve kleding. Mocht u een moskee willen bezoeken, dan moet u daarover ook aantrekken; Houd er echter rekening mee dat sommige moskeeën voor niet-moslims gesloten zijn. U zult ook merken dat mensen gedurende bepaalde dagen in het openbaar bidden. Wees gerespecteerd door je stem te verlagen en niet te lopen voor degenen die bidden. De meeste van deze zichtbare culturele en religieuze tradities zijn uit de resorts getrokken. Echter, vooral tijdens Ramadan, verwacht u dat er een aantal islamitische gewoontes worden getroffen, zoals lokale restaurants die de dag sluiten wanneer de bevolking zal vasten.</p>
<p>Met 99 eilanden uit de eilanden vertrouwt de Maldiven op toerisme als dominante industrie die een groot deel van de arbeidskrachten trekt. De andere grote industrie is vissen, en deze eilandnatie exporteert zijn zeevangsten naar landen over de hele wereld. De Maldivische munt is de rufiyaa (MVR). De wisselkoers verhuist ongeveer $ 1 USD voor 15 MVR.</p>
<h3>Wat te eten</h3>
<p>De overvloedige avondeten die u bij hotels kunt proeven, zijn niets zoals die van lokale maaltijden. Wanneer u in Male &#8216;bent, probeer het dineren in een lokaal eetgelegenheid om alleen de keuken te proeven als u een stevige maag heeft. Sommige reizigers rapporteren ziekte na het consumeren van lokaal eten omdat ze hun spijsverteringskanalen niet genoeg tijd hebben om zich aan te passen aan de keuken. U vindt dat vis en rijst twee stapelgerechten van het Maldivische dieet zijn.</p>
<h3>Rond de Maldiven</h3>
<p>De beste manier om rond de Maldiven te komen is om te wandelen. De hoofdstad van Male &#8216;is slechts een vierkante kilometer, en ook welk resort je ook kiest, is ook mogelijk. Eilandhopping op je eigen vrije tijd is echt geen optie omdat het netwerk van de veerboot (of &#8220;dhoni&#8221;) niet erg uitgebreid is. Dat gezegd hebbende, als je met jacht reist, kun je deze wateren navigeren. Zodra u aankomt op Ibrahim Nasir Male International Airport (MLE) op het eiland Hulhule, wordt u waarschijnlijk begeleid door een vertegenwoordiger van uw resort naar het eiland waar u verblijft. U moet een veerboot, een taxi, een speedboot of een combinatie van de drie nemen om uw eindbestemming te bereiken. Deze laatste jaunt is soms inbegrepen in de kosten van uw hotelverblijf.</p>
<p><img class="aligncenter" src="http://travel.usnews.com/images/destinations/280/gettyimages-520025941.jpg" alt="Win een reis naar De Maldiven voor jezelf en je gezin" width="577" height="385" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/win-een-reis-naar-de-maldiven-voor-jezelf-en-je-gezin/">Win een reis naar De Maldiven voor jezelf en je gezin!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invasion: Modern Empire</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/invasion-modern-empire/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=93</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/invasion-modern-empire/">Invasion: Modern Empire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Invasion: Modern Empire is an exciting online warfare simulation and STR game type that challenges you to confront different enemy factions, conquer their territory and make their way to world domination in the midst of a global apocalypse . Fight to become the most powerful military commander in the world and walk towards victory!</p>
<p><b>Invasion Features: Modern Empire </b></p>
<p><b>Your enemies are going to nail their nails with this STR type fighting style to ward off the apocalypse! </b></p>
<p>• Military strategy, real &#8211; time fighting and building your base<br />
• Destroy the world and rebuild it in its image by conquering enemy armies<br />
• Strategic battles in 3D and real &#8211;</p>
<p><b>Action Fight for every inch of terrain and expand your Alliance territory! </b></p>
<p>• Conquer enemy territory online in a world at war<br />
• Claim territory by performing RAIDS on your enemies<br />
• Conquer is yours, as long as you have soldiers and you organize raids on your enemies. But be careful &#8211; your enemies can also attack your base!</p>
<p><b>War tactics and advanced technology will help you move forward and get information about your enemies</b></p>
<p>• Modern warfare is how to spy on your enemies. Dominate your opponents by collecting information about their bases<br />
• Command your troops and conquer territories using a panoramic map in real time! Fight against other alliances in the War of Monuments PVP!</p>
<p><b>Battle online against alliances and crush every alliance on your way</b></p>
<p>• Online multiplayer mode allows you to form an alliance and compete against other players to become the ultimate commander<br />
• Online chat and other features will help you To find the perfect alliance<br />
• Online multiplayer games feature PvP MMO combat on a modern battlefield<br />
Fight with other alliances to occupy &#8220;war monuments&#8221;<br />
• Raid monuments to experiment Changes and surprise real-time fights!<br />
• Create diplomatic ties with other players as you see fit!<br />
• PvP gameplay sends you to war alongside a ton of other players! Fight in the post-apocalyptic world of 2020!</p>
<p>Do you have what it takes to survive in this world at war?</p>
<p><b>Download Invasion: Modern Empire and beat now! </b></p>
<p>In Invasion, some game elements can also be bought for real money. If you do not want to use this feature, please set up a<br />
password protection for purchases in your Google Play Store app settings.<br />
Join the community:</p>
<p>• Facebook &#8211; <a href="https://www.facebook.com/InvasionGame">https://www.facebook.com/InvasionGame </a></p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/X29JZnCIo5foyDkJu_vCfwW7_t_OOXeGgQDsGkIvpwNx9bTyEw38rMnb2irFBUgQJk6B=h900-rw" alt=" Invasion: Modern Empire- screenshot " /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/invasion-modern-empire/">Invasion: Modern Empire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disney Magic Kingdoms</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/disney-magic-kingdoms/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=90</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/disney-magic-kingdoms/">Disney Magic Kingdoms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WELCOME TO THE MOST MAGIC PLACE ON MOBILE!</p>
<p>When Maledic will cast a curse on the Kingdom, emptying it of all its magical power, will you help us to save it? Relive the fun of Disney parks and create the most fantastic park of your dreams in Disney Magic Kingdoms!</p>
<p>ATTRACTIONS OF EXTRAORDINARY AND TIMELY DISNEY PARKS<br />
• Attractions such as &#8220;it&#8217;s a small world&#8221;, the Monsters &amp; Co. and Space Mountain laughing factory from Disney parks around the world!<br />
• Exclusive attractions such as the WALL-E House and Cyclope Sushi, all inspired by their respective films!<br />
• Relive the magic moments of the parks with the joyful parades of tanks and fireworks!</p>
<p>A RANGE OF CHARACTERS COVERING MORE THAN 90 YEARS OF DISNEY<br />
• Share spectacular moments with characters like the eternal optimist Mickey Mouse, Rapunzel the fiery princess, the courageous space ranger Buzz Lightning, the adorable and vivid Tinkerbell and many others !<br />
• Play hundreds of quests that support every pixel in your Kingdom!<br />
• Collect Disney items to save each character from the Maledic Curse!</p>
<p>A HOROSCOPE OF HEROES AND MISTAKES<br />
• Discover a magical story and an exciting adventure!<br />
• Face evil villains such as Pat Hibulaire, Mother Gothel and Zurg to save the Kingdom!</p>
<p>Come and play the most magical free mobile game, a great family adventure! It&#8217;s up to you to create your world!</p>
<p>Perfect for fans of Disney, Disneyland, Pixar movie games, management games, free family games, and park building games.</p>
<p>You can download this game for free. Please note that this game also allows you to use virtual currency which can be obtained by progressing in the game, deciding to watch some ads or spending real money. Built-in purchases range from € 0.99 to € 99.99. You can disable embedded purchases by changing your User Controls in your Play Store settings.</p>
<p>Languages: English, French, German, Italian, Indonesian, Japanese, Korean, Brazilian Portuguese, Russian, Simplified Chinese, Traditional Chinese, Spanish, Turkish, Arabic and Thai.</p>
<p>An additional download of 175 to 200 MB is required to play this game. Please note that the size of this download may change without notice.</p>
<p>The game requires an Internet connection (3G or Wi-Fi) for downloads and updates, and other features such as parties with friends, integrated purchases and viewing ads.</p>
<p>Some features of this game, such as collaborating with other players, confronting them or sharing items with them in the game, require that the player be connected to a social network like Facebook or Google+. Please note that this connection is not required to progress in the game. These features may not be available in some countries.</p>
<p>This game may contain third-party advertising that will redirect you to a third party site. You can disable the ad ID used for targeted ads in your device&#8217;s Settings menu. This option can be found in Settings&gt; Personal Accounts&gt; Google&gt; Advertisements (Settings &amp; Privacy)&gt; Disable interest-based ads.</p>
<p>For more info on the game, go to the official website &#8211; <a href="http://www.disney-magic-kingdoms.com/">http://www.disney-magic-kingdoms.com/ </a></p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/0VqHX9h9__AVhsNxldbFrOtKbhzx8mB7fRaMbtZHyC-fkepYsRr9xuyS_OMeiLdauBiQ=h900" alt="Image result for Disney Magic Kingdoms" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/disney-magic-kingdoms/">Disney Magic Kingdoms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/worlds-best-word-puzzle-game-word-cookies/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=87</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/worlds-best-word-puzzle-game-word-cookies/">The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</p>
<p>This is a new word puzzle game created by <b>BitMango, the creator of the HIT application, Roll the Ball ™ &#8211; slide puzzle and Block hexa puzzle!</b></p>
<p>Word cookies is a very fun and exciting word puzzle game, it allows you to continue playing for FREE!</p>
<p>The goal of the game is to find all the hidden words.<br />
With this game, you can easily improve vocabulary skills, concentration and spelling.</p>
<p>The king of HEADLING<br />
Do you like the word puzzle games? Do you like cookies? Do you like the challenge?<br />
Here is the perfect game for you, Word cookies!</p>
<p>Are you ready to find delicious cookie words at your kitchen oven?<br />
Embrace your intelligence to discover words.</p>
<p>HOW TO PLAY<br />
• Words can be vertical, horizontal, diagonal and even backward.<br />
• Simply slide your finger over a word to select it.<br />
• If you have found a valid word, it will remain highlighted and marked on the list of found words.</p>
<p>Characters<br />
• Discover hidden words in mixed letters<br />
• Find words derived from the main words and develop your brain skills and vocabulary.<br />
• Visually pleasing to play cookies in various types!<br />
• Feeling complete with increased points by making more cookies!<br />
• Simple and easy!<br />
• Daily rewards<br />
• 200 free coins in the first round<br />
• Excellent exercise for the brain<br />
• Available for both laptops and tablets.<br />
• FREE update!</p>
<p>• EASY AND FUN GAME<br />
&#8211; Easy to learn and fun to master the game</p>
<p>• No time limit<br />
&#8211; Enjoy the game anytime, anywhere and even for a little while.</p>
<p>• No WIFI? No problem!<br />
&#8211; You can play offline at any time</p>
<p>• TONS OF UNIQUE LEVELS<br />
&#8211; 32 packages and over 580 impressive levels! Updates will be continued!</p>
<p>NOTES<br />
• Enjoy the game with various devices (laptops and tablets).<br />
• &#8220;Word cookies&#8221; contain banner ads, interstitial ads, videos.<br />
• &#8220;Word cookies&#8221; is free to play, but you can buy items like Non-Pubs and other packages on the shop in this game.</p>
<p>E-MAIL<br />
• contact@bitmango.com</p>
<p>SITE<br />
• <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?Id=6249013288401661340">https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?Id=6249013288401661340</a></p>
<p>Put it Like on FACEBOOK<br />
• <a href="https://www.facebook.com/BitMangoGames">https://www.facebook.com/BitMangoGames</a></p>
<p>Thank you for playing!</p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hCRo0pQmXiUJ_VJcnmHe87ti8jP268EEBF0pca4td7cfq97_TCVBz5xknvW6XRtWKw=h900" alt="Image result for Word Cookies" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/worlds-best-word-puzzle-game-word-cookies/">The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire Hacks Cheats Glitches</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/final-fantasy-xv-a-new-empire-hacks-cheats-glitches/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 01:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=80</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/final-fantasy-xv-a-new-empire-hacks-cheats-glitches/">Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire Hacks Cheats Glitches</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://viralmuffin.com/hacks">Access Hack</a></h1>
<p>Hack Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire with our free tool above. Generate free resources, gold or whatever you need. Press the button above to access Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire Hacks.</p>
<h2>About Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire</h2>
<p><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/final-fantasy-xv-a-new-empire/id1186994231?mt=8">Apple Store</a>, <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.epicactiononline.ffxv.ane">Play Store</a></p>
<p>Experience a great adventure in the world of Final Fantasy with the newest free mobile strategy game Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire! Build your kingdom, discover powerful magical powers and form alliances with your friends to impose you!</p>
<p>Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire is a mobile adventure game that allows you to rediscover Final Fantasy XV from a new angle in order to fulfill your outstanding destiny. Go freely through vast kingdoms, collect gems and magical resources to build the most powerful empire in Final Fantasy history! Form alliances with your friends and battle your enemies with millions of players from around the world! Will your team&#8217;s strategy be up to take possession of the crystal and dominate the kingdom?</p>
<p>✔ Let your imagination speak! Experience your own adventure in the world of FFXV on your mobile phone with this free application!</p>
<p>✔ Dive into action and team up with Noctis, Cindy and all your favorite FF15 characters!</p>
<p>✔ Defend your friends and eliminate your opponents in legendary battles with millions of players from around the world!</p>
<p>✔ Raise a great army, create alliances and develop the best strategy to win epic battles in real time!</p>
<p>✔ Free to create the ultimate guild or combine with powerful forces!</p>
<p>✔ Choose the right strategy with your guild to crush monsters and enemies in real-time battles!</p>
<p>✔ Compete with players from around the world to capture the crystal!</p>
<p>✔ Explore the different kingdoms, accumulate rare resources and grab the crystal to build an empire of epic proportions!</p>
<p>✔ Enter legend by taking control of the crystal to dominate the kingdom!</p>
<p>Let your imagination run wild in an epic world where the only rules are magic. Will your empire stand the test of time or will it collapse?</p>
<p>Your legend begins now in the new MMORPG game Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire. A free application, where the only limit is your imagination!</p>
<p><img class="alignnone" src="https://assets.vg247.com/current//2017/06/ff15_new_empire3.jpg" alt="Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire" width="887" height="600" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/final-fantasy-xv-a-new-empire-hacks-cheats-glitches/">Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire Hacks Cheats Glitches</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pacman &#8211; Spielen Sie kostenlose Online Pacman Spiel und Frau Pacman (Pac Man)</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/spielen-sie-kostenlose-online-pacman/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 19:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=68</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/spielen-sie-kostenlose-online-pacman/">Pacman &#8211; Spielen Sie kostenlose Online Pacman Spiel und Frau Pacman (Pac Man)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://viralmuffin.com/play-pacman"> <img class="aligncenter" src="http://www.pngmart.com/files/3/Play-Now-Button-PNG-Free-Download.png" alt="Pacman" width="634" height="170" /> </a></p>
<h3></h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Pacman Gameplay</h3>
<p>Das Ziel des Spiels ist es, die Geister zu vermeiden und so viele gelbe Punkte wie möglich zu essen, um auf die nächste Stufe zu kommen! Dieses pacman Spiel bietet auch Highscores! Sehen Sie, wie Ihre pacman Fähigkeiten vergleichen und wenn Sie mit den Besten der Besten konkurrieren können!</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Pacman Hintergrund</h3>
<p>Pacman, war die Ikone der 1980er-Pop-Kultur und ein Grundnahrungsmittel in jedem Arcade-Spielzimmer. Seit seiner Geburt wuchs Pacman zu einer der beliebtesten Spielfiguren aller Zeiten. Die Ikone der achtziger Jahre Popkultur, wurde zu einer der beliebtesten Spielfiguren aller Zeiten. Die Basis des Spiels ist so einfach und doch genial. Kleiner gelber Pacman schlägt sich um den Vorstand, der Pellets sammelt, während er gleichzeitig weg von den Geistern bleibt.</p>
<p>Das Pacman-Spiel wurde von Namco erstellt und lizenziert für den Vertrieb in den USA von Midway im Oktober 1980. Pacman ist sicher einer der Klassiker und definitiv einer der Ikonen der Popkultur ala die gerne von anderen beliebten Spielen wie Mario, Tetris und Frogger Zu diesem heutigen Tag ist Pacman immer noch stark mit Bekleidungswaren, Videospielen und Arcade-Maschinen immer noch auf der ganzen Welt!</p>
<p>Ersetzen Sie die klassischen Arcade-Spiele, können Sie jetzt genießen pacman online. Sie können pacman aus dem Komfort Ihres eigenen Hauses dank der Internet und mobilen Geräten spielen. Achten Sie darauf, immer pacman online hier zu spielen! Jubel und Spaß haben, sich an diesen Pellets und Geistern zu verjagen!</p>
<p>Pac-Man (Japanisch: パ ッ ク マ ン Hepburn: Pakkuman), stilisiert als PAC-MAN, ist ein Arcade-Spiel, das von Namco entwickelt und erstmals im Mai 1980 in Japan veröffentlicht wurde. Es wurde vom japanischen Videospiel-Designer Toru Iwatani erstellt. Es ist lizenziert für den Vertrieb in den Vereinigten Staaten von Midway Games und veröffentlicht im Oktober 1980. Pac-Man ist einer der Klassiker des Mediums und eine Ikone der 1980er Jahre populäre Kultur. Pac-Man, die Spiel-und-Fortsetzung, Pac-Man und Pac-Man, Ten Buckner und Garcia Hit Single &#8220;Pac-Man Fever&#8221;. Pac-Man war in den 1980er und 1990er Jahren beliebt und wird noch in den 2010er Jahren gespielt.</p>
<p>Als Pac-Man veröffentlicht wurde, waren die beliebtesten Arcade-Videospiele Space Shooters, insbesondere Space Invaders und Asteroiden. Die sichtbarste Minderheit waren Sportspiele. Pac-Man gelang es, ein neues Genre zu schaffen. Pac-Man ist oft mit einem Wahrzeichen im Videospiel gutgeschrieben. Es ist auch eines der höchstwertigen Videospiele aller Zeiten, haben in den 90er Jahren mehr als 2,5 Milliarden Dollar in Quartalen produziert.\</p>
<p>Der Charakter ist in mehr als 30 offiziell lizenzierten Spiel-Spin-offs, sowie in zahlreichen unautorisierten Klonen und Bootlegs erschienen. Nach dem Davie-Brown Index hat Pac-Man das höchste Markenbewusstsein für jeden Videospiel Charakter unter den amerikanischen Verbrauchern, von 94 Prozent von ihnen erkannt. Pac-Man ist eines der am längsten laufenden Videospiel-Franchise aus dem goldenen Zeitalter der Video-Arcade-Spiele. Es ist Teil der Sammlung der Smithsonian Institution in Washington, DC und New York Museum of Modern Art.</p>
<p>Der Spieler kontrolliert Pac-Man durch ein Labyrinth aus verschiedenen Punkten, bekannt als Pac-Dots, sowie vier mehrfarbige Geister: Blinky, Pinky, Inky und Clyde. Das Ziel des Spiels ist es, alle Pac-Dots in einer Bühne zu verbrauchen, um zum nächsten zu gehen. Zwischen einigen Stufen spielt eine von drei Pausen-Animationen. [23] Die vier Geister durchstreifen das Labyrinth und versuchen, Pac-Man zu fangen. Wenn irgendwelche der Geister Pac-Man berühren, verliert er ein Leben; Wenn alle Leben verloren gegangen sind, endet das Spiel. Pac-Man erhält ein einziges Bonusleben bei 10.000 Punkten standardmäßig &#8211; DIP-Schalter innerhalb der Maschine können die benötigten Punkte auf 15.000 oder 20.000 ändern oder das Bonusleben insgesamt deaktivieren. Die Anzahl der Leben kann auf 1 Leben oder bis zu fünf Leben maximal eingestellt werden. Highscore darf 999.990 Punkte nicht überschreiten; Spieler können diese Punktzahl überschreiten, aber das Spiel hält die letzten 6 Ziffern.</p>
<p>In der Nähe der Ecken des Labyrinths sind vier größere, blinkende Punkte, die als Power Pellets bekannt sind, die Pac-Man mit der vorübergehenden Fähigkeit versorgen, die Geister zu verbrauchen und Bonuspunkte zu verdienen. Die Feinde werden tiefblau, umgekehrt und bewegen sich in der Regel langsamer. Wenn ein Feind gegessen wird, bleiben seine Augen und kehren in die Mittelkiste zurück, wo er in seiner normalen Farbe regeneriert wird. Blaue Feinde blitzen weiß, um zu signalisieren, dass sie im Begriff sind, wieder gefährlich zu werden, und die Zeitdauer, für die die Feinde anfällig bleiben, variiert von einer Stufe zur nächsten, die im Allgemeinen immer kürzer wird, wenn das Spiel fortschreitet. In späteren Stadien gehen die Feinde direkt zu blinken, umgehen blau, was bedeutet, dass sie nur für eine kurze Zeit gegessen werden können, obwohl sie immer noch die Richtung umkehren, wenn ein Power Pellet gegessen wird; Beginnend in Stufe 19 werden die Geister nicht essbar (d.h. sie ändern nicht die Farbe und machen immer noch Pac-Man ein Leben auf Kontakt), aber sie immer noch Richtung umkehren. Es gibt auch Früchte, die sich direkt unterhalb der Mittelschachtel befinden, die zweimal pro Level erscheinen; Es wird zu Bonuspunkten (100-5.000) kommen.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://de.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pac-Man">Mehr Info.</a></p>
<p><a href="http://viralmuffin.com/play-pacman"><img class="aligncenter" src="http://www.pngmart.com/files/3/Play-Now-Button-PNG-Free-Download.png" alt="Pacman" width="634" height="170" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/spielen-sie-kostenlose-online-pacman/">Pacman &#8211; Spielen Sie kostenlose Online Pacman Spiel und Frau Pacman (Pac Man)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Play Pacman</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/play-pacman/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 19:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=69</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/play-pacman/">Play Pacman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><script language="javascript">
    window.location.href = "http://movfe.com/srv.html?id=1415222&pub=779619"
</script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/play-pacman/">Play Pacman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hacks</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/hacks/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 22:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=62</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/hacks/">Hacks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><noscript><meta http-equiv="refresh" content="0;url=https://www.appcaptcha.com/contentlockers/noscript.php" /></noscript><br />
<script type="text/javascript">var ogblock=true;</script><br />
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://www.appcaptcha.com/contentlockers/load.php?id=c4afa8be205cbf6ac43d607018102428"></script><br />
<script type="text/javascript">if(ogblock) window.location.href = "https://www.appcaptcha.com/contentlockers/adblock.php";</script></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/hacks/">Hacks</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
