<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Games &#8211; ViralMuffin</title>
	<atom:link href="http://viralmuffin.com/category/games/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://viralmuffin.com/</link>
	<description>Discover the World</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 07:57:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://viralmuffin.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/cropped-kawaii_muffin_by_elekmario-d5ul3eh-1-150x150.jpg</url>
	<title>Games &#8211; ViralMuffin</title>
	<link>http://viralmuffin.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/little-nightmares-secret-maws/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 07:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=153</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/little-nightmares-secret-maws/">Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="intro-article">Surfing the wave of platform / reflection games built around an enchanting or disturbing world and unspoken ones letting the imagination of the player create his own story, Little Nightmares only managed to convince half . The fault with some gameplay worries and a very nebulous narrative never arriving at the ankle of that of a Braid , Limbo or even Inside . Not surprisingly, his first DLC, Secret of The Maws , has the same strengths but also and above all the same defects.</p>
<div class="player-contenu">
<p>If I had opted for the easy solution, I could probably copy / paste part of the test of the friend Kaaraj so Secret of the Maws is itself an exact replica of the original game to this That we are incarnating this time a young boy who will try to escape from the boat-prison in which he is. Once again, do not expect to know more about the Little Nigtmares universe, the content being free from any explanation of where we are, although the end of the original game gave us some details in order to Better to apprehend this world deliciously glaucous.</p>
<h2 id="attrape-moi-si-tu-peux" class="h2-default-jv">CATCH ME IF YOU CAN</h2>
<figure class="encart-article pull-left"><img src="http://image.jeuxvideo.com/medias-sm/150143/1501429555-9046-capture-d-ecran.jpg" alt="Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws" /><figcaption>It will not be necessary to be afraid to get wet to progress</figcaption></figure>
<p>In fact, it will be necessary to be content with directing the young boy, whose escape runs in parallel of that of the young lady of the basic game, and this for a little more than thirty minutes, that is the life of the DLC. If this longevity unfortunately wants to be in line with that of the basic content, we will still be disappointed by the very great facility of extension. Indeed, <strong>each puzzle using known mechanics, we advance without any problem by generally solving every puzzle</strong> . If to complete the whole, one will be entitled to two or three purses with a terrifying creature living under the waves (here also in the vein of what one found in Little Nightmares), the same observation is necessary: ​​one Knows how the game works and c &#8216;</p>
<figure class="serie-images">
<div class="images"><img src="http://image.jeuxvideo.com/medias-sm/150143/1501429608-9051-capture-d-ecran.jpg" alt="Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws" /><img src="http://image.jeuxvideo.com/medias-sm/150143/1501429614-9100-capture-d-ecran.jpg" alt="Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws" /><img src="http://image.jeuxvideo.com/medias-sm/150143/1501429622-7376-capture-d-ecran.jpg" alt="Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws" /></div>
</figure>
<p>And this is the most frustrating because if The Secret of the Maws also has some jumping concerns about him because of his sometimes annoying depth of field, we want to stay in this bewitching universe before so much to Tim Burton that &#8221; To Jean-Pierre Jeunet. <strong>Unfortunately, the background lacks consistency and in contrast to an Inside that makes us want to go further in the analysis, The Little Nightmares rests too much on its aesthetics at the expense of its narrative frame</strong> . It is probably even more blatant with Secret of the Maws who leaves the aspect hide-and-seek leaving the player only a very short session of plate-reflection certainly superb but meaningless. Pity.</p>
<figure class="serie-images">
<div class="images"><img src="http://image.jeuxvideo.com/medias-sm/150143/1501429651-286-capture-d-ecran.jpg" alt="Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws" /><img src="http://image.jeuxvideo.com/medias-sm/150143/1501429661-9205-capture-d-ecran.jpg" alt="Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws" /><img src="http://image.jeuxvideo.com/medias-sm/150143/1501429668-3381-capture-d-ecran.jpg" alt="Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws" /></div>
</figure>
<div class="bloc-critique">
<div class="titre-critique">The notes</div>
<div class="bloc-pos-neg">
<div class="row">
<div class="col-md-6">
<div class="barre-plus">+Positive aspects</div>
<ul class="liste-argument">
<li>Aesthetics always as superb</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="col-md-6">
<div class="barre-moins">-Negative points</div>
<ul class="liste-argument">
<li>Much too short</li>
<li>Much too simple</li>
<li>No more hide-and-seek</li>
<li>The non-existent narrative aspect</li>
<li>Does not add anything to the basic game</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="bloc-critique">
<div class="resume-critique">
<p>One would have loved to boast only of the aesthetic qualities of Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws which also succeeds in flattering the retina with new immersed environments and an atmosphere as disturbing as that of its model. Yet, beyond the atmosphere, this first content has against him the same gameplay faults as his elder, leaves some of his mechanics and wants to be too simple and short to really arouse interest.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/little-nightmares-secret-maws/">Little Nightmares: Secret of the Maws</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Death Road to Canada Review</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/death-road-to-canada-review/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=148</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/death-road-to-canada-review/">Death Road to Canada Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="intro-article">If the name Rocketcat Games tells you something, you&#8217;ve definitely heard about Death Road to Canada , their zombie roadtrip simulator where you can say &#8220;Cool It&#8221; to the first person who passes by. If you do not know, let me make you discover one of the most crazy survival that has come out on the market. Tie your belts, we go to Canada!</p>
<figure class="serie-images">
<div class="images"><span class="capsule-img big-image"><img title="Death Road to Canada - The Barbar Zombie Roadtrip" src="https://image.noelshack.com/fichiers-md/2017/30/4/1501165368-7939-noelshack-logo.jpg" alt="Death Road to Canada - The Barbar Zombie Roadtrip" /></span></div>
</figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Death Road to Canada is above all a game of zombies: we start with one or two characters generated in a completely random way by the game. <strong>It is already the occasion to evoke one of the strong points of the game: The generation of characters, which is frankly to applaud. </strong>The characters generated are of a hallucinatory consistency, although sometimes it is a little difficult to differentiate a boy from a girl. But hey, the random generation always has limits, whatever its power.</p>
<figure class="encart-article pull-left"><img src="https://image.noelshack.com/fichiers-sm/2017/30/4/1501165684-5887-noelshack-logo.jpg" alt="Death Road to Canada - The Barbar Zombie Roadtrip" /><figcaption>Outside the search or rescue missions, the characters interact freely with one another. Tips for the player and disputes to the appointment.</figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Once the game starts, a small pitch is given: the leader of your fortune group learns that Canada would be a safe place, away from zombies and bandits. He decides to go there, and will have to borrow the Death Road. </strong>The bare minimum, of course, but the most important is not the story in Death Road to Canada. Throughout the game, various events will happen. Some will involve zone exploration, either automatic or in the form of a playable mission, where each area must be searched meticulously for food, fuel, ammunition and weapons. These same weapons will be more or less resistant, more or less powerful and more or less manageable. A simple femur will break after a few strokes, but can still be used as a rescue weapon,</p>
<h2 id="des-situations-cocasses-par-dizaines" class="h2-default-jv">TOUGH SITUATIONS</h2>
<figure class="encart-article pull-right"><img src="https://image.noelshack.com/fichiers-sm/2017/30/4/1501166395-6404-noelshack-logo.jpg" alt="Death Road to Canada - The Barbar Zombie Roadtrip" /><figcaption>A demon that appears without screaming and asks for pizza? Welcome to Death Road to Canada.</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Obviously, you will also face events involving making a choice. </strong>For example, some will choose who will watch at night to watch for bandits and zombies, who will explore the city in search of resources, how to deal with bandits &#8230; and this is only the classic side of Death Road to Canada, Which will also feature delusional events, which will test your reaction to something totally impropable. Are you going to enter the delirium or will you remain lucid by acting in a classic way? Yeah, well, okay, it&#8217;s not very clear says that, but in the game, it&#8217;s going to come quickly, no worries.</p>
<h2></h2>
<h2 id="la-loi-du-mieux-entraine" class="h2-default-jv">THE LAW OF THE BEST TRAINED</h2>
<figure class="encart-article pull-left"><img src="https://image.noelshack.com/fichiers-sm/2017/30/4/1501166897-7213-noelshack-logo.jpg" alt="Death Road to Canada - The Barbar Zombie Roadtrip" /><figcaption>Not very welcoming, the staff, so!</figcaption></figure>
<p>During your first games, you often see your little team being eaten, losing its hard-won equipment, being killed by bandits, and even knocking on the back without really understanding why you lost. And over time, <strong>you&#8217;ll understand that every statistic your survivors have has an impact on your entire game. </strong>A loyal survivor will endanger his life to protect his neighbor. A good mechanic will know how to maintain the vehicle of the group easily and go much further than the one with no mechanical knowledge. A calm survivor and good shooter will knock down a threatening bear without flinching, where a lambda survivor will panic and be devoured.</p>
<h2></h2>
<h2></h2>
<h2></h2>
<h2 id="un-survivant-a-son-image" class="h2-default-jv">A SURVIVOR TO HIS IMAGE</h2>
<figure class="encart-article pull-right"><img src="https://image.noelshack.com/fichiers-sm/2017/30/4/1501167764-1356-noelshack-logo.jpg" alt="Death Road to Canada - The Barbar Zombie Roadtrip" /><figcaption>This is what happens when you try to provoke someone who is stronger verbally than yourself.</figcaption></figure>
<p>We were talking about character generation just now, right? Well, know that you can also integrate into the game! Friends, family, acquaintances &#8230; Is not it great to see &#8220;survivor&#8221; versions of your entourage being crunched, getting knocked down or fighting violently because the CD player of your car broadcasts a single song ? Besides, speaking of customizable characters, let me tell you that there are also many rare characters capable of turning a whole part upside down. You may well come across Jason Voorhees, Link, fencers, girls from animes and much more, each with his behavior, his powers (useful or dangerous) &#8230; Rocketcat has done a very good job on this side -the.</p>
<p>Needless to perpetuate this article, let us hasten to conclude: <strong>Death Road to Canada is certainly one of the most wacky and addictive that Steam has known survival. </strong>With its effective gameplay, its crazy little delusions, its brilliant references and its soundtrack that delights the ears, this excellent game will tape you for long hours. At least, if you manage to appreciate its particularly retro style which will reject some and its difficulty during your first attempts.</p>
<div></div>
<h3 class="titre-critique">The notes</h3>
<div class="bloc-pos-neg">
<div class="row">
<div class="col-md-6">
<div class="barre-plus">+Positive aspects</div>
<ul class="liste-argument">
<li>Relatively effective gameplay</li>
<li>References to each corner</li>
<li>This soundtrack that gets into our ears!</li>
<li>One can teach a dog to drive!</li>
<li>High quality roadtrip</li>
<li>Saying &#8220;Cool It&#8221; to bandits, so rejoicing</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="col-md-6">
<div class="barre-moins">-Negative points</div>
<ul class="liste-argument">
<li>Clearly not for anti-retro</li>
<li>A difficulty that will discourage some</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/death-road-to-canada-review/">Death Road to Canada Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clash of Clans Review</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/clash-clans-review/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 07:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=144</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/clash-clans-review/">Clash of Clans Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="intro-article">Free-to-play has been in the air for some years now and is gradually spreading to all types of games. Games are so numerous on the Web and smartphones that to distinguish themselves, some adopt models offering to play for free in exchange for some optional purchases. Clash of Clans is no exception and since its launch in August 2012 it has been downloaded by hundreds of thousands of players and today has an impressive community. Full of qualities but also defects, is the game worth it as you try it in your turn?</p>
<figure class="serie-images">
<div class="images"><a class="xXx capsule-img big-image" href="http://www.jeuxvideo.com/screenshots/332785-1891101-0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img title="Clash of clans" src="http://image.jeuxvideo.com/images-md/ip/c/l/clash-of-clans-iphone-ipod-00a.jpg" alt="Clash of clans" /></a></div>
</figure>
<h2 id="le-jeu-de-strategie-revisite" class="h2-default-jv">THE STRATEGY GAME REVISITED</h2>
<p>The mechanisms of Clash of Clans, you already know them if you are used to war strategy games such as the Age of Empire series. We start with the strict minimum of buildings and gradually we build others then we improve them before extending its city. Of course, in order for all this to be possible, resources are required and they are in the game of two: gold and elixir, accompanied by their own reservoirs. Then come the defenses, which are much more varied. There are of course the traditional ramparts but also cannons, towers of archers and mortars to attack from a distance, as well as traps like hidden bombs or even more zany, springs. <strong>By gradually improving all these facilities, </strong>Your city will become a real fortress and organize its buildings will quickly appear to you as a must. In addition to being practical (a simple drag and drop allows to change the place of a building), this system is paramount because you can not defend your base in real time with armies like in most games of the genre. So prepare for the best, because in your absence an enemy might well point out and plunder your resources.</p>
<h2 id="a-l-attaque" class="h2-default-jv">Attack!</h2>
<figure class="encart-article pull-left"><a class="xXx " href="http://www.jeuxvideo.com/screenshots/48244-1686169-0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img src="http://image.jeuxvideo.com/images-sm/ip/c/l/clash-of-clans-iphone-ipod-1365605428-004.jpg" alt="Clash of clans" /></a><figcaption>Construisez et défendez votre base.</figcaption></figure>
<p>Obviously, on the other hand, you also have the ability to launch assaults. The creation of units is also simplified: one building to create one, another to improve, both can evolve to provide different and more powerful units. Once you have concocted your army, go into a battle against the goblins (single player mode) or directly in multi by selecting a player at random. The assault is quite complicated to conduct, it is actually just putting its units near the enemy and letting them get by. Certainly, depending on the type of warriors chosen, the targeted buildings will be different, but one can pester against this combat system which besides being particularly annoying, You forbid any control what necessarily implies that it will not happen exactly as you expected. <strong>In fact, once the units are laid, there is nothing left to do but to contemplate the battle in hopes of winning it. </strong>Positive point about attacks though, the ability to store units of allies of his clan that manifest themselves in the event of assault of your base.</p>
<h2 id="lenteur-quand-tu-nous-tiens" class="h2-default-jv">SLOWNESS WHEN YOU HOLD US &#8230;</h2>
<figure class="encart-article pull-right"><a class="xXx " href="http://www.jeuxvideo.com/screenshots/48244-1686171-0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img src="http://image.jeuxvideo.com/images-sm/ip/c/l/clash-of-clans-iphone-ipod-1365605428-005.jpg" alt="Clash of clans" /></a><figcaption>Detailed information is available for each building.</figcaption></figure>
<p>The existence of special heroes to unlock at very high level also energizes the battles. However, before you see the color of these heroes, you have time in front of you. Of course, Clash of Clan is not a completely free game and its developers have to feed themselves from time to time, so the presence of an in-game currency, called &#8220;gem&#8221; is not surprising. <strong>As in most free-to-play games of this kind, these gems are mainly used to save time, by finishing construction or unit formation. </strong>On the other hand, what is much more surprising are the completely abusive times required for basic actions. At first everything goes well, but it quickly degenerates. Take the gold mine for example, Building of which you will quickly have 6 copies. A mine takes only one minute to build, 5 minutes to evolve to level 2, then twelve hours from level 5 to 6 and five days from level 10 to level 11, which is absolutely huge! Of course, we say that it is to encourage in-game purchases but these are totally useless since once an improvement purchased, we always find ourselves having to wait without discovering new possibilities of gameplay. <strong>Purchases are also offered at exorbitant prices. </strong>To avoid waiting five days to improve the gold mine, it would be necessary to spend 750 gems or already more than 5 €. Multiply this figure by the number of buildings and evolutions, Add the necessary resources as well as the workforce (2 simultaneous constructions maximum, up to 5 while spending 25 € in the shop) and you will have a good idea of ​​the problem of this game: everything is extremely long and / or expensive . So you always have the possibility of fighting to wait, but because of having nothing else to do but to spend 5 minutes every other day, you will soon forget Clash of Clans and it&#8217;s a shame.</p>
<div class="bloc-critique">
<div class="titre-critique">The notes</div>
<div class="bloc-pos-neg">
<div class="row">
<div class="col-md-6">
<div class="barre-plus">+Positive aspects</div>
<ul class="liste-argument">
<li>Beautifully done</li>
<li>The possibilities of defense of its base</li>
<li>A simple but not simplistic strategy game</li>
</ul>
</div>
<div class="col-md-6">
<div class="barre-moins">-Negative points</div>
<ul class="liste-argument">
<li>Frustrating assaults</li>
<li>Abusive in-app purchases</li>
<li>A few minutes of play per day maximum, even when paying</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="bloc-critique">
<div class="resume-critique">
<p>Friendly to see and play, Clash of Clans is likely to attract you if you are used to social free-to-play on iOS or Facebook. Complete, but sufficiently accessible for the neophytes of the genre, the game proposes mechanics of strategy reviewed and simplified with a small tactical side very appreciable as regards the organization of the defenses of his village. However, the shortcomings of the attack phases and especially its incomprehensible economic system that makes the game extremely long, will certainly make you quickly let go of this Clash of Clans yet very promising.</p>
</div>
</div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/clash-clans-review/">Clash of Clans Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gardenscapes Hack &#8211; Gardenscapes New Acres Hack</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/gardenscapes-hack/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=105</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/gardenscapes-hack/">Gardenscapes Hack &#8211; Gardenscapes New Acres Hack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The first working Gardenscapes Hack. Hack Gardenscapes New Acres for free and receive unlimited coins or stars. Enjoy Gardenscapes to it&#8217;s fullest. You can access the hack <a href="http://viralmuffin.com/hacks">here </a>or click &#8220;Go to Generator&#8221; below.</p>
<h1 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://viralmuffin.com/hacks">Go to Generator</a></h1>
<h3>Gardenscapes Hack:</h3>
<p>The Gardenscapes hack was made by an experienced team of app developers with one simple goal in mind, we want people to enjoy apps to the fullest. We make all of our tools completely free to ensure everyone can use them. You can use the Gardenscapes hack by pressing &#8220;Go to Generator&#8221; above.</p>
<h3>Gardenscapes New Acres:</h3>
<p>Welcome to Gardenscapes! Enter a story full of unexpected twists and give your splendor to a wonderful garden!</p>
<p>Embark on an authentic adventure: Beat levels, restore and decorate different areas of the garden, discover the secrets you hide and have fun with the friendly characters in the game, including Austin, your butler! What are you waiting for? Build the garden of your dreams!</p>
<p>Game Features:<br />
● A unique play style: swap and match, restores and decorates the garden, and follows an amazing storyline. Everything at once!<br />
● Hundreds of unique combination levels.<br />
● Dozens of characters in the game that can be your friends.<br />
● A lovely pet always ready to cheer you up.<br />
● A social gaming network that you can use to get the latest news.<br />
● Different areas in the garden with unique structures: broken fountains, mysterious labyrinths and much more.<br />
● Community comes first: your Facebook friends can be your neighbors!</p>
<p>Gardenscapes is played for free, but some game items can be bought for real money.</p>
<p>Having fun with Gardenscapes? Find out more about the game!<br />
Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Gardenscapes">https://www.facebook.com/Gardenscapes </a><br />
Instagram: <a href="https://www.instagram.com/gardenscapes_mobile/">https://www.instagram.com/gardenscapes_mobile/ </a><br />
Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/garden_scapes">https://twitter.com/garden_scapes</a></p>
<p>Gardenscapes: New Acres is overall a great game that will keep you hooked. Try it out for free at the <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/gardenscapes-new-acres/id1105855019">App Store</a> or <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.playrix.gardenscapes">Google Play store</a>.</p>
<p><img class="gardenscapes hack aligncenter" title="gardenscapes hack" src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hMyYwLOEm4hqw_16GmBhxict2_UYwLelRG2hzrJtxobEJv8gtk1buVBPSDXcvM6AU3U=h900" alt="gardenscapes hack" width="1440" height="900" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Gardenscapes Hack Last Thoughts:</h3>
<p>Well what are you waiting for? Go and use the Gardenscapes hack now!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/gardenscapes-hack/">Gardenscapes Hack &#8211; Gardenscapes New Acres Hack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Graj King of Thieves</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/graj-king-of-thieves/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=98</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/graj-king-of-thieves/">Graj King of Thieves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://movfe.com/srv.html?id=1418014&amp;pub=779619">Zagraj teraz!</a></h1>
<p>Ubierz klejnoty, buduj swoją obronę i wygrywaj wojnę gildii w tej unikalnej kombinacji gry zręcznościowej, platformy i multiplayer PVP!<br />
Konkurować z ponad 50 milionami użytkowników na całym świecie i tworzyć własne klany złodziei. Przenieś się do lochu wroga i ukradnij złoto.<br />
Udowodnij, że jesteś najmądrzejszym i najzdolniejszym złodziejem na świecie!</p>
<p>UWAGA: gra jest bardzo wciągająca i nieuchronnie prowadzi do zwiększenia liczby Twoich znajomych.</p>
<p>KLUCZOWE CECHY:</p>
<p>STANDARDOWE WYDARZENIA. Kradzieży to zabawa! Zbieraj złoto i kamienie innych graczy, aby stać się najbogatszym złodziejem na świecie.<br />
OCHRONA DWA. Zaprojektuj broń obronną, pułapki i platformy, aby uniemożliwić innym kradzież skarbu. Zobacz, jak zostali złapani w pułapki. Nie ma ucieczki, muhaha!<br />
ZAREJESTRUJ SIĘ THRONE. Zanurkuj się w akcji, zwiększ swoje umiejętności i konkurować z innymi graczami na całym świecie, aby przejść na szczyty liderów.<br />
JOIN GUILD. Znajdź wiarygodne dudy i ogłaszaj wojnę innym gildiom. Wygraj epickie walki klanów!<br />
DOSTOSUJ TWÓJ WYDAJNOŚĆ. Wybierz fajny kostium, który idealnie pasuje do twojej osobowości. Bądź eleganckim złodziejem, wyróżnij się z tłumu!<br />
PODRÓŻ I PRZEGLĄD. Sprawdź swoją zwinność dzięki 112 poziomom pojedynczego trybu lub zanurz się w podziemnym świecie treści generowanych przez użytkowników.<br />
_________________________________________________________<br />
SUBSKRYPCJA. Subskrybuj, aby mieć szansę szybszego i szybkiego dostępu do ekskluzywnych kostiumów!</p>
<p>Poprzez subskrypcję Króla Złodziei otrzymuje się:<br />
&#8211; blokady x10 (zwiększenie maksymalnej pojemności)<br />
&#8211; Odblokowanie blokady bloków jest szybsze od x10<br />
&#8211; Kopalnia złota wytwarza codziennie &#8220;łzy&#8221;<br />
&#8211; 3 unikalne stroje<br />
_________________________________________________________</p>
<p>Gotowi sprostać wyzwaniu? Gra na!<br />
Dołącz do społeczności, znajdź przyjaciół i sprawdź wiadomości:<br />
<a href="http://www.facebook.com/kingofthievesgame">www.facebook.com/kingofthievesgame</a><br />
<a href="http://www.twitter.com/kingthieves">www.twitter.com/kingthieves</a><br />
&#8220;Król złodziei to dobrze zaprojektowane wyzwanie dla wielu graczy, które pozwoli Ci wrócić i zdecydowanie ukradnia ofertę bezpłatnej rozrywki&#8221; &#8211; Apple&#8217;N&#8217;Apps</p>
<p>&#8220;Król złodziei to najcudowniejsza gra PvP, która może się pojawić od dłuższego czasu. Dobrze być zły, więc idź dalej i rozkoszuj się &#8220;- Gamezebo</p>
<p>&#8220;King of Thieves jest jednym z największych aplikacjach tam” &#8211; App Mag</p>
<p>&#8220;King of Thieves to z pewnością warto go wypróbować gry teraz” &#8211; ZoGames</p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/BPVU1uxVIK_gZy_JS5Lbsa_TQ0TKeR-18hhrZW5kfL-aBTGgHTZvLyM8zjMWbkispQ=h900-rw" alt=" King of Thieves – zrzut ekranu " /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/graj-king-of-thieves/">Graj King of Thieves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invasion: Modern Empire</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/invasion-modern-empire/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=93</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/invasion-modern-empire/">Invasion: Modern Empire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Invasion: Modern Empire is an exciting online warfare simulation and STR game type that challenges you to confront different enemy factions, conquer their territory and make their way to world domination in the midst of a global apocalypse . Fight to become the most powerful military commander in the world and walk towards victory!</p>
<p><b>Invasion Features: Modern Empire </b></p>
<p><b>Your enemies are going to nail their nails with this STR type fighting style to ward off the apocalypse! </b></p>
<p>• Military strategy, real &#8211; time fighting and building your base<br />
• Destroy the world and rebuild it in its image by conquering enemy armies<br />
• Strategic battles in 3D and real &#8211;</p>
<p><b>Action Fight for every inch of terrain and expand your Alliance territory! </b></p>
<p>• Conquer enemy territory online in a world at war<br />
• Claim territory by performing RAIDS on your enemies<br />
• Conquer is yours, as long as you have soldiers and you organize raids on your enemies. But be careful &#8211; your enemies can also attack your base!</p>
<p><b>War tactics and advanced technology will help you move forward and get information about your enemies</b></p>
<p>• Modern warfare is how to spy on your enemies. Dominate your opponents by collecting information about their bases<br />
• Command your troops and conquer territories using a panoramic map in real time! Fight against other alliances in the War of Monuments PVP!</p>
<p><b>Battle online against alliances and crush every alliance on your way</b></p>
<p>• Online multiplayer mode allows you to form an alliance and compete against other players to become the ultimate commander<br />
• Online chat and other features will help you To find the perfect alliance<br />
• Online multiplayer games feature PvP MMO combat on a modern battlefield<br />
Fight with other alliances to occupy &#8220;war monuments&#8221;<br />
• Raid monuments to experiment Changes and surprise real-time fights!<br />
• Create diplomatic ties with other players as you see fit!<br />
• PvP gameplay sends you to war alongside a ton of other players! Fight in the post-apocalyptic world of 2020!</p>
<p>Do you have what it takes to survive in this world at war?</p>
<p><b>Download Invasion: Modern Empire and beat now! </b></p>
<p>In Invasion, some game elements can also be bought for real money. If you do not want to use this feature, please set up a<br />
password protection for purchases in your Google Play Store app settings.<br />
Join the community:</p>
<p>• Facebook &#8211; <a href="https://www.facebook.com/InvasionGame">https://www.facebook.com/InvasionGame </a></p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/X29JZnCIo5foyDkJu_vCfwW7_t_OOXeGgQDsGkIvpwNx9bTyEw38rMnb2irFBUgQJk6B=h900-rw" alt=" Invasion: Modern Empire- screenshot " /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/invasion-modern-empire/">Invasion: Modern Empire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disney Magic Kingdoms</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/disney-magic-kingdoms/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=90</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/disney-magic-kingdoms/">Disney Magic Kingdoms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WELCOME TO THE MOST MAGIC PLACE ON MOBILE!</p>
<p>When Maledic will cast a curse on the Kingdom, emptying it of all its magical power, will you help us to save it? Relive the fun of Disney parks and create the most fantastic park of your dreams in Disney Magic Kingdoms!</p>
<p>ATTRACTIONS OF EXTRAORDINARY AND TIMELY DISNEY PARKS<br />
• Attractions such as &#8220;it&#8217;s a small world&#8221;, the Monsters &amp; Co. and Space Mountain laughing factory from Disney parks around the world!<br />
• Exclusive attractions such as the WALL-E House and Cyclope Sushi, all inspired by their respective films!<br />
• Relive the magic moments of the parks with the joyful parades of tanks and fireworks!</p>
<p>A RANGE OF CHARACTERS COVERING MORE THAN 90 YEARS OF DISNEY<br />
• Share spectacular moments with characters like the eternal optimist Mickey Mouse, Rapunzel the fiery princess, the courageous space ranger Buzz Lightning, the adorable and vivid Tinkerbell and many others !<br />
• Play hundreds of quests that support every pixel in your Kingdom!<br />
• Collect Disney items to save each character from the Maledic Curse!</p>
<p>A HOROSCOPE OF HEROES AND MISTAKES<br />
• Discover a magical story and an exciting adventure!<br />
• Face evil villains such as Pat Hibulaire, Mother Gothel and Zurg to save the Kingdom!</p>
<p>Come and play the most magical free mobile game, a great family adventure! It&#8217;s up to you to create your world!</p>
<p>Perfect for fans of Disney, Disneyland, Pixar movie games, management games, free family games, and park building games.</p>
<p>You can download this game for free. Please note that this game also allows you to use virtual currency which can be obtained by progressing in the game, deciding to watch some ads or spending real money. Built-in purchases range from € 0.99 to € 99.99. You can disable embedded purchases by changing your User Controls in your Play Store settings.</p>
<p>Languages: English, French, German, Italian, Indonesian, Japanese, Korean, Brazilian Portuguese, Russian, Simplified Chinese, Traditional Chinese, Spanish, Turkish, Arabic and Thai.</p>
<p>An additional download of 175 to 200 MB is required to play this game. Please note that the size of this download may change without notice.</p>
<p>The game requires an Internet connection (3G or Wi-Fi) for downloads and updates, and other features such as parties with friends, integrated purchases and viewing ads.</p>
<p>Some features of this game, such as collaborating with other players, confronting them or sharing items with them in the game, require that the player be connected to a social network like Facebook or Google+. Please note that this connection is not required to progress in the game. These features may not be available in some countries.</p>
<p>This game may contain third-party advertising that will redirect you to a third party site. You can disable the ad ID used for targeted ads in your device&#8217;s Settings menu. This option can be found in Settings&gt; Personal Accounts&gt; Google&gt; Advertisements (Settings &amp; Privacy)&gt; Disable interest-based ads.</p>
<p>For more info on the game, go to the official website &#8211; <a href="http://www.disney-magic-kingdoms.com/">http://www.disney-magic-kingdoms.com/ </a></p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/0VqHX9h9__AVhsNxldbFrOtKbhzx8mB7fRaMbtZHyC-fkepYsRr9xuyS_OMeiLdauBiQ=h900" alt="Image result for Disney Magic Kingdoms" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/disney-magic-kingdoms/">Disney Magic Kingdoms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/worlds-best-word-puzzle-game-word-cookies/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=87</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/worlds-best-word-puzzle-game-word-cookies/">The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</p>
<p>This is a new word puzzle game created by <b>BitMango, the creator of the HIT application, Roll the Ball ™ &#8211; slide puzzle and Block hexa puzzle!</b></p>
<p>Word cookies is a very fun and exciting word puzzle game, it allows you to continue playing for FREE!</p>
<p>The goal of the game is to find all the hidden words.<br />
With this game, you can easily improve vocabulary skills, concentration and spelling.</p>
<p>The king of HEADLING<br />
Do you like the word puzzle games? Do you like cookies? Do you like the challenge?<br />
Here is the perfect game for you, Word cookies!</p>
<p>Are you ready to find delicious cookie words at your kitchen oven?<br />
Embrace your intelligence to discover words.</p>
<p>HOW TO PLAY<br />
• Words can be vertical, horizontal, diagonal and even backward.<br />
• Simply slide your finger over a word to select it.<br />
• If you have found a valid word, it will remain highlighted and marked on the list of found words.</p>
<p>Characters<br />
• Discover hidden words in mixed letters<br />
• Find words derived from the main words and develop your brain skills and vocabulary.<br />
• Visually pleasing to play cookies in various types!<br />
• Feeling complete with increased points by making more cookies!<br />
• Simple and easy!<br />
• Daily rewards<br />
• 200 free coins in the first round<br />
• Excellent exercise for the brain<br />
• Available for both laptops and tablets.<br />
• FREE update!</p>
<p>• EASY AND FUN GAME<br />
&#8211; Easy to learn and fun to master the game</p>
<p>• No time limit<br />
&#8211; Enjoy the game anytime, anywhere and even for a little while.</p>
<p>• No WIFI? No problem!<br />
&#8211; You can play offline at any time</p>
<p>• TONS OF UNIQUE LEVELS<br />
&#8211; 32 packages and over 580 impressive levels! Updates will be continued!</p>
<p>NOTES<br />
• Enjoy the game with various devices (laptops and tablets).<br />
• &#8220;Word cookies&#8221; contain banner ads, interstitial ads, videos.<br />
• &#8220;Word cookies&#8221; is free to play, but you can buy items like Non-Pubs and other packages on the shop in this game.</p>
<p>E-MAIL<br />
• contact@bitmango.com</p>
<p>SITE<br />
• <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?Id=6249013288401661340">https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?Id=6249013288401661340</a></p>
<p>Put it Like on FACEBOOK<br />
• <a href="https://www.facebook.com/BitMangoGames">https://www.facebook.com/BitMangoGames</a></p>
<p>Thank you for playing!</p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hCRo0pQmXiUJ_VJcnmHe87ti8jP268EEBF0pca4td7cfq97_TCVBz5xknvW6XRtWKw=h900" alt="Image result for Word Cookies" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/worlds-best-word-puzzle-game-word-cookies/">The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire Hacks Cheats Glitches</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/final-fantasy-xv-a-new-empire-hacks-cheats-glitches/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 01:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=80</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/final-fantasy-xv-a-new-empire-hacks-cheats-glitches/">Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire Hacks Cheats Glitches</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://viralmuffin.com/hacks">Access Hack</a></h1>
<p>Hack Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire with our free tool above. Generate free resources, gold or whatever you need. Press the button above to access Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire Hacks.</p>
<h2>About Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire</h2>
<p><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/final-fantasy-xv-a-new-empire/id1186994231?mt=8">Apple Store</a>, <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.epicactiononline.ffxv.ane">Play Store</a></p>
<p>Experience a great adventure in the world of Final Fantasy with the newest free mobile strategy game Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire! Build your kingdom, discover powerful magical powers and form alliances with your friends to impose you!</p>
<p>Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire is a mobile adventure game that allows you to rediscover Final Fantasy XV from a new angle in order to fulfill your outstanding destiny. Go freely through vast kingdoms, collect gems and magical resources to build the most powerful empire in Final Fantasy history! Form alliances with your friends and battle your enemies with millions of players from around the world! Will your team&#8217;s strategy be up to take possession of the crystal and dominate the kingdom?</p>
<p>✔ Let your imagination speak! Experience your own adventure in the world of FFXV on your mobile phone with this free application!</p>
<p>✔ Dive into action and team up with Noctis, Cindy and all your favorite FF15 characters!</p>
<p>✔ Defend your friends and eliminate your opponents in legendary battles with millions of players from around the world!</p>
<p>✔ Raise a great army, create alliances and develop the best strategy to win epic battles in real time!</p>
<p>✔ Free to create the ultimate guild or combine with powerful forces!</p>
<p>✔ Choose the right strategy with your guild to crush monsters and enemies in real-time battles!</p>
<p>✔ Compete with players from around the world to capture the crystal!</p>
<p>✔ Explore the different kingdoms, accumulate rare resources and grab the crystal to build an empire of epic proportions!</p>
<p>✔ Enter legend by taking control of the crystal to dominate the kingdom!</p>
<p>Let your imagination run wild in an epic world where the only rules are magic. Will your empire stand the test of time or will it collapse?</p>
<p>Your legend begins now in the new MMORPG game Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire. A free application, where the only limit is your imagination!</p>
<p><img class="alignnone" src="https://assets.vg247.com/current//2017/06/ff15_new_empire3.jpg" alt="Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire" width="887" height="600" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/final-fantasy-xv-a-new-empire-hacks-cheats-glitches/">Final Fantasy XV: A New Empire Hacks Cheats Glitches</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pacman &#8211; Spielen Sie kostenlose Online Pacman Spiel und Frau Pacman (Pac Man)</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/spielen-sie-kostenlose-online-pacman/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 19:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=68</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/spielen-sie-kostenlose-online-pacman/">Pacman &#8211; Spielen Sie kostenlose Online Pacman Spiel und Frau Pacman (Pac Man)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://viralmuffin.com/play-pacman"> <img class="aligncenter" src="http://www.pngmart.com/files/3/Play-Now-Button-PNG-Free-Download.png" alt="Pacman" width="634" height="170" /> </a></p>
<h3></h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Pacman Gameplay</h3>
<p>Das Ziel des Spiels ist es, die Geister zu vermeiden und so viele gelbe Punkte wie möglich zu essen, um auf die nächste Stufe zu kommen! Dieses pacman Spiel bietet auch Highscores! Sehen Sie, wie Ihre pacman Fähigkeiten vergleichen und wenn Sie mit den Besten der Besten konkurrieren können!</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Pacman Hintergrund</h3>
<p>Pacman, war die Ikone der 1980er-Pop-Kultur und ein Grundnahrungsmittel in jedem Arcade-Spielzimmer. Seit seiner Geburt wuchs Pacman zu einer der beliebtesten Spielfiguren aller Zeiten. Die Ikone der achtziger Jahre Popkultur, wurde zu einer der beliebtesten Spielfiguren aller Zeiten. Die Basis des Spiels ist so einfach und doch genial. Kleiner gelber Pacman schlägt sich um den Vorstand, der Pellets sammelt, während er gleichzeitig weg von den Geistern bleibt.</p>
<p>Das Pacman-Spiel wurde von Namco erstellt und lizenziert für den Vertrieb in den USA von Midway im Oktober 1980. Pacman ist sicher einer der Klassiker und definitiv einer der Ikonen der Popkultur ala die gerne von anderen beliebten Spielen wie Mario, Tetris und Frogger Zu diesem heutigen Tag ist Pacman immer noch stark mit Bekleidungswaren, Videospielen und Arcade-Maschinen immer noch auf der ganzen Welt!</p>
<p>Ersetzen Sie die klassischen Arcade-Spiele, können Sie jetzt genießen pacman online. Sie können pacman aus dem Komfort Ihres eigenen Hauses dank der Internet und mobilen Geräten spielen. Achten Sie darauf, immer pacman online hier zu spielen! Jubel und Spaß haben, sich an diesen Pellets und Geistern zu verjagen!</p>
<p>Pac-Man (Japanisch: パ ッ ク マ ン Hepburn: Pakkuman), stilisiert als PAC-MAN, ist ein Arcade-Spiel, das von Namco entwickelt und erstmals im Mai 1980 in Japan veröffentlicht wurde. Es wurde vom japanischen Videospiel-Designer Toru Iwatani erstellt. Es ist lizenziert für den Vertrieb in den Vereinigten Staaten von Midway Games und veröffentlicht im Oktober 1980. Pac-Man ist einer der Klassiker des Mediums und eine Ikone der 1980er Jahre populäre Kultur. Pac-Man, die Spiel-und-Fortsetzung, Pac-Man und Pac-Man, Ten Buckner und Garcia Hit Single &#8220;Pac-Man Fever&#8221;. Pac-Man war in den 1980er und 1990er Jahren beliebt und wird noch in den 2010er Jahren gespielt.</p>
<p>Als Pac-Man veröffentlicht wurde, waren die beliebtesten Arcade-Videospiele Space Shooters, insbesondere Space Invaders und Asteroiden. Die sichtbarste Minderheit waren Sportspiele. Pac-Man gelang es, ein neues Genre zu schaffen. Pac-Man ist oft mit einem Wahrzeichen im Videospiel gutgeschrieben. Es ist auch eines der höchstwertigen Videospiele aller Zeiten, haben in den 90er Jahren mehr als 2,5 Milliarden Dollar in Quartalen produziert.\</p>
<p>Der Charakter ist in mehr als 30 offiziell lizenzierten Spiel-Spin-offs, sowie in zahlreichen unautorisierten Klonen und Bootlegs erschienen. Nach dem Davie-Brown Index hat Pac-Man das höchste Markenbewusstsein für jeden Videospiel Charakter unter den amerikanischen Verbrauchern, von 94 Prozent von ihnen erkannt. Pac-Man ist eines der am längsten laufenden Videospiel-Franchise aus dem goldenen Zeitalter der Video-Arcade-Spiele. Es ist Teil der Sammlung der Smithsonian Institution in Washington, DC und New York Museum of Modern Art.</p>
<p>Der Spieler kontrolliert Pac-Man durch ein Labyrinth aus verschiedenen Punkten, bekannt als Pac-Dots, sowie vier mehrfarbige Geister: Blinky, Pinky, Inky und Clyde. Das Ziel des Spiels ist es, alle Pac-Dots in einer Bühne zu verbrauchen, um zum nächsten zu gehen. Zwischen einigen Stufen spielt eine von drei Pausen-Animationen. [23] Die vier Geister durchstreifen das Labyrinth und versuchen, Pac-Man zu fangen. Wenn irgendwelche der Geister Pac-Man berühren, verliert er ein Leben; Wenn alle Leben verloren gegangen sind, endet das Spiel. Pac-Man erhält ein einziges Bonusleben bei 10.000 Punkten standardmäßig &#8211; DIP-Schalter innerhalb der Maschine können die benötigten Punkte auf 15.000 oder 20.000 ändern oder das Bonusleben insgesamt deaktivieren. Die Anzahl der Leben kann auf 1 Leben oder bis zu fünf Leben maximal eingestellt werden. Highscore darf 999.990 Punkte nicht überschreiten; Spieler können diese Punktzahl überschreiten, aber das Spiel hält die letzten 6 Ziffern.</p>
<p>In der Nähe der Ecken des Labyrinths sind vier größere, blinkende Punkte, die als Power Pellets bekannt sind, die Pac-Man mit der vorübergehenden Fähigkeit versorgen, die Geister zu verbrauchen und Bonuspunkte zu verdienen. Die Feinde werden tiefblau, umgekehrt und bewegen sich in der Regel langsamer. Wenn ein Feind gegessen wird, bleiben seine Augen und kehren in die Mittelkiste zurück, wo er in seiner normalen Farbe regeneriert wird. Blaue Feinde blitzen weiß, um zu signalisieren, dass sie im Begriff sind, wieder gefährlich zu werden, und die Zeitdauer, für die die Feinde anfällig bleiben, variiert von einer Stufe zur nächsten, die im Allgemeinen immer kürzer wird, wenn das Spiel fortschreitet. In späteren Stadien gehen die Feinde direkt zu blinken, umgehen blau, was bedeutet, dass sie nur für eine kurze Zeit gegessen werden können, obwohl sie immer noch die Richtung umkehren, wenn ein Power Pellet gegessen wird; Beginnend in Stufe 19 werden die Geister nicht essbar (d.h. sie ändern nicht die Farbe und machen immer noch Pac-Man ein Leben auf Kontakt), aber sie immer noch Richtung umkehren. Es gibt auch Früchte, die sich direkt unterhalb der Mittelschachtel befinden, die zweimal pro Level erscheinen; Es wird zu Bonuspunkten (100-5.000) kommen.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://de.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pac-Man">Mehr Info.</a></p>
<p><a href="http://viralmuffin.com/play-pacman"><img class="aligncenter" src="http://www.pngmart.com/files/3/Play-Now-Button-PNG-Free-Download.png" alt="Pacman" width="634" height="170" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/spielen-sie-kostenlose-online-pacman/">Pacman &#8211; Spielen Sie kostenlose Online Pacman Spiel und Frau Pacman (Pac Man)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
