<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Misc &#8211; ViralMuffin</title>
	<atom:link href="http://viralmuffin.com/category/misc/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://viralmuffin.com/</link>
	<description>Discover the World</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 08:31:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.8.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>http://viralmuffin.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/08/cropped-kawaii_muffin_by_elekmario-d5ul3eh-1-150x150.jpg</url>
	<title>Misc &#8211; ViralMuffin</title>
	<link>http://viralmuffin.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Voices of the Beyond</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/the-voices-of-the-beyond/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 08:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Misc]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=141</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/the-voices-of-the-beyond/">The Voices of the Beyond</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a strange way, the dead sometimes telephoned relatives or strangers to deliver messages. Many witnesses have reported their experiences, and their stories are all alike. The phone rings, sometimes with a different ring, even if it is disconnected or out of operation. The line is crackling, sometimes a wind seems to blow, the voice is distant, the communication brief, often unique but not always. Most of the time, the messages consist of mundane love words, posthumous happiness assurance, comfort words or warnings, and then the communication abruptly breaks down. In the case of multiple appeals, the deceased often repeats the same sentence as, for example, &#8220;It&#8217;s cold here&#8221; or &#8220;Why did you bury me next to grandmother?&#8221; &#8221;</p>
<p>Often calls are anonymous and untraceable but sometimes the number of the missing or strange numbers, such as &#8220;000 000 0000,&#8221; are displayed on the screen. In case of absence, some would even leave messages on answering machines or voice mail. The recipients of these calls are rarely involved in paranormal research, they are generally frightened by the phenomenon and fearing ridicule, they are reluctant to talk about it. Many cases have, however, been referenced in the world, which have been reported in books, magazines and newspaper articles.</p>
<p>In 1979, D. Scott Rogo and Raymond Bayless, two parapsychologists, have written a book about these phone calls from the beyond, <em>Phone Calls From the Dead</em> , featuring many well-documented cases. In one of these stories, several people were simultaneously talking to the missing and in another, the recipient spoke for a moment, then handed the handset to someone else when the mind asked.</p>
<h2> Pierre Monnier</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-29467" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/pierre-monnier.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 165px) 100vw, 165px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/pierre-monnier.jpg 165w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/pierre-monnier-99x150.jpg 99w" alt="Pierre Monnier" width="165" height="250" /></p>
<p>On January 8, 1915, Pierre Monnier, a young man of good family who had gone to war the year before, called his mother to reassure her, but it was her young cousin who answered the telephone: &#8220;Dagmar, tell mamma that I am alive. &#8221;</p>
<p>When she heard the news, her mother, Mrs. Cécile Monnier, called the telephone to find out where the call came from, but the operator told her that no one had asked for her number. Two days later, the gendarmes appeared at his door to inform him of Pierre&#8217;s death on January 8th on the front of Argonne. He was then twenty-three years old. On Monday, August 5, 1918, Mrs. Monnier received a telepathic message from her son, who commanded him: &#8220;Do not think of anything! Write! &#8221;</p>
<p>The poor woman, who believed that Pierre had sent her a sign on the day of her death, quickly grabbed a pencil and a little notebook and began to write the words of her son: &#8220;Yes, Asked to write. I believe that by this means we will be able to communicate much more easily. I&#8217;m so happy to be able to talk to you as I used to &#8230; &#8221;</p>
<p>For more than twenty years, Cécile Monnier kept the messages that Pierre sent her through automatic writing. These texts, mainly spiritual, were then collected and published in a book in seven volumes,  <em>The Letters of Peter</em> .</p>
<h2>Ida Lupino</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-29468" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/ida-lupino.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 200px) 100vw, 200px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/ida-lupino.jpg 200w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/ida-lupino-120x150.jpg 120w" alt="Ida Lupino" width="200" height="250" /></p>
<p>During the Second World War, Ida Lupino, an actress who lived in Los Angeles, received a phone call from her father, who had died six months earlier. The family home of the Lupino family, which was located in London, had just been destroyed by a bomb, and as no one knew where its title was, the family could not get the insurance money, An embarrassing situation. During this call, his father described to him with the greatest precision the place of the cellar where the papers were hidden. The young woman then informed her family and the documents were found at the indicated location. Mrs. Pendleton, a friend of the actress, witnessed this phone call and she vouched for the authenticity of the story.</p>
<h2>The Peggy Fox Case</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-29491 size-full" title="Phone Hanté 1960" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/telephone-1950.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 310px) 100vw, 310px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/telephone-1950.jpg 310w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/telephone-1950-300x242.jpg 300w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/telephone-1950-150x121.jpg 150w" alt="Phone Hanté 1960" width="310" height="250" /></p>
<p>On a Saturday morning in June 1960 in Toronto, Canada, Mrs. Fox was waiting for a call from her mother when the telephone bell rang in her fourth floor apartment. &#8220;I picked up the phone and almost fainted when I heard the voice. It was my daughter, Peggy. I immediately recognized him. She said, &#8220;Hello mom! Can you hear me? Do not be sad ! I am so happy ! Then the line was cut off. I stood there, motionless, unable to move, in shock. &#8221;</p>
<p>Peggy, Mrs. Fox&#8217;s daughter, died six months earlier, during the winter of 1959, a victim of a viral infection. She was twelve years old. Her mother, who worked half-time as a secretary, had gone through dark hours, but she was beginning to feel a little better. Finally, until that phone call &#8230; An hour later, when her husband, Paul, returned home, he found her in tears. She immediately told him his incredible experience and he concluded that someone had to make a joke of bad taste. Enervé, he immediately contacted the telephone company to find out the number of the joker but it appeared that nobody had called them from the morning.</p>
<p>Two days later, Paul was in the room when his wife answered the phone and seeing her turn pale, he understood at once. He quickly snatched the receiver, just in time to hear: &#8220;It&#8217;s Peggy, Mom do not cry &#8230;&#8221; Then suddenly the line was cut off. Shocked, Paul Fox contacted the phone company again, but no trace of the call could be found: &#8220;I could swear it was my daughter&#8217;s voice &#8230; Yet I was there when her coffin was taken down in the fall … &#8221;</p>
<p>In the following week, Ms. Fox received another call from the voice, which asked her to &#8220;spend the morning in Minou. This nickname was the one that Peggy had affectionately given to his maternal grandfather and no one knew him except his parents and her. &#8220;Nobody knew that, except for my daughter,&#8221; Fox said. &#8220;His words and the tone of his voice were identical to those of Peggy. She had the same funny way to pronounce the &#8220;th&#8221; as Peggy. I refuse to believe that someone was imitating him. &#8221;</p>
<p>Shortly afterwards, the story, which had been reported in the papers, attracted the attention of Dr. John Craggs, psychologist at the University of Chicago and psychic researcher, and he decided to investigate. &#8220;I&#8217;m sure Mr. and Mrs. Fox are telling the truth about these calls. There is absolutely no reason to think they are lying. With the agreement of the family, he installed a recording device that was to be triggered at the ringing of the phone. On August 3, 1960, Mrs. Fox answered the telephone as usual and the voice that resembled her daughter&#8217;s voice said:</p>
<p>&#8211; I love you. Tell Dad I love him too. I am very happy. Please do not cry like you did last time.</p>
<p>&#8220;Peggy, my dear, is it really you?&#8221; Asked Mrs. Fox.</p>
<p>&#8220;You must not be hurt.&#8221; I will try to &#8230; And suddenly, the communication was interrupted.</p>
<p>Dr. Craggs&#8217;s system worked perfectly: &#8220;The tape was shown to several of Peggy&#8217;s friends who all recognized his voice. The tape was preserved and is now in the archives of the American Society for Psychical Research.</p>
<p>Dr. Craggs concluded that external influences could manipulate the electrical pulses of telephones. This hypothesis may seem surprising, but in the case of Peggy Fox, no one has ever proposed a better one.</p>
<h2>Karl Uphoff</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-29477 size-full" title="Call of the Beyond" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/telephone-grand-mere-morte.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 297px) 100vw, 297px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/telephone-grand-mere-morte.jpg 297w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/telephone-grand-mere-morte-150x126.jpg 150w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/telephone-grand-mere-morte-239x201.jpg 239w" alt="Call of the Beyond" width="297" height="250" /></p>
<p>In 1969, a young New Jersey rock musician, Karl Uphoff, received a call from his grandmother, who had died two days earlier. Karl was eighteen at the time of the incident and he had always had a special connection with his grandmother, who was deaf. Sometimes she phoned her friends and she asked them, &#8220;Is Karl in your house?&#8221; Then, as she knew she could not hear the answer, she said without delay: &#8220;Tell her to go home.&#8221; Egotistically, Karl&#8217;s friends were annoyed at these constant calls and they were lecturing him for giving their number to the old lady.</p>
<p>Karl was overwhelmed by the disappearance of his grandmother, and as he did not believe in the survival of the soul, he never thought of hearing it again. Two days after his death, Karl was in the basement of an apartment in Montclair, New Jersey, when a friend&#8217;s mother went down to pick him up and told him he was being asked over the phone. Karl went up immediately and took the handset and an old woman began to talk to him, which he immediately recognized as his grandmother. He tried to ask her how she would call him when she was dead, but she hung up without answering.</p>
<p>Many more phone calls followed, but every time he asked about life after death, the old woman hung up. Finally, the calls ceased, but Frank was not saddened. He knew, even if she did not talk to him, that his grandmother was still there, near him.</p>
<h2>Mary Meredith</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-29499 size-medium" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/evp-voix-au-dela-300x169.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/evp-voix-au-dela-300x169.jpg 300w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/evp-voix-au-dela-150x84.jpg 150w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/evp-voix-au-dela.jpg 445w" alt="EVP Voice of the Beyond" width="300" height="169" /></p>
<p>In 1977, in Wilmslow, Cheshire, a young woman named Mary Meredith claimed to have received a phone call from her cousin Shirley, who lived in Manchester and had just heard of her death. The girl had been the victim of a car accident an hour earlier, and she had not survived. Mary would have liked to question her, but she did not have time. Shirley uttered a few words in a distant, disturbed voice, then silence.</p>
<h2>Ken Webster</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-29473 size-full" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/ken-webster.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 236px) 100vw, 236px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/ken-webster.jpg 236w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/ken-webster-150x150.jpg 150w" alt="Ken Webster" width="236" height="236" /></p>
<p>In 1984, Ken and Debbie Webster moved to the small village of Doddleston, England, and when they arrived in the house they noticed strange phenomena. The tin cans moved by themselves and rearranged in the cupboards, newspapers levitated above the table, imprints appeared in the dust etc &#8230;</p>
<p>Then one day Ken, who was a university professor, brought back a computer to work at home and mysterious messages began to arrive, which he found on his hard drive and which seemed to come from nowhere. Troubled, Ken and Debbie decided to study the phenomenon scientifically. If a spirit wanted to communicate with them through the PC, then they would give him the opportunity. They left the PC to turn day and night, and in fifteen months they received nearly two hundred and fifty messages from a certain Thomas Harden, who pretended to live, and not to have lived, under Henry VIII. He spoke in an English Middle Ages, using old names fallen into disuse to designate certain places and nicknames to talk about his contemporaries. His vocabulary, his spelling,</p>
<p>Apparently Thomas Harden did not know he was dead. He recounted his memories as if they were from the previous day, and it proved impossible to make him admit that King Henry VIII had not been there long ago. He said he lived in the house they were occupying now and communicated with them through a &#8220;light box.&#8221; He was even afraid of being arrested for witchcraft if anyone ever found out.</p>
<p>The dialogue continued until the computer crashed. It was later repaired, but Thomas Harden never reappeared.</p>
<h2>The History of Sadie</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-29501 size-full" title="Lady in Black" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/dame-en-noir-sadie.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 394px) 100vw, 394px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/dame-en-noir-sadie.jpg 394w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/dame-en-noir-sadie-300x190.jpg 300w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/dame-en-noir-sadie-150x95.jpg 150w" alt="Lady in Black" width="394" height="250" /></p>
<p>In the late 1980s, Sadie, who lived in Manchester, England, lost her husband in tragic circumstances and inherited a considerable sum. Shortly after, she moved to an old house on the outskirts of Sandbach with her seven-year-old daughter, Abigail. In a strange way, the landlord was only asking for a modest rent for the cottage, and Sadie would have liked to ask her about it but she thought the question was inappropriate and she had not dared to ask it during her visit. She began by cleansing the house, which was abominably dusty, then she adapted it to her liking and little by little she fell in love. She loved more than all the back garden, a peaceful place where a weeping willow nostalgic enthroned in the middle of a neglected lawn.</p>
<p>Three months after their arrival, one evening in December, Abigail told her mother with enthusiasm that she had just seen a &#8220;sort of old woman in a long black robe standing under the willow. The little girl, who did not seem frightened, explained with a smile that she had greeted him with her hand and that the old lady had disappeared. Abigail was a calm child who did not have the habit of imagining things or inventing fanciful stories, and her mother immediately worried. No one ever saw the ghost, but soon after, strange phenomena began to occur in the house.</p>
<p>One night, Abigail told her mother she was feeling sick and Sadie put her to bed earlier than usual. In the afternoon, the little girl had helped her to pull the weeds out of the garden, and as she was not used to it, her mother thought she was tired. Sadie then retired into the bedroom with a book.</p>
<p>An hour had elapsed when a blow struck the front door of the house, and wondering who could come to her house at twenty-three, the young woman was alarmed. She came down in slippers and nightgown in the entrance hall, and in a nervous voice she cried out through the door: &#8220;Who is there? &#8221;</p>
<p>A man, speaking in a loud voice, replied that he was a doctor, and that he had been called to examine a girl named Abigail. Sadie unlocked the door and opened it carefully, she looked out. A gray-haired man stood on the landing, a briefcase in one hand, a card in the other. Glancing quickly at the piece of cardboard, he asked her, &#8220;Are you all right &#8230; Sadie? Strangely, he knew his surname.</p>
<p>Surprised, the young woman explained that she had not called anybody, but as he was a doctor and his daughter was ill, she invited him back and took him to Abigail&#8217;s room. After examining the girl, who had strange red patches on her arms, the doctor explained to Sadie that her daughter had all the symptoms of meningitis. The man himself took Abigail and his mother to the hospital, where the disease was categorically identified. However, as it had been in its infancy, antibiotics soon came to an end. No one ever knew who had called the doctor for Abigail. Sadie was greatly disturbed by this mystery, which she sought to solve without succeeding. But a few years later &#8230;</p>
<p>In 1989, a handsome middle-aged man came to the cottage and told Sadie that his car had run out of gas, asked if she could lend him some books so he could fill up at the station Very close. The man promised to return later to reimburse him, and to prove his good faith, he proposed to leave his watch, an object of prize, as a pledge. Then, as he looked sincere, Sadie gave him a five-pound note and he was obviously very grateful. The man walked to the petrol station with his can, filled it with gasoline, and then returned to his Ford Fiesta, which was parked in an alley near the cottage. He then went to Sadie&#8217;s house, handed her the change of the five dollar bill she had lent him, And told him that he would immediately go and get the money he still owed him. The young woman tried to dissuade him, but the man seemed to be there because he left without waiting. He returned about six o&#8217;clock in the evening with a five-dollar note and a bouquet of carnations. Flattered by this attention, Sadie accepted the flowers, and he kissed her hand gallantly. He had just turned round, ready to go, when suddenly she exclaimed:</p>
<p>&#8211; Wait! You forget your wristwatch!</p>
<p>&#8220;Oh, yes,&#8221; replied the man, walking up the road.</p>
<p>&#8220;Come and have a cup of tea,&#8221; she said graciously.</p>
<p>Sadie was alone since the death of her husband, and she found the man seductive. They argued for hours. He told her that his name was Tim, that he was from Middlewich, and that he was coming out of a long relationship that had ended badly. His girlfriend, with whom he had been for four years, had suddenly left him for someone else and he had kept a certain mistrust for the opposite sex. The young woman advised her not to shut herself up because of an unfortunate experience, and she discreetly made him understand that she felt lonely. Sadie was almost forty, Tim was twenty-six, but the age gap did not seem so great. They left each other at twenty-one, after exchanging their telephone numbers.</p>
<p>Two days later, Sadie tried to phone Tim, but it appeared that the number he had given her was not assigned and she did not know what to think. She wondered if he had voluntarily given her a false number or if she had simply deceived herself but she hoped that he would call her and see each other again. A few days later, the phone rang in the house. Abigail replied, then ran to her mother, crying, &#8220;Mom, it&#8217;s for you! Sadie, hoping to hear Tim, grabbed the receiver hurriedly and said, &#8220;Hello?&#8221; &#8221;</p>
<p>An old woman then began to talk to her, who told him abominable things about Tim from Middlewich, claiming he was a bigam, that he was a crook and knew that Sadie&#8217;s husband had left him a great deal of money. &#8216;money. The young woman was heartbroken. She asked for her identity, and the old lady answered him to address her owner, who knew her and would give her the answer.</p>
<p>On Sunday night of the following week, Tim made a surprise visit to Sadie. This time he had brought her flowers and a bottle of wine. Troubled by the old lady&#8217;s words, she immediately spoke to him of the anonymous call but even before she had finished telling his story, Tim got up abruptly, then put on his coat and left the house without saying a word word. She never saw him again. A few months later she learned from a neighbor that the young man had an abominable reputation and had spent six months in jail for fraud. He was also known to have two women, one in Crewe, another Chester, and a mistress in Middlewich, with whom he lived.</p>
<p>Soon after, the owner of Sadie visited her for an unimportant question. She took the opportunity to explain that an old lady, who had refused to give her name, had called her to warn her of a certain danger, and began to be nervous. She added that the mysterious stranger had told her he knew her, and he admitted reluctantly that the previous tenants had told her to see the ghost of an old lady. She told them they would have nocturnal phone calls to advise them or prevent them, and he had told himself that they were looking for an excuse to leave without paying their rent. Sadie, who understood his dilemma, reassured him immediately. She did not intend to move. She loved the house and the ghost seemed harmless, not to say benevolent.</p>
<p>Visibly relieved, he told her that five years earlier an old girl named Enid had died at the cottage. She had lived there for twenty years, and she only rarely came out. Rumors had it that she had experienced a grief of love in her youth, and that she had never recovered from it. She loved the little garden behind the house, she spent a lot of time there. One afternoon, his body had been found under the weeping willow. The coroner concluded that he had stroke. A few months later, the new tenants had reported seeing the specter of an elderly woman crossing the back garden on a night in the middle of the night. They had seen her slide over the snow-covered lawn, but when they had gone out, they had found no footprints.</p>
<p>Sadie continued to live in the cottage with her daughter, exactly as she had said. She received no further phone calls from Enid, but every time the phone rang, she expected to hear it. Years later Abigail married, and Sadie, who was still single, found herself alone in the house. Finally alone &#8230; She never really felt alone. She knew that there, somewhere, Enid was still watching over her.</p>
<h2>Dean Koontz</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-29470" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/dean-koontz.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 279px) 100vw, 279px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/dean-koontz.jpg 279w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/dean-koontz-110x100.jpg 110w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/dean-koontz-150x134.jpg 150w" alt="Dean Koontz" width="279" height="250" /></p>
<p>On September 20, 1988, the author of Dean Koontz detective novels had an experience that he refused to speak for more than ten years. That day, he was working in his office when the phone rang. He picked up the receiver and the voice of a woman, who seemed distant to him, said: &#8220;Please, pay attention! Surprised, Dean asked him, &#8220;Who are you?&#8221; But the woman did not answer. She repeated the same warning three times, and on each occasion her voice seemed a little distant.</p>
<p>Suddenly the voice was silent, and Dean sat there listening to the silence for a while. He did not know what to think. The voice resembled that of his mother, who had been dead for almost twenty years. &#8220;It&#8217;s much harder to remember a voice than a face,&#8221; he told himself. &#8220;I have too much imagination. &#8221;</p>
<p>His phone number being on a red list, he knew that no one had been able to play him a trick. Perhaps someone had mistaken the number, quite simply. He told the story to his wife, but to no one else.</p>
<p>&#8220;It was a strange call. I do not pretend it was a ghost. I do not know what I think. It was certainly strange. People tell these stories all the time, and it always struck me that everybody seemed to have had one or two strange or disturbing experiences.</p>
<p>Sometimes I think the call was from my mother and sometimes it was a very strange bad number, a happy coincidence. I think you should always keep some skepticism about this kind of stuff, but it is comforting to think that there may be a kingdom where the personality survives. &#8221;</p>
<p>Two days after the phone call, Dean went to visit his father, who was a boarder in a nursing home. He had behavioral problems and the staff had asked his son to come and talk with him. Ray had hit another resident, a man with a walker, and the nurses were worried.</p>
<p>Dean did not know that his father had used part of his small allowance to buy a yellow-handled fishing knife. He had sharpened it so that it would be cut like a razor and he had oiled the hinge so that it could open like a notch.</p>
<p>When Dean entered his room, Ray moved quickly. He grabbed the concealed knife in a drawer, and he ran on to his son. Dean had to struggle to get away from him, and he narrowly escaped the blade of his knife. Many people witnessed this incident, and one of them called the police.</p>
<p>Finally, Dean managed to get the knife back, and he took it to the front desk when the policemen entered the hall. Seeing him with the knife in their hand, they immediately took out their arms and ordered him: &#8220;Throw the knife! Dean, who did not understand, pointed to his father&#8217;s room: &#8220;It&#8217;s not me you are looking for, it&#8217;s there. &#8220;Drop the knife!&#8221; Repeated the policemen, pointing their weapons at him.</p>
<p>Then suddenly he realized that they would shoot him if he did not drop the object. They thought he was the aggressor. Terrified, he quickly opened his hand and let go of the knife, which fell on the floor with a dull thud. He thought he was going to die. Finally, Dean was able to explain and they took his father to a psychiatric cell, where he was kept under observation.</p>
<p>Subsequently, Dean often thought back to the mysterious phone call. He told himself that he had induced him to be more cautious, and that he might have saved his life. He never received another call.</p>
<h2>The Wilson Affair</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-29487" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/james-byrne.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 258px) 100vw, 258px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/james-byrne.jpg 258w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/james-byrne-150x145.jpg 150w" alt="James Byrne" width="258" height="250" /></p>
<p>In 1995, a medium named James Byrne came every week to answer questions from the listeners of a radio station in Liverpool, England. Mr. Byrne said he was delivering messages from the other world, and he was very popular. He was even asked so much that in each of his passages, the calls would blow up the standard. One day Mrs. Wilson of Ellesmere Port called the radio station to try to talk to the medium. She was desperate. Her grandfather had died a year ago, and she wanted to know if he had a message for her. Unfortunately, the standard was so cluttered that its appeal was not meant to succeed. Then, as she could do nothing else, she sat down in her chair and listened to the show.</p>
<p>About twenty-two o&#8217;clock, at the beginning of the <em>News At Tens program</em> , as every evening, his telephone began to ring. Mrs. Wilson answered the call, and a distant and familiar voice said to her: &#8220;Listen, sweetie, I&#8217;m fine. It&#8217;s wonderful here. I&#8217;m with your grandmother and all the other nice people who are dead. &#8221;</p>
<p>Amazed, Mrs. Wilson, who had recognized her grandfather, murmured: &#8220;Grandfather, is it you? Her legs were so weak that it seemed she was going to fall. &#8220;Yeah, darling. Now listen. You have to stop living in the past and memories. Go ahead. I&#8217;m still there and I look at you. I have to go now love. Tell the children that I love them. Goodbye. &#8221;</p>
<p>Mrs. Wilson thought for a moment and once the emotion passed, she came to wonder if anyone had not made a joke. She dialed 1471 on her phone to get the last caller&#8217;s number but to her surprise the automated voice gave her her own number. As if she had telephoned herself. Mrs. Wilson, who had no other post in the house, then concluded that her grandfather had somehow called her from beyond to let her know that he was fine.</p>
<h2>The Thing</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-29484" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/franck-jones.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 221px) 100vw, 221px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/franck-jones.jpg 221w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/franck-jones-133x150.jpg 133w" alt="Franck Jones" width="221" height="250" /></p>
<p>In 1971, Mr. and Mrs. Ross told <em>The Gazette</em> that a malicious spirit, which they had dubbed <em>The Thing</em> , was pulling the covers of the children&#8217;s beds while they were sleeping, smelling stinking odors in their homes And that something was breathing close to their ears.</p>
<p>Twenty years later, Frank Jones, his wife and two children moved into the former Ross family home on Windsor Avenue in Thornton. Frank was more than skeptical about the reality of an evil presence, but he quickly changed his mind. &#8220;I thought they&#8217;d imagined it, but there was a lot of door slamming and a smell of dirt in the house. Then one evening I lay down in my bed, and a fog crossed the room. I wanted to shout something at him, but the words did not come out of my mouth. My face seemed paralyzed. I was completely overwhelmed. &#8221;</p>
<p>According to her daughter, Maureen, who was thirty years old, The Thing enjoyed opening the faucets and sacking the house. &#8220;You think people exaggerate until you experience it. One evening, I was alone at home when suddenly I heard these footsteps on the stairs. They went into my dad&#8217;s room and I heard all the cabinets banging, as if they were open. It sounded like burglars. &#8221;</p>
<p>In 1996 an exorcist of the Spiritualized Church of Fleetwood claimed to have expelled from property a &#8220;spirit trapped between two worlds&#8221; and all phenomena suddenly ceased. The family then had a few peaceful years, until 2003, when Frank experienced a double tragedy. He lost his son, Steven, thirty-two years old, from a brain tumor, and three months later his wife, Sadie, from a heart attack.</p>
<p>&#8220;Right after Sadie&#8217;s death, I went back home but I did not want to go home. I saw that I had a missed call on my mobile, but it had not rang and the number was that of my own home. Yet there was no one. Then I went inside, and there was the usual smell of Sadie&#8217;s cigarettes and that of her perfume. &#8221;</p>
<p>Subsequently, Frank and his family began receiving strange SMS messages and they concluded that they were from Sadie. &#8220;She always had a mobile with her. We buried him with his phone and the messages were composed of the words that Sadie used to say, but there was no number. &#8221;</p>
<h2>Charles Peck</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-29475" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/charles-peck.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 190px) 100vw, 190px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/charles-peck.jpg 190w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/charles-peck-120x150.jpg 120w" alt="Charles Peck" width="190" height="238" /></p>
<p>On September 12, 2008, a train crash at San Fermando, California, killed twenty-five people, including Charles Peck, a forty-nine-year-old man. He died on impact, but his body was not immediately found. During the following hours, his family received thirty-five calls from his cell phone. No one ever heard anything other than static electricity, but thinking that he was still alive, every time his fiancée was called, she shouted messages of encouragement: &#8220;Hang baby! &#8220;We&#8217;ll get you out of here!&#8221; &#8221; &#8221; Everything will be alright ! &#8220;Etc. When they tried to reach him, they immediately fell on the voicemail, as if the phone was already on the phone.</p>
<p>The authorities succeeded in drawing one of these telephone calls, which led them to the first wagon, where Charles Peck&#8217;s body was. According to the rescuers, there was no sign that he survived the accident, even for a short time. His phone kept calling his family for an hour, then he stopped for good. Some argued that his laptop had a technical failure and that he had dialed numbers from his address book at random, but in a strange way, only his family members, his son, his brother, his sister , His mother-in-law and his fiancee had been called.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/the-voices-of-the-beyond/">The Voices of the Beyond</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dangers of Ouija</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/the-dangers-of-ouija/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 08:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Misc]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=138</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/the-dangers-of-ouija/">The Dangers of Ouija</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-29335 size-full" title="Yesja Danger" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/ouija-dangereux.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 328px) 100vw, 328px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/ouija-dangereux.jpg 328w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/ouija-dangereux-281x300.jpg 281w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/ouija-dangereux-141x150.jpg 141w" alt="Yesja Danger" width="328" height="350" /></p>
<p>Many people, who wonder about the dangers of Ouija, write to me regularly to ask for advice. So, rather than giving my opinion, which has only relative value, I decided to gather the opinions of specialists of the paranormal, religious, scientists and testimonies of some participants. Thus, everyone can get an idea on the issue and decide, knowingly, whether to use a Ouija board</p>
<h2>The Opinion of the Experts of the Paranormal</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-29337 size-full" title="Manly P. Hall" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/manly-p-hall.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 288px) 100vw, 288px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/manly-p-hall.jpg 288w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/manly-p-hall-144x150.jpg 144w" alt="Manly P. Hall" width="288" height="300" /></p>
<p>Most paranormal investigators and mediums affirm that Ouija only has a name for it, that it opens a portal to evil spirits and demons, and that it can have serious consequences.</p>
<p>In 1944, the occultist Manly P. Hall, the founder of the Philosophical Research Society, declared in <em>Horizon</em> magazine : &#8220;In the last 20-25 years I have met a considerable number of people who have complicated their lives Playing with a Ouija board. Out of a hundred cases, at least ninety-five had disastrous consequences. I have seen broken homes, alienated families, and even suicides that can be attributed directly to this cause. &#8221;</p>
<p>Stocker Hunt, who had researched the effects of using a Ouija board, believed that victims often came into contact with spirits of the astral bottom. &#8220;The invader focuses on the character weaknesses of his victims. If one is vain, then calls to vanity will be made. &#8220;I need help,&#8221; said the invader, &#8220;You alone can help me.&#8221; The malevolent entity does not hesitate to lie, to change one&#8217;s identity, usually taking that of a deceased loved one, and she is flattering. It is preferable for the invader that his victim be alone, isolated and ill. If need be, it will frighten him by materializing in a horrible form, inducing grotesque visions, producing a poltergeist activity, materializing objects, Giving false or tragic news, and levitating objects or even his victim. All these things and more can be produced, not as ends in them, but as a means for complete eventual possession. &#8221;</p>
<p>In 1971, in his autobiography, medium Susy Smith issued this warning: &#8220;We must tell people to stay away from Ouija and automatic writing. I have experienced many and terrible problems with such practices. If I had been warned that I was at risk of mental disorders, I would probably be more cautious. &#8221;</p>
<p>In 1976, Martin Ebon explained in his book <em>The Satan Trap: Dangers of the Occult</em>  : &#8220;Everything can start innocently enough, perhaps with a Ouija board, which will begin to bring information to establish some credibility or pretend to be A deceased. It is common that people have allegedly chosen to perform a special task.</p>
<p>Then often, Ouija becomes vulgar, aggressive or threatening. Its demands increase and become hostile. Participants can use the board compulsively, as if they were possessed by a spirit, or hear voices that control or command them. &#8221;</p>
<p>In 1987, Phil Phillips and Joan Hake Robie wrote in their book, <em>Halloween and Satanism</em> : &#8220;The Ouija board is NOT a game for a pajama party. It is a deadly, serious and occult instrument. Nevertheless, there are people for whom the Ouija board is like a religion. They consult her to ask her to guide them, and they live according to what she tells them. This is extremely dangerous and can lead to destruction. &#8221;</p>
<p>The American demonologists Ed and Lorraine Warren said they understood the mediums who used Ouija knowingly, but they considered the game &#8220;as dangerous as drugs&#8221; for all amateurs. They asserted that during the Ouija sessions, evil spirits were often considered dead relatives to better control the lives of their victims. Ed even called the board a &#8220;famous passe-partout for terror.&#8221; &#8221;</p>
<p>John Zaffis, the famous paranormal investigator, said the most serious cases of harassment and demonic possession occurred after a Ouija session.</p>
<p>Ralph Sarchie, the famous policeman and demonologist who inspired the film <em>Deliver Us from Evil</em>, said that he had studied cases of witchcraft, Satanism, and that he had attended a dozen exorcisms but that Ouija Remained one of the greatest dangers of occultism. &#8220;There should be a law against these bad occult toys,&#8221; he wrote in his book <em>Beware the Night</em> . &#8220;I can hear some of you saying&#8221; Hey, I used a Ouija board, and nothing happened. &#8220;Consider yourself lucky then. It&#8217;s like playing Russian roulette. When you put the gun on your head, if you do not hear a loud sound, then it&#8217;s good. It is the same for Ouija. The more you pull the trigger, the more likely it is that at the next move, Your world will darken. &#8221;</p>
<p>Millions of Ouija have been sold around the world, which would be responsible for marriages, divorce, illness, misery, paranormal phenomena or murder. The medium Ann Rose commented on these stories as follows: &#8220;Horrible demons have most certainly been freed by the Ouija board. In an interview with the <em>Sun</em> , Mrs. Rose, who lived in Merriville, Indiana, warned readers of the newspaper, saying that evil spirits or demonic forces often gained the confidence of people experiencing Ouija in Responding honestly to several of their questions and offering them predictions. &#8220;Once they have gained the confidence of their victims, it is easy for the entity to take over the person either by strongly influencing it, Or by possessing it purely and simply. &#8221;</p>
<p>According to the ghost hunter Dale Kaczmarek of the Ghost Researtch Society: &#8220;Ouija is not dangerous in itself, but your way of communicating is often dangerous. Most of the time, the spirits contacted by the Ouija are those who reside on the lower astral plane. These minds are often very confused. They may have had a violent or sudden death, they were murdered, they committed suicide etc. Therefore, many violent, negative and potentially dangerous conditions are present for those who use the Ouija board.</p>
<p>Often, many minds try to come at the same time, but the real danger lies when you ask them for a physical proof of their existence! You might say, &#8220;Well, if you really are a spirit, can you put out that light or move that object? What you have just done is simple, you have opened a door. You have allowed them to enter the physical world and problems are to be expected. &#8221;</p>
<p>For the past few years, the sale of Ouija boards has been steadily increasing and Darren Ansell, a paranormal investigator, has expressed concern about this issue. &#8220;I will not advise anyone to use a Ouija board. The few times I tried to try, I had many fears. &#8221;</p>
<p>Dr. Peter Moscou, President of the Psychotronics Association in the United States, said the dangers of Ouija were real: &#8220;Unfortunately, there are many negative experiences with Ouija. I really can not recommend its use. In my experience, there are too many negative experiences, and sometimes very serious negative experiences, as a result of the opening up of areas of reality that people are not ready to manage. &#8221;</p>
<p>The medium Anna Foster explained the Ouija thus: &#8220;Imagine, if you will, that the Ouija board is a dimensional door. When you use the board you open it, as a receiving station, and you can get something positive or very negative. People often discover, from the moment they experience real negative phenomena with the Ouija, what we call the lower spirits. These are people who have not migrated to their next level of life. &#8221;</p>
<p>In his book <em>Your Powers Sprituels</em> Laura Tuan, who presents himself as an expert in astrology, parapsychology and esotericism, describes some methods and theories related to the paranormal. She dedicates a few pages to the Ouija, touting her merits and presenting it as an excellent means of communicating with spirits, but also with living beings. She ended by saying that we should not believe all the negative testimonies on the Ouija, which is absolutely not dangerous.</p>
<h2>The Scientific Opinion</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-29339 size-full" title="Sir William Barrett" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/sir-william-barrett.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 246px) 100vw, 246px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/sir-william-barrett.jpg 246w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/sir-william-barrett-123x150.jpg 123w" alt="Sir William Barrett" width="246" height="300" /></p>
<p>In general, scientists do not believe in spirits, demons and all these things, and they do not consider Ouija as a dangerous game. They accuse participants of unconsciously moving the clipboard, cheating or being naive. However, some psychiatrists advise against the practice of Ouija, underlining the disturbing psychological repercussions observed among the most fragile.</p>
<p>Toward the end of the nineteenth century, Sir William Barrett, an English physicist and parapsychologist, declared that the intelligence displayed in certain sittings of Ouija went well beyond the usual human faculties.</p>
<p>In 1924, Dr. Carl Wickland, an American psychiatrist, wrote a book on mental illness, warning users of Ouija boards: &#8220;The serious problem of alienation and insanity after attending mundane Psychic experiences has been brought to my attention. I have thus been able to observe the cases of several persons whose innocuous activities, such as automatic writing or the Ouija board, have led them into such wild madness that it has been necessary to lock them up in asylum. Many other disastrous consequences of the use of a Ouija board, a so-called innocent object, have been reported to me, and my observations have led me to seek in psychic phenomena a possible explanation for these strange events. &#8221;</p>
<p>In 1995, former Director of the New Jersey Psychiatric Asylum, Dr. Curry, declared that the Ouija board was a dangerous object that could cause mental imbalance and that if its popularity persisted, then the asylums would be filled with people, Having used.</p>
<p>According to scientific experiments conducted in 2014 by physicist Michael Faraday, chemist Eugene Chevreul and psychologists William James and Ray Hyman, many phenomena attributed to paranormal forces were due to an ideomotor effect. The participants, even if they are sincere, would move the board without even realizing it, by small unconscious muscular movements, in order to obtain a response in accordance with their expectations.</p>
<p>James Randhi, illusionist and skeptical, adheres to the theory of the ideomotor effect. In an experiment he found that when the participants in a Ouija session were blindfolded, then the messages delivered by the so-called spirits no longer made any sense. He then concluded that the movements of the planchette were due to the unconscious muscular thrusts of the participants and that all the other manifestations observed, the poltergeist phenomena, the revelations, the smells of decaying flesh, the Ouija plates refusing to burn, Was that legend. One day, when he spoke of the stories surrounding Ouija with one of his skeptical friends, he offered to pass on the message: &#8220;Ask everyone to go and buy a Ouija board and set it on fire. If it does not burn, They will earn a million dollars. &#8221;</p>
<p>Recently, a British university used a Ouija board in hopes of advancing knowledge about unconscious cognition. According to Hélène Gauchou, a member of the research team: &#8220;We can consciously believe that we do not know an answer, but in fact we have it somewhere in our subconscious. Maybe we heard it on the radio without paying attention to it. &#8221;</p>
<p>The experiment took place in two stages. The team first asked the participants concrete questions, who responded according to their level of knowledge, then asked the same questions using a Ouija board and some who said they did not know the answers first Times, have just answered. They were blindfolded, alone in front of the Ouija board, but the rate of correct answers rose from 50 to 65%. The researchers concluded that men possessed another intelligent, unconscious and accessible under certain conditions, and that Ouija did not allow to communicate with the spirits, but with a buried part of our brain.</p>
<p>According to Father Dominic Walker, psychologist and counselor in exorcism, the Ouija practice would not allow communication with the dead, but it would exert a dangerous influence on the minds of the participants.</p>
<p>According to Dr. Alberto Gonzalez of the Pan American Health Institute, terrifying demons, freed from other dimensions, attack defenseless men through Ouija boards. &#8220;They are vile creatures of the night,&#8221; explained Dr. Gonzalez. &#8220;They exist. They can possess the bodies of their victims and push calm and non-violent people to commit abominable crimes. They can take other forms, some quite horrible.</p>
<p>And they are among us, in many cases, solely because of these sinister toys called Ouija. &#8220;Dr. Gonzalez, a psychiatrist and parapsychologist, also claimed to have found evidence that demons were involved in several cases of female genital mutilation and vampirism in South America.</p>
<p>Dr. Marta Prohazka of Fairfax, Virginia, is convinced that spirits can play destructive and terrifying games with humans. &#8220;The use of Ouija has already led to violence and even assassination &#8230;&#8221; During her career as a psychotherapist and psychoanalyst, she realized that many patients, whom she had initially considered Hallucinating paranoid schizophrenics, could simply be in contact with something invisible to her, but visible to them. &#8220;I came to understand that another plan, or another dimension or existence, was interacting with our world,&#8221; she explained. &#8220;Through the formation and expansion of consciousness, some individuals acquire an entrance into this invisible dimension. For some people,</p>
<p>I also learned that contact with the other dimension could be dangerous, especially if a psychologically sensitive person loses emotional harmony. The window on the sky can then become a window on hell. &#8221;</p>
<h2>Reviews of Christians</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-29047 size-medium" title="Malaqui Martin" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/malachi-martin-300x300.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/malachi-martin-300x300.jpg 300w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/malachi-martin-150x150.jpg 150w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/malachi-martin.jpg 360w" alt="Malaqui Martin" width="300" height="300" /></p>
<p>Christians regard the Ouija as the instrument of the devil. The Bible does not speak of Ouija, but it warns against spiritism and, more generally, against all occult practices.</p>
<ul>
<li>Leviticus 19:31: &#8220;Do not speak to those who evoke spirits, nor to soothsayers; Do not consult them, not to be defiled by them. I am Yahweh your God. &#8220;</li>
<li>Deuteronomy 18: 10-12: &#8220;Let no one be found in you who causes his son or daughter to pass through the fire, who engages in divination, auguries, superstitions and enchantments, , Who consults evocators and sorcerers, and who questions the dead. For every man that doeth these things is an abomination to Yahweh, and it is because of these abominations that Yahweh your God will drive these nations out before you. &#8220;</li>
<li>Isaiah 8:19: &#8220;When they say to you,&#8221; See those who call to mind the dead, and the soothsayers who murmur and whisper, &#8220;reply,&#8221; Shall not a people consult their God? Will he consult the dead for the living? &#8220;</li>
</ul>
<p>For the religious authorities, to use a Ouija board, even innocently, opens a portal to demons that &#8220;then invade the heart and the mind&#8221; of those who have unintentionally attracted them. The dead are never manifested through the Ouija, only the evil spirits who pretend to be dead.</p>
<p>J. Godfrey Raupert was an investigator of the paranormal and hoped to prove scientifically spiritualism but he converted to Catholicism and renounced his project. In the late 1910s Ouija became such a concern for the Church that Pope Pius X asked Raupert to warn the faithful of the dangers of his use. In 1919 he published a book on the subject, <em>The New Black Magic and the Truth on the Ouija Board</em> , explaining that the spirits contacted were often Machiavellian, that they ridiculed Christianity and fanned the lowest instincts of the participants. &#8220;By this means it is easy to open a mental door through which the mind can be invaded and it is very difficult, if not impossible, To close this door to expel the invader. &#8221;</p>
<p>Fr. Thomas Euteneurer, exorcist and author of <em>Exorcism and the </em><em>Militant Church</em> , claimed that ninety percent of possession cases had started with a Ouija board.</p>
<p>Father Malachi Martin, a Jesuit who wrote many books on demonic possession, explained that the individual did not even need to engage with the demoniac intentionally to find himself possessed, but that it was enough for him to bubble In the occult, play with a Ouija board or just attend a session.</p>
<p>For the Catholic apologist Joel S. Peters, Ouija is a very dangerous game. &#8220;The Ouija board is far from being harmless, because it is a form of divination. In reality, the Ouija board does not really work, and the only spirits contacted through it are evil. That someone considers Ouija as harmless does not mean that it really is.</p>
<p>Disbelief for something does not necessarily mean that something is not real. The Ouija board has an objective reality that exists outside the perception of the object. In other words, it&#8217;s real, even if you do not believe in it. &#8221;</p>
<p>According to Father John Zühlsdorf: &#8220;Avoid, avoid, avoid these things that might open you up to oppression for the enemy, such as Tarot cards, Ouija, and other things that might be taken for&#8221; games. If you possess such things, destroy them now, not later. &#8221;</p>
<p>For Reverend Morris Cerullo, author of <em>The Black Side Of Satan </em> : &#8220;Many people have told me strange stories about answers given by a Ouija board. Ouija and other occult games may seem intriguing, but the consequences are serious and should not be approached. They can lead to dangerous waters in truth. &#8221;</p>
<p>In 2010, Father Luc Beaudoin, of the parish of Saint-Antoine-de-Lavaltrie, Quebec, had been a priest for four years and had already practiced a dozen exorcisms. He said: &#8220;Some houses where I went are sometimes places where spiritual sessions or black masses were celebrated. We must take these things very seriously. We do not play with this kind of practice. Ouija, we should not take this lightly. &#8221;</p>
<p>In 2015, Fr. José María Muñoz Urbano, the official exorcist of the diocese of Cordoba, was interviewed on the radio and said that the exorcism was still in great demand, even more and more, and that the possessions or infestations Often the consequence of Ouija&#8217;s session. &#8220;70% of cases of possessions or people infected by the demon that I meet are because of Ouija sessions,&#8221; explained the priest. &#8220;We want to try to talk with a dead man &#8230; We play and then strange things happen in the house where people suddenly begin to feel bad or some things do not work anymore. When we call the demon, it comes and then we have to pay the price. &#8221;</p>
<p>Father Vincent Lampert, an American exorcist priest, also found that demands for exorcism were becoming more and more frequent. In the United States, the number of exorcists has increased from twelve to fifty in ten years. The phenomenon is the same in the United Kingdom and other European countries, and largely due to activities &#8220;bringing the Devil,&#8221; such as the use of a Ouija board to dialogue with the dead.</p>
<p>&#8220;It is easy to invoke evil spirits with this board, but it is very difficult to get rid of it,&#8221; said a priest on condition of anonymity. &#8220;People can sometimes be very naive when they think they are in contact with the spirits of their loved ones. &#8221;</p>
<h2>Testimonials</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter wp-image-29341 size-full" title="Testimonials Ouija" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/temoignages-ouija.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 384px) 100vw, 384px" srcset="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/temoignages-ouija.jpg 384w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/temoignages-ouija-300x234.jpg 300w, http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/temoignages-ouija-150x117.jpg 150w" alt="Testimonials Ouija" width="384" height="300" /></p>
<p>Many Ouija boards have been sold around the world, and the testimonies are legion, both in the newspapers and on the Internet. Most users report having had a negative experience, and even terrifying at times, but some, much more rare, say they are satisfied with their sessions and feel ready to start over.</p>
<h3>The Ouija Hex</h3>
<p>( <em>National Examiner</em> of 17-03-1997)</p>
<p>I invited the horror into my house with a Ouija board. My brother and I had no results when we started using the psychic apparatus, then the message indicator suddenly and mysteriously began to move. The first thing Ouija told us is that the message was sent by Seth. I then made the tragic mistake of asking us to prove that it was real by doing something supernatural. The results were frightening and surprising. The council told us that the grandfather of one of my best friends was going to die in the week. The chandelier in the room began to shake violently and the chime sounded as if pieces of metal had banged together.</p>
<p>Suddenly all the noises ceased and the room became as silent as a cemetery in the middle of the night. My brother and I looked at each other, terrified. We opened all the windows to get rid of the decaying smell of flesh and we thought we would forget everything but a week later my friend&#8217;s grandfather died just as the board had Predicted! From time to time the chandelier made a back and forth movement, the room became icy and the terrible odor came back. I could not bear any more. I threw the Ouija and told the experience to my mother. She told me that once you&#8217;ve been rubbing with a Ouija board, her spell remains forever. Nowadays,</p>
<h3>Join Me in Hell</h3>
<p>(Tony&#8217;s testimony)</p>
<p>The night of terror began with a few drinks, one evening in July 2011. &#8220;It was just another night out with our group of friends,&#8221; explained Toni. &#8220;We all drank and decided to go to a friend&#8217;s house called Brittny. &#8221;</p>
<p>The idea of ​​using a Ouija board was floating in Toni&#8217;s mind for three days and when her friends sat down in Brittny&#8217;s house, she immediately offered to have a session. &#8220;I wanted to play with a Ouija board just for fun. As we had all drunk and my elder brother knew how to make a Ouija board home, we all thought it was a good idea. &#8221;</p>
<p>Unfortunately, they were cruelly mistaken. After reciting an opening prayer, the friends began their Ouija session. &#8220;We put my hands and my brother on the triangle we had cut and used as a planchette. We had it heated by rotating it in a circle for about forty seconds. &#8221;</p>
<p>They then stopped, and Toni&#8217;s brother asked the first question.</p>
<p>&#8220;Is there a spirit with us now?&#8221;</p>
<p>For a moment, nothing happened and then Toni&#8217;s friend Taylor made a sarcastic remark and the plank slipped to the Yes in the top corner of the board.</p>
<p>&#8220;At first, I really thought it was my older brother who made her move,&#8221; Toni said. But I was wrong. &#8221;</p>
<p>Toni, his brother and his friends played with the board in turn, and the messages became more and more dark.</p>
<p>&#8220;We changed people about eight times when we started to be afraid. Between all of us, we had allowed nine spirits to enter the room. &#8221;</p>
<p>Ouija told them that the minds of six women and three men were in the same room as they did, and they started asking them questions like, &#8220;Is one of you &#8216; Is committed suicide? &#8221;</p>
<p>Apparently, some had. &#8220;Ouija wrote the word&#8221; three. We then asked them how, proposing to them to designate the letter B Ball, P for hanged etc &#8230; »</p>
<p>At first, the plank slipped to the X, then it went to the P, and something happened that terrified them.</p>
<p>&#8220;We heard a soft knock, as if someone was rocking at the end of a rope and his feet regularly hit the wall. We asked the mind what was this noise and why he had killed himself, and he stated &#8220;woman.&#8221; »»</p>
<p>&#8211; Your wife was murdered?</p>
<p>&#8211; No.</p>
<p>&#8211; How she died ?</p>
<p>&#8211; Devil.</p>
<p>&#8220;We asked her if the devil had pushed her to do it, and the triangle went on Yes. We then inquired whether he hated women, and he answered each one of them. »»</p>
<p>A heavy silence fell on the room, which was only broken by the dull sound of their breaths and their occasional questions. The board moved quickly, sliding without hesitation on the table.</p>
<p>&#8220;We asked him if he wanted to harm one of the girls in the room, and the triangle said yes. We asked him how, and he spelled fire. »»</p>
<p>Then suddenly, the board began to move quickly from letter to letter and she repeatedly spelled the word &#8220;mutilate.&#8221; &#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;Then one of the candles we had lit fell on the floor and the hot wax splashed my leg. Or at least it seemed to me that it was hot wax. It finally turned out that it was a pretty deep cut. I do not know who made it to me. &#8221;</p>
<p>Despite this incident, the meeting continued. &#8220;Some started to have fun. When asked, the Ouija board identified each of the people present. &#8221;</p>
<p>The last to use Ouija were the brother of Toni and Brittny. The two boys came face to face, and they began to ask questions. &#8220;I was not afraid until the last session. This time we were dealing with a demonic spirit, an angry demonic spirit. &#8221;</p>
<p>Toni&#8217;s brother asked, &#8220;Are you good or bad?&#8221; Ouija replied that he was evil. &#8220;We all laughed, and my brother asked several questions. &#8221;</p>
<p>Taylor then shouted, &#8220;We should put it away and stop messing around with it. But the group was focused on the board, and everyone ignored it. &#8220;We asked the demonic spirit if he wanted to hurt someone in the room, and the board spelled&#8221; hat. &#8221; But Taylor was the only one wearing a hat. My brother asked him to point the triangle to the one he wanted to hurt, and he went straight to Taylor. &#8221;</p>
<p>The young man jumped out of his seat swearing and then went to sit in another part of the room, away from Ouija. The point of the planchette followed him and she wrote that he was cursed. &#8220;We asked more questions, but most of the answers were too confusing for us to understand. Others, on the other hand, were very clear.</p>
<p>&#8220;The Ouija board spelled out my father&#8217;s name and I almost got a heart attack because my dad is really a first bastard. &#8221;</p>
<p>Toni&#8217;s brother asked him why he was interested in their father, and the board started to move again. &#8220;He slowly wrote&#8221; agreement with the devil. My brother asked him to be more specific, and he replied &#8220;no work.&#8221; &#8220;Indeed, their father did not work. He was invalid, he was receiving a government pension and his medicines were free. The board began to spin, stopping briefly on certain letters.</p>
<p>JOINMEINHELLPAD (Join me in Hell Pad)</p>
<p>&#8220;My brother knocked down the Ouija board before he finished writing our name. &#8221;</p>
<p>Toni&#8217;s brother and Brittny took the Ouija board and destroyed it, just like the leaves they used to write the messages of the spirits. Then they burned the pieces.</p>
<p>&#8220;After that night, I never touched a Ouija board again. I now know it&#8217;s not a game. &#8221;</p>
<h3>A Ouija Summons A Demon</h3>
<p>( <em>The Sun</em> , 09-12-1986)</p>
<p>A simple Ouija board became a passport to hell for a family who accidentally invited a demon into their living room. &#8220;I thought it could be the devil himself,&#8221; said John Ravens, the father of the tormented family. &#8220;When it was over, we were all bleeding and we had serious traces of burns. Our living room was a disaster area. &#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;It was supposed to be a joke,&#8221; said his wife Gloria. We wanted to make believe that we were talking with the spirit world. &#8221;</p>
<p>Young Lynda, her nine-year-old brother, Ronald, and their parents had gathered around a Ouija board for what they thought was a pleasant evening in their home on the outskirts of Toronto, Canada. &#8220;We were just playing with all of a sudden, the board that gives the answers started to move by itself,&#8221; John explained. &#8220;We were all scared, but I thought maybe one of the kids was joking us. We started asking questions, and that spirit started talking to us. Then he asked if he could come and see us. At the time, I was sure someone was playing a trick, and I said yes. &#8221;</p>
<p>That&#8217;s when the nightmare really started. &#8220;The demon appeared in a few seconds. He walked around the room laughing and cursing us all. It was surrounded by a ring of fire and the room became so hot it looked like a brazier of hell. The family described the demon as a red and black creature with scales on the skin, horns and large bat wings. &#8220;Then he suddenly fell on us and he attacked us. He began by biting each of us in the face and arms. We tried to get up and run to the door, but whenever we did, the creature scratched us. It was so fast that we could not escape. &#8221;</p>
<p>Lynda and her brother were caught repeatedly and thrown across the room. When they fell helplessly on the ground, the demon leapt upon their breasts and heads. &#8220;He had clogs that left traces on my children&#8217;s faces and skin, scarred them cruelly,&#8221; added Gloria. The attack lasted more than an hour before the demon disappeared as quickly as it had appeared. John then took out the children, who screamed and cried, from the house and took them to a nearby hospital, where they were treated for cuts and burns.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Positive Experience with Ouija</h3>
<p>(Testimony Anonymous)</p>
<p>In June 2002, I lost my sister in dramatic circumstances. She was seven months pregnant and had a stroke following an aneurysm. She and the baby died. She was only twenty-two and needless to tell you that shook the family. She died during her baby shower, and it was really weird.</p>
<p>A few years later my mother came to see me and she confessed that from time to time she would play with a Ouija board with some friends and talk to my sister Emma. At first I thought she was crazy and I told her she was stupid. Eventually, she managed to convince me to sit down to take part in a session with her and her friends. They started asking commonplace questions, such as &#8220;Is someone here?&#8221; Then it became more personal.</p>
<p>My sister told us she was there and then she told us things that only my mother and I knew. She seemed very, very real. I was never afraid, I felt almost at peace.</p>
<p>Little things happened. Sometimes my mother smelled a pat on her shoulder and the Ouija said, &#8220;I&#8217;ve got it! On other occasions, the telephone rang and the Ouija asked us, &#8220;Why are not you going to answer?&#8221; &#8221;</p>
<p>I had always been told not to get close to Ouija boards, to invite evil into your life, among other things, but I have tried many times, and I have never had a bad experience.</p>
<h3>Good experience with Ouija</h3>
<p>(Testimony Anonymous)</p>
<p>True story. Several years ago when I was a teenager, I was seventy-three years ago, and I was in the forces stationed in Gilbratar. One day, one of the girls, whom I will call Joan, wanted to try a Ouija board and she made one with cut letters and a simple glass. Another girl and I refused to attend, but we sat down and watched from a distance. His questions were of the kind that young girls like to ask &#8220;Will I get married? &#8220;How many children will I have?&#8221; Each time, the glass began to move and he answered his questions.</p>
<p>At one point, the other girl, whom I will call her Fay, accused Joan of moving the glass, telling her that it was easy to cheat because all the answers were about future events, which could not be verified . Joan asked me to ask a question I knew the answer but that no one else knew. I ended up asking him my father&#8217;s first name, which is usually used as a surname.</p>
<p>At first, the glass remained motionless then it began to move and slowly, he spelled correctly his first name. He then wrote my name and a message. He told me that I was loved and that I should not be afraid because I was protected. At that moment, Joan had her finger on the glass and she looked frightened.</p>
<p>As the glass uttered the last word, suddenly he fled from under his finger, he crossed the table and he smashed on the floor. Needless to say, she never wanted to try again.</p>
<p>At the time, my father was alive and well, but I had no contact with him since the divorce of my parents. All I know is that regardless of the difficulties in my life, something or someone has always managed to fix them at best. Is it a coincidence or does someone or something watch over me? I would not know how to say it. I never retouched a Ouija board.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/the-dangers-of-ouija/">The Dangers of Ouija</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Legend of the Werewolf</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/legend-of-the-werewolf/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 08:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Misc]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=135</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/legend-of-the-werewolf/">Legend of the Werewolf</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The term waswolf, or lycanthrope (lykánthrôpos of the Greek lúkos, loup and ánthrôpos, human being), refers to a human being who has the faculty of transforming himself into a wolf, voluntarily or involuntarily. The metamorphosis usually occurs during the nights of full moon, forcing the lycanthropus to wander in its wolf form until the first rays of the sun.</p>
<p>In its modern version, the werewolf presents all the physical characteristics of the wolf: long hairs completely cover the body and it is suddenly provided with fantastic muscular power, long fangs and sharp claws. The werewolf screams to the moon like a wolf, and if he sometimes stands on two legs, like a man, it is not an absolute rule. When he changes his appearance, his sense of smell, hearing and night vision develop. He becomes agile, cunning, and shows incredible speed. The werewolf is a lonely and merciless killer. He always shows an implacable ferocity and massacres without distinction the animals and the men whom he crosses at random from his nocturnal outings in order to regain their flesh. Like the vampires,</p>
<h2>Little Loup-Garou History</h2>
<div id="attachment_959" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-full wp-image-959" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/Loup-garou-Lebrun.jpg" alt="Etchings by Charles Lebrun" width="301" height="250" /></p>
<p class="wp-caption-text">Etchings by Charles Lebrun 1806</p>
</div>
<p>There used to be as many different versions of the werewolf as legends. Its appearance varied according to the time and country, but it was often described as difficult to differentiate from an ordinary wolf.<br />
The werewolf was provided with a large mouth, a sparkling look and hooked teeth. He was sometimes portrayed as a huge wolf, others like a wolf-headed human, but it could also look like our modern version of the werewolf. Here is Simon Goulard&#8217;s description (1543-1628): &#8220;The werewolf is different from the wolf in that his coat is not outside, but between leather and flesh. It goes as fast as the wolf, which must not be found unbelievable, for it is the efforts of the evil demon that shape them as the wolves want. While walking, They leave on the earth the trace of wolves. Their eyes are frightful and sparkling like wolves, ravages and cruelty of wolves, choke dogs, cut their throats with teeth to young children, take a taste for human flesh like wolves, have skill and resolution Men to perform such acts. And when they run together, they are accustomed to depart from their hunt to each other. If they are drunk, they scream to call the others. &#8221; They are accustomed to depart from their hunt to each other. If they are drunk, they scream to call the others. &#8221; They are accustomed to depart from their hunt to each other. If they are drunk, they scream to call the others. &#8221;</p>
<p>Some testimonies said that the lycanthropists did not have a tail, but that they kept their eyes and a human voice. Thus, according to some Swedish tales, the werewolf could be distinguished from an ordinary wolf because it moved only on three legs. He stretched the fourth backwards to make it look like a tail.<br />
If their descriptions changed, there was one thing in common among all lycanthropists in medieval Europe: they seemed to have a clear preference for young children, and they devoured freshly buried corpses.<br />
The powers of the lycanthropes seemed to increase during the new moon and at the time of the solstices, but some Christian religious festivals seemed to reinforce them as much. So, In some texts, mention was made of transformations which had lasted up to twelve days after Christmas. In the twentieth century Gervais de Tilbury pointed out that in England it was common to see men change into wolves when the moon began a new cycle. In 1848, when the moon was red, one could witness epidemics of lycanthropy.</p>
<p>Olaus Magnus reported that in Prussia, Livonia and Lithuania, the inhabitants suffered throughout the year from the rapacity of the wolves who decimated their cattle, but as they were dispersed through a great number of woods, they were not Not as dangerous as the men who turned into wolves.<br />
For the feast of Christ&#8217;s Nativity, a multitude of men transformed into wolves gathered in certain places to spread their rage and incredible ferocity against human beings and domestic animals.<br />
People from these areas suffered much more from these wolves than from real wolves because when they spotted an isolated dwelling in the woods, they cruelly besieged it, striving to break its doors. When they arrived, They devoured all the human beings and all the animals that were inside. They also broke into the beer cellars, emptied the barrels of beer or mead and then piled empty casks one above the other in the middle of the cellar, thus showing their difference with the real wolves. Between Lithuania, Livonia and Courland stood the walls of an old castle in ruins. At this place thousands of wolves were gathering, trying to prove their agility in the jump. Those who were unable to cross the walls, as was often the case with the larger ones, were killed without hesitation by their captain. Emptied the casks of beer or mead, and then they piled the empty barrels one above the other in the middle of the cellar, showing their difference with the real wolves. Between Lithuania, Livonia and Courland stood the walls of an old castle in ruins. At this place thousands of wolves were gathering, trying to prove their agility in the jump. Those who were unable to cross the walls, as was often the case with the larger ones, were killed without hesitation by their captain. Emptied the casks of beer or mead, and then they piled the empty barrels one above the other in the middle of the cellar, showing their difference with the real wolves. Between Lithuania, Livonia and Courland stood the walls of an old castle in ruins. At this place thousands of wolves were gathering, trying to prove their agility in the jump. Those who were unable to cross the walls, as was often the case with the larger ones, were killed without hesitation by their captain. At this place thousands of wolves were gathering, trying to prove their agility in the jump. Those who were unable to cross the walls, as was often the case with the larger ones, were killed without hesitation by their captain. At this place thousands of wolves were gathering, trying to prove their agility in the jump. Those who were unable to cross the walls, as was often the case with the larger ones, were killed without hesitation by their captain.</p>
<p>The origins of the werewolf are old and uncertain. For many centuries the specialists have been confronting each other on the subject without being able to agree. Of course, many factors can explain the legends about the lycanthropes, but there is still a part of the unresolved mystery that makes the belief in the myth of the werewolf still strangely widespread. According to the legends and writings that have come down to us, there used to be many ways to become a werewolf. Lycanthropy may be due to the bite or scratches of a wolf or werewolf, satanic ritual, curse, absorption of human flesh, magic filter or pact with But it could also be acquired at birth,</p>
<div id="attachment_960" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-full wp-image-960" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/Zeus-Lycaon.jpg" alt="The Metamorphosis of Lycaon en Loup" width="353" height="250" /></p>
<p class="wp-caption-text">The Metamorphosis of Lycaon en Loup</p>
</div>
<p><span class="ContentBox" data-cd="Text">Lycanthropy could be the result of a divine punishment as we learn from the legend of King Lycaon, the first and oldest of the famous werewolves. In Greek mythology, Lycaon was king of Arcadia. He was known to be a cruel king who respected nothing and nobody and was known for his disdain for the gods. In order to test him, Zeus, accompanied by other gods, presented himself to him in the guise of a beggar.<br />
Lycaon, scenting the trap, invited the beggars to eat at his table. But, desiring to verify their divine nature, he caused his grandson, Arcas, to be killed and offered it to the gods as a meal.<br />
All the gods immediately perceived it, except Demeter, who mistakenly ate a shoulder. Unworthy, Zeus then thundered the king&#8217;s fifty sons and then changed Lycaon into a wolf. The young Arcas was resurrected and Zeus offered him the throne of his grandfather. When her shoulder was missing, she was replaced by a silver shoulder.<br />
Following this legend, cannibalism was closely associated with lycanthropy in ancient Greece, where it was also believed that devouring the raw flesh of an enraged wolf transformed into a lycanthropist.</span></p>
<p>On Mount Lykaion, the birthplace of Zeus, games were held every four years. They were accompanied by banquets in honor of the god, during which practices of cannibalism were common. The human flesh was divided between the different participants who were then changed into wolves for nine years. If they did not consume any human flesh during this period, they could then recover their original form.<br />
Quoting Agriopas, Pliny the Elder reported the story of the Demenet of Parrhasia, who, having tasted the entrails of a child, sacrificed at a sacrifice that the Arcadians had made to Jupiter, had been transformed into a wolf. At the end of ten years, he had returned to his human form and then went to the Games, where he had competed for the price of the pugilate. He had returned victorious from Olympia. In his writings Pliny the Elder also quoted Euanthes, a Greek writer who was not without reputation, who explained that according to the books of the Arcadians, a man from the family of a certain Anthus was chosen at random from among his own And that he was taken to a pond in Arcadia and then hung his clothes on an oak before crossing the pond, then he turned into a wolf and lived with them for nine years. If, during this period, he stood away from the man, then he could return to the pond and after crossing it, he recovered his human form, aged nine years. He indicated that he even found his old clothes.<br />
According to certain superstitions, stealing the clothes of a lycanthropist prevented him from regaining his human form. In France,</p>
<p>In France, around 1131, Hugues de Camp d&#8217;Avesnes, Count of Saint-Pol, called the Canterine Beast, was changed into a werewolf by divine force because of the terrible crimes he had committed. During the night he could be seen wandering through the streets, screaming, loaded with chains.</p>
<p>The angels, the priests and some saints apparently also possessed the power to launch this curse. Saint Thomas Aquinas had a maxim on this subject: &#8220;Omnes angeli, boni and Mali, ex virtue naturali habent potestatem transmutandi corpus nostra&#8221; (All angels, good or bad have the power to transform our bodies).<br />
Saint Natalis would have cursed an Irish family whose members had become wolves for seven years and Saint Patrick would have transformed the Welsh king Vereticus into a wolf. The excommunicated Catholics, for their part, were suspected of being werewolves. In other tales the divine intervention was even more direct and in Russia a legend related that men had become werewolves after incurring the wrath of the devil.</p>
<p><img class="alignleft wp-image-965 size-full" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/loup-garou-peinture.jpg" alt="Werewolf Metamorphosis" width="158" height="250" /></p>
<p>According to some popular beliefs, sorcerers, gods and the Devil could easily change a man into a wolf (or a wild beast) by throwing a curse on him.<br />
In the fifth century BC Herodotus, in his Histories, recounted that the Greeks who had established themselves on the shores of the Black Sea in the north-east of Scythia regarded the members of the Neur tribe as skilled strong magicians who Were transformed into wolves once a year, for several days, before resuming their human appearance.<br />
The Neures observe the same customs as the Scythians. It seems that these people are enchanters. Indeed, if we are to believe the Scythians and the Greeks established in Scythia, each Neure changes once a year into a wolf for a few days, and then resumes its first form. The Scythians may well say, they will not make me believe such tales; It is not that they support them, and even with an oath.<br />
In Polish folklore, if a witch threw a human skin belt on the threshold of a house in which a marriage was celebrated, then the husband and wife, the damsels and the groomsmen turned into wolves . After three years, the witch covered the skin of their hair and they then found their human form.<br />
On this subject, an anecdote related that a sorceress having thrown a skin too small on the husband, when it resumed its human form, it retained its tail of wolf. If a witch threw a human skin belt on the threshold of a house in which a marriage was celebrated, then the husband and wife, the damsels and the groomsmen turned into wolves. After three years, the witch covered the skin of their hair and they then found their human form. On this subject, an anecdote related that a sorceress having thrown a skin too small on the husband, when it resumed its human form, it retained its tail of wolf. If a witch threw a human skin belt on the threshold of a house in which a marriage was celebrated, then the husband and wife, the damsels and the groomsmen turned into wolves. After three years, the witch covered the skin of their hair and they then found their human form. On this subject, an anecdote related that a sorceress having thrown a skin too small on the husband, when it resumed its human form, it retained its tail of wolf.</p>
<p>Sorcerers were able to cast a curse that changed their enemies into werewolves, but most often they chose to transform themselves in order to satisfy their appetites of human flesh. They performed a ritual during which various satanic allegiances were pronounced. If the ritual was properly followed, the invoker could take on the appearance of the wolf by putting on his skin.<br />
In this new form he attacked the herds and the men, whose flesh he devoured. He could, of course, regain his original form when he wished. In the 12th century, according to William of Palermo, many wizards roamed the fields during the nights of full moon, equipped with wolf skins, in order to frighten the populations.<br />
Thievenne Paget, Who was a witch, also changed into a she-wolf, according to her own confession. Thus metamorphosed, she accompanied the Devil in mountains and valleys, killing cows and devouring children. Claude Isan Prost, a lame woman, Clauda Isan Guillaume and Isan Roquet, who participated in the murder of five children, apparently did as much.</p>
<p>In Norway, it was thought that some people could take the form of a bear or a wolf and then return to their human form by their own will. This faculty was transmitted to them by the Trollmen, and those who possessed it were themselves called Trolls.<br />
In a hamlet, in the midst of a forest, a man named Lasse lived in a cottage with his wife. One day he went to the forest to cut down a tree, but before forgetting to cross himself and say his Pater, so that some trolls or wolves took control easily and turned it into a wolf. His wife wept for many years, but on Christmas Eve a truly poor beggar with ragged clothes knocked at her door. The woman of the house was good. After having made her go home, She nurtured it, and treated it with kindness. Before leaving, the beggar told the woman that she would probably be happy to see her husband again, for he was not dead but he was walking in the forest like a wolf. At nightfall, the woman went to her pantry to pick up a piece of meat for the next day when suddenly, as she turned to go out, she caught sight of a wolf standing on her paws looking at her With a sad and hungry air. Seeing that, the woman exclaimed: &#8220;I&#8217;m sure you were my Lasse, I&#8217;ll give you some meat.<br />
At that moment the skin of a wolf disappeared. In front of her now was her husband in the clothes he wore the day she had seen him for the last time. It is easy to distinguish in this moralistic fable,</p>
<p>In the Satyricon, Niceros related that he had been invited to the banquet of one of his friends and that he had suddenly turned into a wolf. According to Niceros: &#8220;When I turned to my friend, I saw that he had taken off his clothes and had piled them by the side of the road. He sat in a circle around his clothes, and then, like that, turned into a wolf! He uttered loud howls and then fled into the woods. &#8221;<br />
Legend of the Lithuanian folklore assured that it was also possible to turn into a werewolf carelessly touching glasses with a werewolf when he gave a transmission formula. In his collection Chansons du peuple russe, Ralston also gave an incantation which still remains popular in Russia today.</p>
<p>In the 9th century Nennius reported in his <em>Historia Brittonum</em> that some Celtic men were reputed to be able to take the form of a wolf at will through a diabolical force derived from their ancestors. They attacked the sheep, and when they were pursued by people armed with sticks, they fled as quickly as possible.<br />
When they wanted to transform themselves, they left their human bodies, but they had firmly told their loved ones that they should not change their positions because, if they did, they could never take back human form again. If someone wounded them in their wolf form, the wound was visible at the same place on their human body.</p>
<div id="attachment_961" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-full wp-image-961" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/loup-garou-allemand.jpg" alt="Werewolf" width="455" height="200" /></p>
<p class="wp-caption-text">Werewolf German 1722</p>
</div>
<p>If Lycanthropy was often connected to the Devil, there is a rare and little known tale, that of an old man named Thiess. In 1692, at Jurgenburg, in Livonia, Thiess testified under oath that he and the other werewolves were the dogs of God. He claimed that they were warriors who had gone to hell with witches and demons. Their efforts had ensured that the Devil and his henchmen did not carry the grain of the last harvests into hell.<br />
Thiess was firm in his assertions, saying that werewolves in Germany and Russia had also fought the devil&#8217;s henchmen in their own versions of hell. He maintained that when the werewolves died, their souls were welcomed into heaven in thanksgiving for their service.</p>
<p>In some countries, children with physical characteristics or those born at certain dates were predisposed to become werewolves. The Serbs, Poles, and Slovenes asserted that children who were born with hair or a task of wine had the gift of double vision and could be transformed into different animals. The wolf was, of course, the animal they preferred. The belief in this phenomenon was so strong that in the 16th century the Church of Russia felt obliged to condemn it.</p>
<p>According to the Galician tradition, the seventh son of a family could be normal or a werewolf. If it was normal, the child had the image of a cross or the wheel of St. Catherine in his mouth, and if he was a werewolf, he had no sign. That a brother sponsors the child for his baptism and confirmation could prevent the metamorphosis. If no brother was available, then baptizing the child by the name of Bieito could also prevent him from becoming a werewolf.<br />
Children born during the full moon, those who were conceived on the eve of a Sunday or a holy day, those born on Christmas day, those with a tail embryo and those who were born with a piece Of placenta on the head) were more likely than others to become werewolves.</p>
<p>In the south of France, it was believed that destiny destined certain men to become lycanthropists. The desire to run came to them at night. They then left their beds, jumped out of the window, and plunged into a fountain. When they came out, they were covered with dense fur, walked on all fours, and wandered through fields and meadows, forests and villages, biting all the animals and human beings they found on Their path. As they approached dawn, they would return to the fountain, plunge into it, lose their fur skins and find their empty beds.</p>
<p>For those who wanted to transform themselves voluntarily into lycanthrope, the thing was relatively easy. One of the simplest ways to turn into a wolf for someone who had no knowledge of magic was to take off his clothes, wear a wolf skin belt or rub his body with various magic ointments .<br />
In 1603, Judge Henri Boguet in The Speech of Wizards emphasized the use of such ointments:<br />
&#8220;Many confessed that, in order to put themselves in wolves, they rubbed themselves with a certain fat; That afterwards the devil affixed to them a wolf&#8217;s skin covering their whole body; After which they set themselves on all fours, and ran among the fields, sometimes after a person, and sometimes after a beast, as their appetites guided or transported them.<br />
It was also possible to drink rain water in the print in wolf or other wild animal, to drink water from a spring where the wolves came to drink, to devour the brains of a wolf, A wolf or sleeping at the place where the beast usually rested. Beer mixed with blood was known to accelerate the metamorphosis sought.<br />
In the 16th century, the Swedish writer Olaus Magnus stated that the werewolves of Livonia had been initiated after drinking a cup of specially prepared beer by repeating an established formula. Beer mingled with blood was known to accelerate the metamorphosis sought. In the 16th century, the Swedish writer Olaus Magnus stated that the werewolves of Livonia had been initiated after drinking a cup of specially prepared beer by repeating an established formula. Beer mingled with blood was known to accelerate the metamorphosis sought. In the 16th century, the Swedish writer Olaus Magnus stated that the werewolves of Livonia had been initiated after drinking a cup of specially prepared beer by repeating an established formula.</p>
<p>In Galicia, a person could become a werewolf by throwing his clothes and leaving his home every Friday. He then had to visit seven villages, and clothe himself in each. He could regain his human form by burning one of the skins he was wearing or bleeding.<br />
In France, Italy and Germany it was thought that man could turn into a wolf if he slept alone outside during certain summer nights on Wednesdays and Fridays and if the full moon directly illuminated his face .<br />
In Russia, the werewolf is called an Oborot. Beliefs affirmed that to become Oborot, one had to follow the following ceremonial:<br />
One who wants to become an Oborot, that he seeks in the forest a small tree and that he stabs it with a knife of copper. He will then walk around the tree, repeating a certain incantation and throwing himself three times against the tree. He can then run into the forest, transformed into a wolf.<br />
In Denmark he said to himself that if a woman lay between four sticks the membrane that wraps a foal at her birth and then sneaks through it, naked, then she would give birth without pain but all the boys she would have would be wolves- And all the daughters of the maras.</p>
<p>It would seem that in some cases, lycanthropy was not the result of a metamorphosis of the body but of a journey of the soul. When a soul was damned, she could not find repose, and sometimes she came out of her grave under the guise of a wolf. This soul then set off in search of a host, and there was generally a fierce struggle between the original soul and the damned soul who sought to take possession of this body. If the damned soul were to win, then the host turned into a werewolf.<br />
In the 1st century, Arétée of Cappadocia spoke of certain men who were persuaded to be made of glass. They were afraid of being broken, in which case they were transformed into wolves. Their behavior became similar in all respects to the animal. They preferred to go out at night, scream at death, and,</p>
<p>The number seven, supposedly sacred, was frequently associated with werewolves. Some lycanthropes were thus condemned to live seven years in their form of wolf in expiation of their crimes or so that the spell cast on them ceases. Each night they had to go through seven parishes and walk around seven bell towers before finding a place in Hell. Breaking Lent seven years in a row was undeniably leading to a metamorphosis.<br />
By their own admission, lycanthropists often united themselves in wolves, and they asserted that their pleasure was intense. When the metamorphosis ceased and the werewolf resumed its human form, he felt physically weak and morally tortured.</p>
<h2>Recognizing a Werewolf</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/lycanthrope.jpg" alt="lycanthrope" width="343" height="250" /></p>
<p>Due to its suspicious and cunning nature, it was difficult to recognize a werewolf as it evolved in its human form. Yet, some signs were revealing because the lycanthropes sometimes retained characteristics specific to their metamorphosis. <span class="ContentBox" data-cd="Text">Bushy eyebrows, red teeth, ears a little lower than normal and behind the head, hairy hands inside the palms, flat and webbed fingers, the middle finger and index finger of the same length , Squat thumbs, slightly reddish or curled nails, a change in the voice where eyes, and in general, hairs on the hands, feet and back were signs that tended to testify to the true nature Of the suspect. </span><span class="ContentBox" data-cd="Text">A strange fatigue, </span>A sad or melancholy look and a sudden lack of appetite were also signs not to be overlooked. The rumor also claimed that his thirst was inextinguishable and that it was almost impossible for him to shed tears.</p>
<p>During the medieval period and the Renaissance, the classic method of formally recognizing a werewolf was to incise the skin of the alleged lycanthropist to see whether hairs were hidden there because, according to certain French and Quebecois legends, Had to turn his skin and turn into a werewolf, as this anecdote testifies:<br />
&#8220;Pomponace, a peasant suffering from lycanthropy, was shouted to his neighbors to escape if they did not want to&#8221; He eats them. As the poor man was not in the shape of a wolf, the villagers, convinced that he was, had begun to flay him to see if he did not wear the hair under his skin. Pomponace cured him, as many others would have been cured if it had not been better to burn them to frighten the indignities.<br />
According to a Russian belief, a lycanthrope could easily be unmasked by the hairs he had under his tongue.<br />
In Hungarian and Balkan folklore, many werewolves were described as vampiric witches who became wolves in order to suck the blood of men who were born on a full moon day. In their human form, these werewolves were pale, had an emaciated face, hollow sockets, swollen lips and flabby arms. As soon as the lycanthrope was formally identified, it was possible to administer a remedy, to enclose it in order to judge it, or to execute it. Many werewolves were described as vampiric witches who became wolves in order to suck the blood of men who were born on a full moon day. In their human form, these werewolves were pale, had an emaciated face, hollow sockets, swollen lips and flabby arms. As soon as the lycanthrope was formally identified, it was possible to administer a remedy, to enclose it in order to judge it, or to execute it. Many werewolves were described as vampiric witches who became wolves in order to suck the blood of men who were born on a full moon day. In their human form, these werewolves were pale, had an emaciated face, hollow sockets, swollen lips and flabby arms. As soon as the lycanthrope was formally identified, it was possible to administer a remedy, to enclose it in order to judge it, or to execute it.</p>
<p>In most legends a werewolf had no means of changing its condition, and only death could deliver it. Yet different remedies were recognized as effective in fighting wolf transformation, and there were many ways to cure lycanthropes, which varied according to the time, country and myth.<br />
In most cases it was assumed that lycanthropy resulted from a curse or possession and it was therefore sufficient to practice an exorcism in order to drive away the demonic spirit that had seized the body of the unfortunate.<br />
In ancient times, in order to cure people with lycanthropy, Greeks and Romans believed in the power of exhaustion. The lycanthrope was then subjected to long periods of physical activity in the hope of ridding him of this disease. This practice resulted from the fact that many suspected werewolves felt weak when they regained their human form.<br />
In Scandinavia, western Russia and central Europe, some 15th-century legends reported the existence of magic philters that could help the werewolves regain their original appearance.<br />
In Denmark a simple reprimand could overcome lycanthropy, and in some parts of Germany it was claimed that a werewolf could be cured if his name was baptized three times. In the middle Ages, The conversion to Christianity was one of the methods used and a devotion to Saint-Hubert was advocated both as a remedy and protection.<br />
Scandinavian, Western Russian and Central European legends mentioned magic philtres which were able to restore its human aspect to the lycanthropist. These philters were prepared with aconite, a plant also known as wolf-wolf.</p>
<p>While some of the methods were relatively mild, most remedies advocated by medieval doctors were unfortunately fatal to patients.<br />
In order to restore his human appearance to the lycanthrope, it was also possible to find the skin of a wolf that he used to transform himself and that he concealed in a secret place, usually a tree stump, in order to burn it. The werewolf then suffered terribly and uttered frightful cries of pain, but he was eventually delivered from his curse.<br />
According to a Quebec belief, the lycanthrope had to be marked at the bottom by carving a cross with a knife, in memory of Christ, or prick it and shed its blood in memory of the martyrdom of Christ.<br />
A former Sicilian superstition claimed that a werewolf could be cured of his disease if he was beaten on the forehead or scalp with a knife, or if his hands were pierced with nails. They could also be beaten with a key or shed his blood because a few drops of blood poured had to make him recover his human form. Once cured, an ancient lycanthrope usually kept the ability to understand the language of wolves.</p>
<h2>Protecting yourself from a Werewolf</h2>
<p><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/pendaison-loup-garou.jpg" alt="Hanging a Werewolf" width="513" height="250" /></p>
<p>If a lycanthrope roamed around, there were very few ways to protect themselves effectively. In Belgium, the rowan was considered to be efficient and it was thought that a house sheltered by the shadow of a rowan was a place on. To stop a werewolf, there was a simple but hazardous way. It was enough to take keys and throw them behind while facing the lycanthropist. It could also be sprinkled with water, which logically had to make him regain human form. By throwing him holy water, the Werewolf sometimes disappeared but he could also turn into a goblin or a vampire. However, this transformation lasted from 1 day to 3 weeks, which generally allowed the victim to escape.<br />
One could also try to poison the evil creature. But it was a relatively risky and generally discouraged method, for the werewolf, being half animal, had a powerful sense of smell. Therefore, he could easily detect any toxic substance. According to some beliefs, cutting off the paw of a werewolf could destroy the charm of his metamorphosis, forcing him to regain his human form, but with a sliced ​​hand or foot. The sensitivity of the werewolves to religious objects such as holy water and crucifixes is a relatively recent belief. Thus obliging him to regain his human form, but with a sliced ​​hand or foot. The sensitivity of the werewolves to religious objects such as holy water and crucifixes is a relatively recent belief. Thus obliging him to regain his human form, but with a sliced ​​hand or foot. The sensitivity of the werewolves to religious objects such as holy water and crucifixes is a relatively recent belief.</p>
<h2>Kill a Werewolf</h2>
<div id="attachment_969" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-full wp-image-969" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/La-Bete-de-Changy.jpg" alt="The Beast of Changy" width="424" height="250" /></p>
<p class="wp-caption-text">The Beast of Changy</p>
</div>
<p>If all the methods of protecting himself from the werewolf were ineffective and no one could identify the responsible person, then he had to be killed when he metamorphoses into a wolf. But the lycanthropes were skilful creatures who often escaped traps and their harsh skin effectively protected them from conventional attacks. However, the wounds made to the werewolves when they were in their animal form were generally found on their human body, which made it easy to recognize them later. The lycanthropists had great resistance and quickly recovered their physical integrity, even though their limbs were severed but decapitation was an undeniable means of overcoming them.</p>
<p>Weapons and silver objects, such as spears, bullets, swords, daggers, or arrows, were deemed to be effective. It was better, however, to bless these weapons, and this blessing was to take place at night, at precise times. Rare and precious objects and a chapel dedicated to Saint-Hubert could further accentuate the effectiveness of the blessings. In the nineteenth century, when the beast of Gevaudan was killed by a silver bullet, the vulnerability of the werewolves to money became indisputable. In Brittany, it was preferred to decapitate the lycanthropus with an ax or a scythe before throwing his body into the river. In the Middle Ages, as witnessed by the numerous executions for lycanthropy, fire and hanging were also effective ways of putting an end to the evil deeds of the evil creature.</p>
<p>In some parts of Germany, northern France and Poland, it was generally accepted that people who died in mortal sin returned in the form of a wolf to drink blood before returning to their homes. Envelope human body from the first gleams of the sun. These lycanthropes were decapitated with a knife and exorcised by the parish priest, and then their head was thrown into a stream, where the crushing weight of their sins dragged him to the bottom.</p>
<p>But even after their death, lycanthropists could still be a problem. Until the 20th century the Greeks believed that the corpses of werewolves that were not destroyed returned to life as wolves, hyenas or vampires and roamed the battlefields to drink the blood of the dying soldiers .</p>
<p>Rural people believed in the existence of werewolves ravaging the countryside and attacking animals as well as humans, and when a person was recognized as a lycanthropist, his judgment was without appeal. However, lycanthropy, as a physical metamorphosis, posed problems from its supernatural side and aroused a certain incredulity among thinkers and scholars and this from ancient Greece. Pliny the Elder indicated that it was not necessary to believe in it, and the Greek physician Arétée assimilated lycanthropy to a disease.<br />
Moreover, the status of werewolves was incompatible with the teachings of the Roman Catholic Church as they were considered a demonic manifestation. The Bible gave no explanation of them, and the theologians were obliged to find one by themselves. It emerged that the demon could not in any case transform a human body into that of a wolf thanks to its magical powers, for only God possessed the power of creation.<br />
The theory that a demon or sorcerer could project his soul into the body of a wolf was also rejected because their powers could not be equivalent to two of God.<br />
Thomas Aquinas, relying on the writings of Augustine Hippome, asserted that metamorphoses were illusions of the Devil, which did not affect either the body or the soul, but the phantasticum, a sort of phantom projection of the &#8221; man. The metamorphosis into wolf was therefore an illusion. It emerged that the demon could not in any case transform a human body into that of a wolf thanks to its magical powers, for only God possessed the power of creation. The theory that a demon or sorcerer could project his soul into the body of a wolf was also rejected because their powers could not be equivalent to two of God. Thomas Aquinas, relying on the writings of Augustine Hippome, asserted that metamorphoses were illusions of the Devil, which did not affect either the body or the soul, but the phantasticum, a sort of phantom projection of the &#8221; man. The metamorphosis into wolf was therefore an illusion. It emerged that the demon could not in any case transform a human body into that of a wolf thanks to its magical powers, for only God possessed the power of creation. The theory that a demon or sorcerer could project his soul into the body of a wolf was also rejected because their powers could not be equivalent to two of God. Thomas Aquinas, relying on the writings of Augustine Hippome, asserted that metamorphoses were illusions of the Devil, which did not affect either the body or the soul, but the phantasticum, a sort of phantom projection of the &#8221; man. The metamorphosis into wolf was therefore an illusion. The theory that a demon or sorcerer could project his soul into the body of a wolf was also rejected because their powers could not be equivalent to two of God. Thomas Aquinas, relying on the writings of Augustine Hippome, asserted that metamorphoses were illusions of the Devil, which did not affect either the body or the soul, but the phantasticum, a sort of phantom projection of the &#8221; man. The metamorphosis into wolf was therefore an illusion. The theory that a demon or sorcerer could project his soul into the body of a wolf was also rejected because their powers could not be equivalent to two of God. Thomas Aquinas, relying on the writings of Augustine Hippome, asserted that metamorphoses were illusions of the Devil, which did not affect either the body or the soul, but the phantasticum, a sort of phantom projection of the &#8221; man. The metamorphosis into wolf was therefore an illusion. A sort of phantom projection of man. The metamorphosis into wolf was therefore an illusion. A sort of phantom projection of man. The metamorphosis into wolf was therefore an illusion.</p>
<p>During the sixteenth and seventeenth centuries, the beliefs remained perennial and the lawsuits for lycanthropy were very numerous. Those who expressed doubts as to the veracity of the phenomenon took the risk of being suspected of sympathy for the sorcerers. The skeptics were few and the doctors were very discreet. The werewolves were detested by the inquisitors, who mercilessly pursued them. A large number of unfortunate accused of lycanthropia were burned daily, and the theologians and devotees complained continually that they were not burning enough.</p>
<p>Henry Boguet, a notorious Inquisitor, had nine cases involving werewolves. He thought the werewolf was a direct manifestation of the Devil.<br />
According to him, Satan abandoned the sleeping lycanthropus in a bush and brought out a wolf. The animal then committed crimes that haunted the mind of the sleeper and disturbed his imagination to such an extent that the lycanthropus had really believed he had metamorphosed into a wolf. He therefore thought he had run the campaign by massacring animals and human beings. Although the reality of physical transformation was questioned in this theory, the werewolf was still held accountable for his actions because he had agreed with the demon, which was an extremely serious crime.</p>
<p>Delancre reported this anecdote on a Duke of Russia, who, warned that his subject was changing into all sorts of animals, sent for him; And, after having chained him, commanded him to make an experiment of his art; Which he soon changed into a wolf; but this duke, having prepared two mastiffs, made them spring against this wretch, who was at once beaten to pieces.</p>
<p>Aristide Dey described the nature of the so-called werewolves thus:<br />
&#8220;In remote times, where obscurantism and superstitions reigned, beings depraved by misery, exalted out of the ways of humanity by the use of intoxicating drugs, Covered themselves with the skin of a wolf, trained themselves to run four feet, and, throwing terror into the people in this disguise, lived through depradations and went so far as to feed on human flesh. &#8221;</p>
<h2>Lycanthropy, Famous Cases and Trials</h2>
<div id="attachment_970" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-full wp-image-970" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/Loup-garou-Normandie.jpg" alt="Loup-Garou in Normandy" width="396" height="250" /></p>
<p class="wp-caption-text">Loup-Garou in Normandy</p>
</div>
<p>From the end of the Middle Ages to the Renaissance, over a hundred years ago, many reports of werewolf attacks and nearly 30,000 lycanthropic trials were recorded in France. It is estimated that the number of trials in Europe was 100,000 but according to Collin de Plancy, tens of thousands of other suspected lycanthropists would have perished without trial, victims of popular vindictiveness.</p>
<p>In some cases there was evidence of murder and cannibalism, without any association with wolves, and in other cases people were simply frightened by wolves. Those found guilty of lycanthropy were burnt at the stake or skinned alive, for legend had it that the hairs of the wolf were concealed under his skin. And sometimes, more rarely, they were hanged, quite simply. At the beginning of the seventeenth century, sorcery was condemned by James I of England and it was not until July 21, 1682, that trials of witchcraft were banned in France.</p>
<p>In 1182, Giraldus claimed to have discovered, in Ireland, a couple of Wolves. But we do not know more about this.</p>
<p>In 1440, Gilles de Rais was executed for acts of barbarism and lycanthropy.</p>
<p>In 1521, Pierre Burgeot and Michel Verdun were accused of lycanthropy by Jean Bodin, the prior of the Dominican convent of Poligny. The trial, which took place at Besancon, attracted a large crowd of curious. The accused were both convicted and burned alive. Their portraits remained posted in the village church to remind everyone what men were capable of doing when they were under the influence of the Devil.<br />
In the same year, three men accused of lycanthropy were burned alive in Besancon. They had admitted that after they had rubbed themselves with fat they changed into wolves, mated with wolves, and devoured several children.</p>
<p>In 1541, in Pavia, Italy, a farmer was suspected of having shredded a large number of people with his teeth while in the form of a wolf. After his capture, he asserted that the only difference between a real wolf and him resided in the fur. She was pushing outward for a wolf, and inwardly for her.</p>
<p>In 1542, according to Henry Boguer, one hundred and fifty werewolves assembled in a square in Constantinople.</p>
<p>In 1573, during the autumn, when a terrible famine was raging, many crimes were committed on children whose bodies were found torn and devoured. Everything indicated that they had been attacked by wolves. The suspicions then turned to Gilles Garnier, a hermit who lived with his family in the middle of the forest of the Serre, in Armange. After being captured, the villagers took him to the Dole court. On 16 January 1574, after the suspect confessed to his crimes, the court delivered his verdict. Among the charges against him, he was accused, among others, of having consumed meat on a Friday, which was formally forbidden. &#8220;Gilles Garnier, who had fallen into witchcraft, had taken and taken several children between the ages of six and twelve, both with his hands as his paws and with his teeth,</p>
<p>In 1584, Pierre Gandillon and his son Georges were arrested and accused of having murdered and devoured many adolescents after smearing the body with an ointment. Their appearance had changed, they moved on all fours, they were provided with nails hard, thick and sharp as claws.</p>
<p>In 1588 Arline de Barioux was burned in the main square of Riom. He was accused of turning into a wolf every Friday afternoon to devour the children.</p>
<p>In 1598, in the Loire valley, Jacques Rollet, a simple-minded man who thought he was a wolf, had been discovered near the bloodied corpse of a 15-year-old boy. Jacques Rollet was already known as the werewolf of Caude.<br />
According to various testimonies, he had fled the place of his crime before being found half naked in the woods. His long hair and big beard were tangled, and his blood-clad hands still held pieces of flesh. In his judgment, Jacques Rollet explained that he had killed judges, lawyers and bailiffs but that the flesh of the latter was hard and tasteless. The court had sentenced him to death but he was considered mentally defective and interned in an asylum where he had stayed for two years.</p>
<div id="attachment_971" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-full wp-image-971" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/Peter-Stumbb.jpg" alt="Peter Stumbb " width="398" height="250" /></p>
<p class="wp-caption-text">Peter Stumbb</p>
</div>
<p>In 1589 the trial and killing of Peter Stumbb, the most famous killer of the suspected werewolves, took place. He was known as the Werewolf of Bedburg. During his trial, he declared that the devil had given him a magic belt that allowed him to transform into a hungry wolf, a voracious, strong and powerful wolf, with large eyes that shone like fire in the night, a Large mouth with pointed and cruel teeth, a gigantic body and powerful legs. &#8220;.</p>
<p>From the same period, the story of a sanguinary tailor has reached us. The man disguised himself as a wolf and roamed the forests at dusk, attacking children and young people to open their throats. Sometimes he would attract the unfortunate in his shop, he would beat them and cut off their necks before cutting them into pieces, like butcher&#8217;s meat. At his execution he showed no remorse. The record of his trial was so horrible that the court decided not to keep it and ordered it to be destroyed.</p>
<p>In 1603, Jean Grenier of Aquitaine, a young boy of thirteen or fourteen years, was accused of lycanthropy. He was physically retarded and mentally deficient, but he was nevertheless considered responsible for the disappearance of children, including that of an infant in his cradle. After his arrest, he asserted that he was the son of a priest and admitted that he had devoured about fifteen children. In reality, his father was a farmman who was so violent towards him that the boy had fled to escape. Delivered to himself, he lived in a savage manner, subsisted through begging and worked occasionally.<br />
During his trial, the judge took his age and disabilities into account and ordered the boy to be interned for life in a cloister. Seven years later, When Pierre de Lancre visited him, it was explained to him that since his arrival, Jean Grenier refused to eat normally. He apparently preferred devouring filth. He was sickly thin, his eyes were sunk and they were burning with a disturbing glow. His hands, with curled nails, resembled claws, and his teeth were long and pointed. He imitated the wolves and moved on all fours with agility. A year later Jean Grenier died. The story of Jean Grenier of Aquitaine influenced the attitude of the judges on the affairs of lycanthropy. But the trials, the tortures, and the executions that followed were all the same. He was sickly thin, his eyes were sunk and they were burning with a disturbing glow. His hands, with curled nails, resembled claws, and his teeth were long and pointed. He imitated the wolves and moved on all fours with agility. A year later Jean Grenier died. The story of Jean Grenier of Aquitaine influenced the attitude of the judges on the affairs of lycanthropy. But the trials, the tortures, and the executions that followed were all the same. He was sickly thin, his eyes were sunk and they were burning with a disturbing glow. His hands, with curled nails, resembled claws, and his teeth were long and pointed. He imitated the wolves and moved on all fours with agility. A year later Jean Grenier died. The story of Jean Grenier of Aquitaine influenced the attitude of the judges on the affairs of lycanthropy. But the trials, the tortures, and the executions that followed were all the same. The story of Jean Grenier of Aquitaine influenced the attitude of the judges on the affairs of lycanthropy. But the trials, the tortures, and the executions that followed were all the same. The story of Jean Grenier of Aquitaine influenced the attitude of the judges on the affairs of lycanthropy. But the trials, the tortures, and the executions that followed were all the same.</p>
<p>In 1605 Henry Gandinn, a native of Limburg, was accused of turning into a werewolf using sorcery. He was transformed into a wolf in the company of two other men, one of whom was named Jan Wolf.<br />
Henry Gardinn declared at his confession that the three men had attacked, killed and ate a child while they were in the form of a wolf. Henry Gardinn had been found guilty of witchcraft for the purpose of turning into a werewolf, and was condemned to be burned alive. During his arrest, his alleged accomplice, Jan the Wolf, had left the parish, but was arrested two years later and executed in turn.</p>
<p>In 1651 Hans appeared before the tribunal of Idavare. He was accused of being a werewolf for his eighteen years. Hans confessed to being a werewolf for two years. He claimed that he had obtained the body of a wolf by a man in black. When the judges asked him if his body had really taken part in the hunt, or if it was his soul that had been transmuted, Hans replied that he had found on his leg the traces of bites that a dog had made him when &#8216;He was a werewolf.</p>
<p>In 1692, at Jurgenburg, in Livonia, Thiess testified under oath that he and the other werewolves were the dogs of God. He claimed that they were warriors who had gone to hell with witches and demons. Their efforts had ensured that the Devil and his henchmen did not carry the grain of the last harvests into hell.<br />
Thiess was firm in his assertions, saying that werewolves in Germany and Russia had also fought the devil&#8217;s henchmen in their own versions of hell. He maintained that when the werewolves died, their souls were welcomed into heaven in thanksgiving for their service. Thiess was finally sentenced to ten lashes for idolatry and superstitious belief.</p>
<p>Between 1500 and 1700, about 100,000 people were sentenced for lycanthropy and burned alive. During the 17th century, doctors&#8217; explanations of lycanthropy put an end to most tortures and killings. However, the population remained fearful and preferred supernatural explanations. Many instances of animal attacks on herds or men inevitably resurfaced the legend of the werewolf.<br />
Nowadays, there are always people who sincerely believe themselves to be werewolves and others who think that lycanthropes exist and that some human beings really turn into wolves.</p>
<div id="attachment_583" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="size-full wp-image-583" src="http://www.mindshadow.fr/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/la-bete-du-gevaudan.jpg" alt="The Gevaudan's beast" width="600" height="250" /></p>
<p class="wp-caption-text">The Gevaudan&#8217;s beast</p>
</div>
<p>In 1764, more than 300 people were victims of the Beast of Gevaudan, which raged in Lozère and the surrounding area. She was described as a giant wolf or a werewolf. His story inspired many theories.</p>
<p>In July 1766, the Quebec Gazette announced that a werewolf was running in the county of Kamouraska.</p>
<p>In 1766, the beast of Sarlat, in the Dordogne, massacred fifteen people.</p>
<p>Towards the middle of the 19th century, in a small village in Poland, a werewolf took away the most beautiful girl in the village.</p>
<p>In 1804, a man named Maréchal, accused of lycanthropy, was condemned to the galleys.</p>
<p>In 1853, in Spain, Manuel Blanco Romasanta admitted to killing thirteen people because he suffered from a curse that transformed him into a wolf.</p>
<p>In 1887, a wild coyote terrorized miners in Saskatchewan, Canada. He was struck down with a golden bullet, and the object was extracted from his body. The story was reported by miners to the writer Ed Bodin in 1940.</p>
<p>In 1899, in Pennsylvania, a peaceful old man had a reputation for being a werewolf.</p>
<p>Shortly before the First World War, three werewolves roamed the Belgian Ardennes.<br />
At the same time, in Scotland, a shepherd from the neighborhood of Inverness was suspected of lycanthropy.</p>
<p>In 1925, a young boy from an Alsatian village was accused of being a werewolf.</p>
<p>In 1930, a werewolf was raging in the region of Bourg-la-Reine.</p>
<p>In 1946, a mysterious creature with all the characteristics of the werewolf created terror in a Navajo reserve in North America.</p>
<p>In 1946-1947 a mysterious animal attacked many herds in the canton of Valais, Switzerland. The affair was never elucidated.</p>
<p>In 1949, in Rome, the police had to investigate a strange affair: every month, at the full moon, a man of the city was in the grip of strange hallucinations and uttered sinister howlings.</p>
<p>In 1957, English newspapers reported the sad story of a seventeen-year-old man from the village of Eccles Hall who thought he was going to turn into a werewolf. To put an end to the moral suffering he endured, he had plunged a knife into his heart. The inquest opened after his death revealed that the unfortunate man had telephoned one of his friends before performing his gesture: &#8220;He told me that his face and his hands were changing colors and that he was Become a werewolf. Then he stopped, and then I heard grunts. &#8221;</p>
<p>In Singapore, again in 1957, mysterious aggressions defeated the police. The rumor was that the attackers were werewolves who were attacking the residents of a nursing home. One night, one of the nurses had awakened with a start to see a horrible bestial face whose hair was so low on the forehead that they reached the root of the nose and whose mouth left sharp fangs. The mystery was never elucidated.</p>
<p>In 1975-1976, the Beast of the Vosges who killed many domestic animals was never identified. She reappeared in 1994 and she slaughtered eighty animals.</p>
<p>In 1978, in the south of Brazil, Rosario do Sul, a 16-year-old schoolgirl, was plagued by demonic visions. She asserted that the spirit of a ferocious wolf had seized her.</p>
<p>In 1982, in the Creuse, a carnivorous creature was at the origin of a series of attacks on flocks. The corpses of the animals, including a bull and a heifer of 400 kg, were horribly shredded. In an organized battle in Noth Forest in November 1982, a hunter claimed to have confronted the animal without successfully identifying it. The case has never been elucidated.</p>
<p>In 1988, in Germany, near Wittlich, a creature close to the dog, passed the alarms of a military base and crossed the surrounding wall after standing on its feet. The dogs at the base refused to chase her.</p>
<p>In 2003, in Switzerland, a man was prosecuted for killing his wife with a knife. He told the criminal court in Lausanne: &#8220;I saw his canines growing. They had a strange odor. Like that of a werewolf &#8220;. According to the psychiatric expert report, he maintained a contact with reality.</p>
<p>In 2013, according to some residents of Vallée-Pitot, a werewolf would appear in places where there would be silence in order to spy on women while they were in the shower or sleeping girls. Witnesses asserted that the creature, presented as agile and particularly fast, would sometimes resound its heavy steps on the roof of houses.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/legend-of-the-werewolf/">Legend of the Werewolf</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Make Homemade Lasagna</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/make-homemade-lasagna/</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 08:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Misc]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=124</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/make-homemade-lasagna/">How to Make Homemade Lasagna</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The lasagna, generally everyone likes it. The perfect friendly dish par excellence, which is always unanimous at table for young and old. In addition, lasagna is not complicated to do. For a basic recipe, a good Bolognese sauce, a béchamel and lasagna pasta.</p>
<p>I often use ready-to-use lasagna pastes, preferring those that are found in the fresh department and which give better results than the dry versions. But when you have a good hour in front of you, you can also go and make homemade pasta with lasagne!</p>
<h3><strong><em>What&#8217;s in the lasagna paste?</em><br />
</strong></h3>
<p>It&#8217;s not as simple as ingredients: flour, eggs and a little olive oil and salt. We can also replace 1/3 of the flour with fine semolina of durum wheat, but since I never have in my cupboards when making lasagna, I find that it goes very well.</p>
<p>According to the recipes, there are pasta made with a large quantity of eggs. I think that&#8217;s enough. With the proportions of my recipe, you can make a large gratin dish for 8 or 9 people, or two dishes of 4 people.</p>
<h3><em><strong>Is it long to do?</strong></em></h3>
<p>I&#8217;m not going to hide it, it&#8217;s a little longer to do that to open a package of pasta with lasagne. With a robot, the dough is very fast to make, but it must be left to stand for at least 30 minutes before going to the rolling mill. Then, when we have our lasagna leaves, let them dry for at least 30 minutes, which makes a good hour of waiting before mounting his lasagne dish.</p>
<p>Usually, I use these waiting times to prepare my bolognese and my béchamel.</p>
<h3><strong><em>What do you need as material?</em></strong></h3>
<p>The indispensable utensil is the rolling mill. You can find them on the net (at Mathon for example), or in the shops where you are used to buying your culinary equipment ( <a href="http://www.genevievelethu.com/">Geneviève Lethu</a> , <a href="http://www.toc.fr/materiel/machine-a-pates-manuelle-atlas-150.html">TOC</a> , the <a href="http://www.lacuisineriedeschartrons.com/site/accueil.php">Cookery of Chartrons</a> for the Bordelais), and it costs between 30 and 50 euros.</p>
<p>Otherwise, if you have a robot like my Kenwood or Kitchenaid, you can add the accessory rolling mill, it costs a little more expensive, in the 70 euros. That&#8217;s what I have and it&#8217;s super easy when you&#8217;re all alone in the kitchen, you do not need someone to turn the crank while the dough is being put through the rolling mill.</p>
<h3><em><strong>What is the recipe?</strong></em></h3>
<p>As I said above, for a large gratin dish, you need 300 g flour (+ or &#8211; 30 g), 3 eggs, 1 pinch of salt and a tablespoon of olive oil .</p>
<p>In the bowl of a robot, mix all the ingredients, until a homogeneous paste and not sticky. Depending on the size of the eggs, add a little flour (30 grams on average). Form a ball, enclose it in food film and leave to stand for 30 minutes.</p>
<h3><em><strong>How do you use the rolling mill?</strong></em></h3>
<p>Check the photo below.</p>
<p><a href="https://i2.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150843_1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-14602" title="P1150843_1" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150843_1-300x225.jpg?resize=300%2C225" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" srcset="https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150843_1-300x225.jpg 300w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150843_1-600x450.jpg 600w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150843_1.jpg 640w" alt="" data-recalc-dims="1" data-pagespeed-url-hash="152598702" /></a></p>
<p>First we take a ball of dough in his hand. Neither too small nor too big.</p>
<p><a href="https://i1.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150844_1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-14603" title="P1150844_1" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150844_1-300x225.jpg?resize=300%2C225" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" srcset="https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150844_1-300x225.jpg 300w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150844_1-600x450.jpg 600w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150844_1.jpg 640w" alt="" data-recalc-dims="1" data-pagespeed-url-hash="3098007129" /></a> <a href="https://i1.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150846_1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-14604" title="P1150846_1" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150846_1-300x225.jpg?resize=300%2C225" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" srcset="https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150846_1-300x225.jpg 300w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150846_1-600x450.jpg 600w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150846_1.jpg 640w" alt="" data-recalc-dims="1" data-pagespeed-url-hash="398889391" /></a></p>
<p>We set the ring of the rolling mill on 1, we throw a small spoon of flour on the rollers to avoid that it sticks and one passes there the ball of dough.</p>
<p><a href="https://i1.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150847_1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-14605" title="P1150847_1" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150847_1-300x225.jpg?resize=300%2C225" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" srcset="https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150847_1-300x225.jpg 300w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150847_1-600x450.jpg 600w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150847_1.jpg 640w" alt="" data-recalc-dims="1" data-pagespeed-url-hash="4176832688" /></a></p>
<p>A thick strip of dough is obtained that is folded in wallet (thank you the photo)</p>
<p><a href="https://i0.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150848_1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-14606" title="P1150848_1" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150848_1-300x225.jpg?resize=300%2C225" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" srcset="https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150848_1-300x225.jpg 300w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150848_1-600x450.jpg 600w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150848_1.jpg 640w" alt="" data-recalc-dims="1" data-pagespeed-url-hash="263522736" /></a> <a href="https://i2.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150849_1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-14607" title="P1150849_1" src="https://i1.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150849_1-300x225.jpg?resize=300%2C225" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" srcset="https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150849_1-300x225.jpg 300w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150849_1-600x450.jpg 600w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150849_1.jpg 640w" alt="" data-recalc-dims="1" data-pagespeed-url-hash="3208931163" /></a></p>
<p>A few pinches of flour on the dough that is passed back into the rolling mill (always on 1), in any direction it does not matter.</p>
<p><a href="https://i2.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150839_11.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-14608" title="P1150839_1" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150839_11-300x225.jpg?resize=300%2C225" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" srcset="https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150839_11-300x225.jpg 300w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150839_11-600x450.jpg 600w, https://www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/P1150839_11.jpg 640w" alt="" data-recalc-dims="1" data-pagespeed-url-hash="3915682438" /></a></p>
<p>All that remains is to pass the dough (without folding it, eh) into the rolling mill by tightening the ring gradually.</p>
<p>That is to say pass it with the ring on 2, then on 3, etc until 6.</p>
<p><a href="https://i2.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/IMG_2833_1.jpg"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-14609" title="IMG_2833_1" src="https://i2.wp.com/www.audreycuisine.fr/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/IMG_2833_1-199x300.jpg?resize=199%2C300" alt="" data-recalc-dims="1" data-pagespeed-url-hash="2882678382" /></a></p>
<p>Large plates of fresh pasta are then obtained to be dried 30 minutes before using to assemble the dishes of lasagna. To make them dry, the clothes line is very practical &#8230;</p>
<p>Tomorrow I publish my recipe lasagne to the bolognese and after it is up to you to test !!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/make-homemade-lasagna/">How to Make Homemade Lasagna</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
