<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Apps &#8211; ViralMuffin</title>
	<atom:link href="http://viralmuffin.com/category/apps/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://viralmuffin.com/</link>
	<description>Discover the World</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:39:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Graj King of Thieves</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/graj-king-of-thieves/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=98</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/graj-king-of-thieves/">Graj King of Thieves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://movfe.com/srv.html?id=1418014&amp;pub=779619">Zagraj teraz!</a></h1>
<p>Ubierz klejnoty, buduj swoją obronę i wygrywaj wojnę gildii w tej unikalnej kombinacji gry zręcznościowej, platformy i multiplayer PVP!<br />
Konkurować z ponad 50 milionami użytkowników na całym świecie i tworzyć własne klany złodziei. Przenieś się do lochu wroga i ukradnij złoto.<br />
Udowodnij, że jesteś najmądrzejszym i najzdolniejszym złodziejem na świecie!</p>
<p>UWAGA: gra jest bardzo wciągająca i nieuchronnie prowadzi do zwiększenia liczby Twoich znajomych.</p>
<p>KLUCZOWE CECHY:</p>
<p>STANDARDOWE WYDARZENIA. Kradzieży to zabawa! Zbieraj złoto i kamienie innych graczy, aby stać się najbogatszym złodziejem na świecie.<br />
OCHRONA DWA. Zaprojektuj broń obronną, pułapki i platformy, aby uniemożliwić innym kradzież skarbu. Zobacz, jak zostali złapani w pułapki. Nie ma ucieczki, muhaha!<br />
ZAREJESTRUJ SIĘ THRONE. Zanurkuj się w akcji, zwiększ swoje umiejętności i konkurować z innymi graczami na całym świecie, aby przejść na szczyty liderów.<br />
JOIN GUILD. Znajdź wiarygodne dudy i ogłaszaj wojnę innym gildiom. Wygraj epickie walki klanów!<br />
DOSTOSUJ TWÓJ WYDAJNOŚĆ. Wybierz fajny kostium, który idealnie pasuje do twojej osobowości. Bądź eleganckim złodziejem, wyróżnij się z tłumu!<br />
PODRÓŻ I PRZEGLĄD. Sprawdź swoją zwinność dzięki 112 poziomom pojedynczego trybu lub zanurz się w podziemnym świecie treści generowanych przez użytkowników.<br />
_________________________________________________________<br />
SUBSKRYPCJA. Subskrybuj, aby mieć szansę szybszego i szybkiego dostępu do ekskluzywnych kostiumów!</p>
<p>Poprzez subskrypcję Króla Złodziei otrzymuje się:<br />
&#8211; blokady x10 (zwiększenie maksymalnej pojemności)<br />
&#8211; Odblokowanie blokady bloków jest szybsze od x10<br />
&#8211; Kopalnia złota wytwarza codziennie &#8220;łzy&#8221;<br />
&#8211; 3 unikalne stroje<br />
_________________________________________________________</p>
<p>Gotowi sprostać wyzwaniu? Gra na!<br />
Dołącz do społeczności, znajdź przyjaciół i sprawdź wiadomości:<br />
<a href="http://www.facebook.com/kingofthievesgame">www.facebook.com/kingofthievesgame</a><br />
<a href="http://www.twitter.com/kingthieves">www.twitter.com/kingthieves</a><br />
&#8220;Król złodziei to dobrze zaprojektowane wyzwanie dla wielu graczy, które pozwoli Ci wrócić i zdecydowanie ukradnia ofertę bezpłatnej rozrywki&#8221; &#8211; Apple&#8217;N&#8217;Apps</p>
<p>&#8220;Król złodziei to najcudowniejsza gra PvP, która może się pojawić od dłuższego czasu. Dobrze być zły, więc idź dalej i rozkoszuj się &#8220;- Gamezebo</p>
<p>&#8220;King of Thieves jest jednym z największych aplikacjach tam” &#8211; App Mag</p>
<p>&#8220;King of Thieves to z pewnością warto go wypróbować gry teraz” &#8211; ZoGames</p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/BPVU1uxVIK_gZy_JS5Lbsa_TQ0TKeR-18hhrZW5kfL-aBTGgHTZvLyM8zjMWbkispQ=h900-rw" alt="  King of Thieves – zrzut ekranu " /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/graj-king-of-thieves/">Graj King of Thieves</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invasion: Modern Empire</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/invasion-modern-empire/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=93</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/invasion-modern-empire/">Invasion: Modern Empire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Invasion: Modern Empire is an exciting online warfare simulation and STR game type that challenges you to confront different enemy factions, conquer their territory and make their way to world domination in the midst of a global apocalypse . Fight to become the most powerful military commander in the world and walk towards victory!</p>
<p><b>Invasion Features: Modern Empire </b></p>
<p><b>Your enemies are going to nail their nails with this STR type fighting style to ward off the apocalypse! </b></p>
<p>• Military strategy, real &#8211; time fighting and building your base<br />
• Destroy the world and rebuild it in its image by conquering enemy armies<br />
• Strategic battles in 3D and real &#8211;</p>
<p><b>Action Fight for every inch of terrain and expand your Alliance territory! </b></p>
<p>• Conquer enemy territory online in a world at war<br />
• Claim territory by performing RAIDS on your enemies<br />
• Conquer is yours, as long as you have soldiers and you organize raids on your enemies. But be careful &#8211; your enemies can also attack your base!</p>
<p><b>War tactics and advanced technology will help you move forward and get information about your enemies</b></p>
<p>• Modern warfare is how to spy on your enemies. Dominate your opponents by collecting information about their bases<br />
• Command your troops and conquer territories using a panoramic map in real time! Fight against other alliances in the War of Monuments PVP!</p>
<p><b>Battle online against alliances and crush every alliance on your way</b></p>
<p>• Online multiplayer mode allows you to form an alliance and compete against other players to become the ultimate commander<br />
• Online chat and other features will help you To find the perfect alliance<br />
• Online multiplayer games feature PvP MMO combat on a modern battlefield<br />
Fight with other alliances to occupy &#8220;war monuments&#8221;<br />
• Raid monuments to experiment Changes and surprise real-time fights!<br />
• Create diplomatic ties with other players as you see fit!<br />
• PvP gameplay sends you to war alongside a ton of other players! Fight in the post-apocalyptic world of 2020!</p>
<p>Do you have what it takes to survive in this world at war?</p>
<p><b>Download Invasion: Modern Empire and beat now! </b></p>
<p>In Invasion, some game elements can also be bought for real money. If you do not want to use this feature, please set up a<br />
password protection for purchases in your Google Play Store app settings.<br />
Join the community:</p>
<p>• Facebook &#8211; <a href="https://www.facebook.com/InvasionGame">https://www.facebook.com/InvasionGame </a></p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/X29JZnCIo5foyDkJu_vCfwW7_t_OOXeGgQDsGkIvpwNx9bTyEw38rMnb2irFBUgQJk6B=h900-rw" alt=" Invasion: Modern Empire- screenshot " /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/invasion-modern-empire/">Invasion: Modern Empire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disney Magic Kingdoms</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/disney-magic-kingdoms/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=90</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/disney-magic-kingdoms/">Disney Magic Kingdoms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WELCOME TO THE MOST MAGIC PLACE ON MOBILE!</p>
<p>When Maledic will cast a curse on the Kingdom, emptying it of all its magical power, will you help us to save it? Relive the fun of Disney parks and create the most fantastic park of your dreams in Disney Magic Kingdoms!</p>
<p>ATTRACTIONS OF EXTRAORDINARY AND TIMELY DISNEY PARKS<br />
• Attractions such as &#8220;it&#8217;s a small world&#8221;, the Monsters &amp; Co. and Space Mountain laughing factory from Disney parks around the world!<br />
• Exclusive attractions such as the WALL-E House and Cyclope Sushi, all inspired by their respective films!<br />
• Relive the magic moments of the parks with the joyful parades of tanks and fireworks!</p>
<p>A RANGE OF CHARACTERS COVERING MORE THAN 90 YEARS OF DISNEY<br />
• Share spectacular moments with characters like the eternal optimist Mickey Mouse, Rapunzel the fiery princess, the courageous space ranger Buzz Lightning, the adorable and vivid Tinkerbell and many others !<br />
• Play hundreds of quests that support every pixel in your Kingdom!<br />
• Collect Disney items to save each character from the Maledic Curse!</p>
<p>A HOROSCOPE OF HEROES AND MISTAKES<br />
• Discover a magical story and an exciting adventure!<br />
• Face evil villains such as Pat Hibulaire, Mother Gothel and Zurg to save the Kingdom!</p>
<p>Come and play the most magical free mobile game, a great family adventure! It&#8217;s up to you to create your world!</p>
<p>Perfect for fans of Disney, Disneyland, Pixar movie games, management games, free family games, and park building games.</p>
<p>You can download this game for free. Please note that this game also allows you to use virtual currency which can be obtained by progressing in the game, deciding to watch some ads or spending real money. Built-in purchases range from € 0.99 to € 99.99. You can disable embedded purchases by changing your User Controls in your Play Store settings.</p>
<p>Languages: English, French, German, Italian, Indonesian, Japanese, Korean, Brazilian Portuguese, Russian, Simplified Chinese, Traditional Chinese, Spanish, Turkish, Arabic and Thai.</p>
<p>An additional download of 175 to 200 MB is required to play this game. Please note that the size of this download may change without notice.</p>
<p>The game requires an Internet connection (3G or Wi-Fi) for downloads and updates, and other features such as parties with friends, integrated purchases and viewing ads.</p>
<p>Some features of this game, such as collaborating with other players, confronting them or sharing items with them in the game, require that the player be connected to a social network like Facebook or Google+. Please note that this connection is not required to progress in the game. These features may not be available in some countries.</p>
<p>This game may contain third-party advertising that will redirect you to a third party site. You can disable the ad ID used for targeted ads in your device&#8217;s Settings menu. This option can be found in Settings&gt; Personal Accounts&gt; Google&gt; Advertisements (Settings &amp; Privacy)&gt; Disable interest-based ads.</p>
<p>For more info on the game, go to the official website &#8211; <a href="http://www.disney-magic-kingdoms.com/">http://www.disney-magic-kingdoms.com/ </a></p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/0VqHX9h9__AVhsNxldbFrOtKbhzx8mB7fRaMbtZHyC-fkepYsRr9xuyS_OMeiLdauBiQ=h900" alt="Image result for Disney Magic Kingdoms" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/disney-magic-kingdoms/">Disney Magic Kingdoms</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/worlds-best-word-puzzle-game-word-cookies/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 03:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Apps]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=87</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/worlds-best-word-puzzle-game-word-cookies/">The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</p>
<p>This is a new word puzzle game created by <b>BitMango, the creator of the HIT application, Roll the Ball ™ &#8211; slide puzzle and Block hexa puzzle!</b></p>
<p>Word cookies is a very fun and exciting word puzzle game, it allows you to continue playing for FREE!</p>
<p>The goal of the game is to find all the hidden words.<br />
With this game, you can easily improve vocabulary skills, concentration and spelling.</p>
<p>The king of HEADLING<br />
Do you like the word puzzle games? Do you like cookies? Do you like the challenge?<br />
Here is the perfect game for you, Word cookies!</p>
<p>Are you ready to find delicious cookie words at your kitchen oven?<br />
Embrace your intelligence to discover words.</p>
<p>HOW TO PLAY<br />
• Words can be vertical, horizontal, diagonal and even backward.<br />
• Simply slide your finger over a word to select it.<br />
• If you have found a valid word, it will remain highlighted and marked on the list of found words.</p>
<p>Characters<br />
• Discover hidden words in mixed letters<br />
• Find words derived from the main words and develop your brain skills and vocabulary.<br />
• Visually pleasing to play cookies in various types!<br />
• Feeling complete with increased points by making more cookies!<br />
• Simple and easy!<br />
• Daily rewards<br />
• 200 free coins in the first round<br />
• Excellent exercise for the brain<br />
• Available for both laptops and tablets.<br />
• FREE update!</p>
<p>• EASY AND FUN GAME<br />
&#8211; Easy to learn and fun to master the game</p>
<p>• No time limit<br />
&#8211; Enjoy the game anytime, anywhere and even for a little while.</p>
<p>• No WIFI? No problem!<br />
&#8211; You can play offline at any time</p>
<p>• TONS OF UNIQUE LEVELS<br />
&#8211; 32 packages and over 580 impressive levels! Updates will be continued!</p>
<p>NOTES<br />
• Enjoy the game with various devices (laptops and tablets).<br />
• &#8220;Word cookies&#8221; contain banner ads, interstitial ads, videos.<br />
• &#8220;Word cookies&#8221; is free to play, but you can buy items like Non-Pubs and other packages on the shop in this game.</p>
<p>E-MAIL<br />
• contact@bitmango.com</p>
<p>SITE<br />
• <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?Id=6249013288401661340">https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?Id=6249013288401661340</a></p>
<p>Put it Like on FACEBOOK<br />
• <a href="https://www.facebook.com/BitMangoGames">https://www.facebook.com/BitMangoGames</a></p>
<p>Thank you for playing!</p>
<p><img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/hCRo0pQmXiUJ_VJcnmHe87ti8jP268EEBF0pca4td7cfq97_TCVBz5xknvW6XRtWKw=h900" alt="Image result for Word Cookies" /></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/worlds-best-word-puzzle-game-word-cookies/">The World&#8217;s Best Word Puzzle Game &#8220;Word Cookies&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
