<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Health &#8211; ViralMuffin</title>
	<atom:link href="http://viralmuffin.com/category/health/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://viralmuffin.com/</link>
	<description>Discover the World</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 23:07:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.8.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Food, our first medicine?</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/food-first-medicine/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 23:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=257</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>What is the common point between diabetes, cardiovascular disorders, hypertension, osteoporosis, depression, overweight, burnout, stress, hypercholesterolemia or degenerative disorders? They are all directly related to the quality of the diet and the practice of regular physical activity. Indeed, without adequate food and sufficient solicitation of our cells, your body can not maintain its homeostasis. &#8221; We are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/food-first-medicine/">Food, our first medicine?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nutrition and liver detoxification: info or intox?</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/nutrition-liver-detoxification-info-intox/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 23:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=255</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>In our body the liver is the main organ responsible for detoxification, and its activity is adapted to the amount of xenobiotics brought to it. These xenobiotics are molecules foreign to our body such as drugs, hormones, heavy metals, but also the chemical compounds associated with the preparation of food (such as the famous Maillard body). The liver is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/nutrition-liver-detoxification-info-intox/">Nutrition and liver detoxification: info or intox?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bariatric surgery</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/bariatric-surgery/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 23:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=252</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>What are the nutritional consequences of bariatric surgery? In the face of the global challenges of obesity and the relative failures of diets, more and more people are resorting to obesity surgery, also called bariatric surgery. 102,000 procedures were performed in Europe in 2014, nearly 47,000 in France including 13,879 gastric bypass, 27,761 sleeve and 4,533 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/bariatric-surgery/">Bariatric surgery</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Animal Proteins and the Environment: Should You Choose?</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/animal-proteins-environment-choose/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 23:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=249</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>If there is a nutrient attributed to the muscles, it is the proteins. And indeed, it is a major constituent of muscle tissue, whose contributions deserve to be optimized daily when you are interested in sports, when you want to lose weight or just take care of your health . The thinning and the regular practice of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/animal-proteins-environment-choose/">Animal Proteins and the Environment: Should You Choose?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Insect protein, an alternative to animal protein?</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/insect-protein-alternative-animal-protein/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 22:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=245</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>You will take a small skewer of crickets? Indeed, the nutritional and environmental qualities of insects are increasingly being touted. So, is it interesting to jump into the water? A global food issue The current evolution of the world&#8217;s population correlated with the increasing consumption of animal proteins puts the population face a nutritional and ecological stalemate. To [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/insect-protein-alternative-animal-protein/">Insect protein, an alternative to animal protein?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polyamines, cancer and chronic pain: what links?</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/polyamines-cancer-chronic-pain-links/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 22:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=240</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Polyamines, cancer and chronic pain, therapeutic tracks still little explored   Behind this technical term lies a family of molecules essential to life. Primarily three in number &#8211; putrescine, spermidine, spermine &#8211; they are closely involved in cell division and proliferation processes. Some studies thus highlight their potential links in the development of cancer and more recently [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/polyamines-cancer-chronic-pain-links/">Polyamines, cancer and chronic pain: what links?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should we avoid gluten? Milk proteins? What are the roles of the intestinal ecosystem on health?</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/avoid-gluten-milk-proteins-roles-intestinal-ecosystem-health/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 22:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=238</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The intestinal tripod is THE keystone of health, the starting point of any nutritional approach. But before you understand the reasons, do you answer yes to many of these questions? &#160; You suffer from intestinal functional disorders  : digestive discomfort, bloating, regular transit disorders (diarrhea, chronic constipation, alternating diarrhea / constipation), colitis, intestinal inflammations? You suffer from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/avoid-gluten-milk-proteins-roles-intestinal-ecosystem-health/">Should we avoid gluten? Milk proteins? What are the roles of the intestinal ecosystem on health?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>60 million consumers: Gluten-free foods bad for health?</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/60-million-consumers-gluten-free-foods-bad-health/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 22:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=235</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Gluten-free products not healthier for 60 million consumers;  Gluten-free products: a wave that lighten the wallet; Gluten-free is not better for you  . &#8221; According to the media wave surging since this morning following the publication of the article of 60 million consumers, the gluten-free would be harmful to health. This is new information that can cause confusion in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/60-million-consumers-gluten-free-foods-bad-health/">60 million consumers: Gluten-free foods bad for health?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should we eat gluten-free?</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/eat-gluten-free/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 22:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=232</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Particularly publicized in recent years, gluten-free diet is in vogue, including in the sports world. His interest has been highlighted for over 30 years by Dr. Kousmine. The reasons for the adoption of this regime, not to say a way of life, remain unclear to many. We practice the gluten-free diet because we suffer from digestive disorders, allergies, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/eat-gluten-free/">Should we eat gluten-free?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is it good to fast? Can we fast and play sports?</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/good-fast-can-fast-play-sports/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2017 22:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[All]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=227</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Historically practiced for reasons of a religious or therapeutic nature, fasting has been highlighted for a few years for its effects on well-being, including in sports circles. But the mere mention of the word &#8220;fasting&#8221; can cool more than one, as it refers to the concept of restriction: it is characterized by a period of deprivation [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/good-fast-can-fast-play-sports/">Is it good to fast? Can we fast and play sports?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
