<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Game Hacks &#8211; ViralMuffin</title>
	<atom:link href="http://viralmuffin.com/category/game-hacks/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://viralmuffin.com/</link>
	<description>Discover the World</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 21:44:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Last Day on Earth: Survival Hacks and Cheats</title>
		<link>http://viralmuffin.com/last-day-on-earth-survival-hack/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 21:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Yappo]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Game Hacks]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://viralmuffin.com/?p=41</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>&#46;&#46;&#46;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/last-day-on-earth-survival-hack/">Last Day on Earth: Survival Hacks and Cheats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looking to hack Last Day on Earth Survival? Well you&#8217;ve come to the right place with our free tool here you can access Last Day on Earth Survival hacks. Our hack tools are absolutely free to anyone who wants to use them. Access our Last Day on Earth Survival hack by pressing the button below.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://viralmuffin.com/premium-content/">Access Hack</a></p>
<h1>About Last Day on Earth: Survival</h1>
<p><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/last-day-on-earth-zombie-survival/id1241932094">App Store Link</a>, <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=zombie.survival.craft.z">Play Store Link</a></p>
<p>Last Day on Earth is a free multiplayer game combining zombies, survival and strategy. All survivors have one goal: to stay alive and survive as long as possible and kill undead zombies. Friendship, love and compassion no longer exist. A deadly pandemic has ravaged the world. You can count only on yourself in this post-apocalyptic world infested with undead zombies.</p>
<h1>Tips for Survivors:</h1>
<h3>ENEMIES EVERYWHERE!</h3>
<p>You are alone against other players and an army of undead zombies in this rpg shooter mixing action, zombies, survival and strategy. Kill the zombies and other threats to survive in this post-apocalyptic world, or they will kill you.</p>
<h3>STAY CALM AND EQUIP YOURSELF!</h3>
<p>Improve your strategy and create deadly weapons to fight the undead and other enemies. Choose your targets and kill zombies, or shoot down local wildlife for a little food.</p>
<h3>EXPLORE NEW TERRITORIES!</h3>
<p>Search for abandoned military bases and survivor camps to recover deadly weapons and resources. Stay away from the zombie border and shoot down zombies to get resources.</p>
<h3>JOIN A CLAN!</h3>
<p>More power, more opportunities and less chance to die. Shoot undead with other players, it&#8217;s an effective war strategy in this free zombie shooter. It will be easier to survive in this post-apocalyptic game by allying yourself with other survivors to kill the undead, so join a clan and kill as many zombies as possible!</p>
<h3>CONTACT OTHER PLAYERS!</h3>
<p>Use the chat. Getting information is a priority after your own survival in this post-apocalyptic game. Cooperate and kill zombies, or go to loot, discover new territories and push back the zombie border.</p>
<h3>FACE PROBLEMS!</h3>
<p>Wild animals, hunger, thirst and cold can kill you faster than an army of undead. The world is governed by evil, ravaged by the pandemic. In this post-apocalyptic zombie-filled survival rpg, you must make deadly weapons, kill zombies and survive.</p>
<p>In 2027, an unknown virus decimated the majority of the world&#8217;s population. The substance developed by soldiers escaped from one of their secret laboratories. The deadly virus triggered a real pandemic, 80% of the population disappeared as a result of the incident. The pandemic slowly killed all these people, then turned them into hordes of undead.</p>
<p>But the hordes of undead are not your main problem. The other survivors of the pandemic will attack you. Go alone or team up with allies to join a clan, and shoot the zombies together. Choose your path and plunge the zombie border into this post-apocalyptic game mixing zombies, survival, and strategy. Use all means to eliminate zombies and survive in this free zombie shooter.</p>
<p>Welcome to this post-apocalyptic world and have fun in this zombie, survival and strategy game!</p>
<p>Please note that Last Day on Earth is a free multiplayer game combining zombies, survival and strategy, but some items can be bought with real money. To avoid using this feature, disable in-game purchases in your phone or tablet settings. You must be at least 13 years old to download or play Last Day on Earth, a zombie shooter rpg survival and strategy game.</p>
<p>Download today Last Day on Earth, a new free game combining action, zombies, survival and strategy, to kill zombies and survive with your friends!</p>
<div style="width: 1290px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img title="last day on earth survival hack" src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/tA3NM0BhUUA/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="last day on earth survival hack" width="1280" height="720" /><p class="wp-caption-text">last day on earth survival hack</p></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/last-day-on-earth-survival-hack/">Last Day on Earth: Survival Hacks and Cheats</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="http://viralmuffin.com/">ViralMuffin</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
